Chapter 81: The One-eyed Giant and the Centaur

In the blink of an eye, the semi-transparent True Extreme Membrane appeared over Han Li's body, and he quickly stabilized himself as faint silver light flashed over the surface of the thin film.

He was stunned by the incredible power imbued within the giant's punch, but given the formidable defensive prowess of his True Extreme Body, he was able to remain unharmed from the blow.

He immediately cast his gaze foward, upon which his pupils contracted ever so slightly.

Standing several thousand feet away from him as a yellow-skinned giant that was around 2,000 to 3,000 feet tall. Its entire body was riddled with strange spirit patterns, and its facial features were downright hideous, with a snub nose and a massive, unsightly mouth. What was most intriguing about it was that it only had a single enormous vertical eye, with murky light shimmering within its hazy gray pupil.

The giant had a disoriented appearance, but it was giving off a savage aura comparable to a True Immortal, much to Han Li's alarm and concern.

This had nothing to do with the giant's cultivation base. Instead, it was purely an instinctive feeling from Han Li.

The one-eyed giant faltered slightly, seemingly rather taken aback by the fact that Han Li had managed to remain completely unscathed from the clash, and immediately thereafter, it let loose a furious roar. A vast expanse of yellow light rose up from its body, and it stomped through the air as it charged directly toward Han Li.

Han Li quickly began to chant an incantation upon seeing this, and bright golden light erupted from his body as he transformed into a giant golden ape that was over 200 feet tall.

The constellation of seven blue stars appeared on the giant ape's chest and abdomen, giving off bright starlight that intertwined with the golden light radiating from the ape's body, causing it to swell even further in size.

It clenched one of its hands into a tight fist, and the muscles on its arms bulged as it threw a vicious punch at the oncoming one-eyed giant.

The space up ahead warped violently as a mountainous golden fist projection appeared. The fist projection was interspersed with traces of starlight, and the one-eyed giant let loose a thunderous roar as it continued to charge forward without slowing down in the slightest, raising a massive fist of its own to combat the golden fist projection.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and this time, it was the giant that was sent flying back, tumbling down from the sky like an enormous asteroid before landing heavily on the island.

The entire island swayed violently, and a massive crater was smashed into the ground, sending dust and debris rising up into the sky.

In the next instant, the giant golden ape appeared directly above the crater, and its arms blurred as it unleashed countless golden fist projections that came raining down in a relentless barrage.

The one-eyed giant clambered rather unsteadily up from the ground, but it didn't appear to have sustained any injuries. However, it was clearly infuriated, and it let loose an enraged roar as it stomped a foot forcefully down onto the ground.

A series of strange yellow patterns instantly appeared over its body, giving off a burst of translucent yellow light that quickly spread onto the ground around it.

All of the soil on the ground in the wake of the translucent yellow light instantly shattered, transforming into countless grains of translucent yellow sand that rose up into the air before forming a series of bands around the giant's body. In the blink of an eye, a suit of translucent yellow sand armor had taken shape around the one-eyed giant.

A string of loud cracks and bangs rang out as the storm of golden fist projections rained down upon the giant before exploding into bursts of golden light.

However, the one-eyed giant remained completely still like an immovable mountain, and the yellow sand armor that its body was encased also wasn't sustaining any damage.

The giant golden ape faltered slightly upon seeing this, then hurriedly shot back in retreat.

The one-eyed giant cast a cold gaze up toward the golden ape in the sky, then stomped its foot down onto the ground again, and the yellow spirit patterns all over its body flashed as a series of yellow ripples proliferated outward, instantly encompassing an area around it in a radius of close to 10 kilometers.

While still in mid-air, the giant golden ape suddenly felt its own body become significantly heavier. The surrounding gravitational force had increased by severalfold, and it was as if it were being dragged down forcefully by a massive, invisible hand, causing it to plummet out of the sky.

It's using gravitational control! Han Li thought to himself with an alarmed expression.

Immediately thereafter, the giant golden ape slammed heavily down onto the ground, and its feet sank several dozen feet into the earth as countless shattered rock fragments flew in all directions around it.

In the next instant, the one-eyed giant charged onto the scene before lashing out with a giant yellow fist with devastating force, while the golden ape was rooted to the spot like a sitting duck.

The giant's fist swept up a gust of ferocious wind that left a massive white mark in the air.

The giant golden raised its arms and crossed them above its head, while a layer of golden scales instantly appeared over its arms.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of tremendous force spread along the giant ape's arms and into its body, forcing it to sink even further into the ground.

The one-eyed giant swayed slightly before it lashed out with its other fist, and soon, both of its fists had transformed into a pair of blurs as one devastating blow after another came raining down in rapid succession.

The golden ape was able to ward off the attacks with its arms, but this situation was naturally far from ideal.

Even though it possessed exceptional physical resistance and didn't have to fear the one-eyed giant's attacks, it was unable to free itself anytime soon under the effects of the heightened gravity, and it was sinking further and further into the ground from the one-eyed giant's pummeling blows.

At this point, it had already sunk all the way down to its waist, and at this rate, it was going to be buried alive!

Right at this moment, spatial fluctuations suddenly erupted over 1,000 feet behind the one-eyed giant, and a centaur-like creature that was over 1,000 feet tall emerged out of thin air without any warning.

The creature's entire body was enveloped within a gust of fierce azure wind, and it was also entirely of a dark azure color. The bottom half of its body was identical to that of a horse, except it was completely devoid of fur and covered in a layer of thick azure scales instead.

Accompanying this horse-like lower body was a well-built human male upper body that was completely bared. What was even more remarkable was that the creature had three identical heads, one on its neck and two on its shoulders.

As soon as the creature appeared, one of its muscular arms was already raised up high, and it was holding a blue lightning spear in its hand. The spear was several hundred feet in length, and it was hurled viciously at the one-eyed giant's heart from behind.

Arcs of blue lightning were springing wildly over the surface of the spear like boiling water, and in the blink of an eye, the spear had already reached the one-eyed giant.

The giant's attention was focused entirely on its battle against Han Li, and by the time it sensed what was happening behind it, it was already too late to take evasive measures.

It let loose an explosive roar as the spirit patterns all over its body lit up with dazzling yellow radiance, and the surrounding earth in a radius of several kilometers instantly began to tremble violently. At the same time, the translucent yellow sand on the ground behind it abruptly rose up into the air, then intertwined to form a brown wall of sand that stood in the path of the oncoming lightning spear.

A dull thump rang out as the blue lightning spear pierced through the wall of sand with ease, then impaled itself into the one-eyed giant's body.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding boom rang out as countless arcs of lightning erupted from the blue spear amid a burst of dazzling radiance before exploding violently.

The one-eyed giant let loose an agonized roar as a massive hole was blown into its body just above its lower abdomen, and massive volumes of reddish-brown blood came gushing out of the wound.

The centaur-like creature flew back before descending onto the ground several thousand feet away, and an elated look appeared on all three of its faces, but its expression then immediately stiffened.

Contrary to its expectations, the blue lightning spear hadn't managed to pierce through the giant's heart. Instead, as aforementioned, it had pierced through its body just above its lower abdomen, so it had failed to deal a killing blow.

As it turned out, in the instant that the lightning spear pierced through the wall of sand, the one-eyed giant had already controlled the sand beneath its feet to elevate the ground by several dozen feet, thereby just barely avoiding a fatal blow.

Even so, the giant had still suffered severe injuries, and blood was trickling down from the corners of its mouth. At the same time, large, irregular chunks of translucent sand were falling off its body, giving it the appearance of an old and dilapidated wall that was falling apart under the elements.

As a result of this abrupt turn of events, the heightened gravity in the nearby area was abruptly eased, and the giant golden ape immediately sprang out of the ground before rushing to several thousand feet away after just a few flashes.

It then cast its gaze toward the centaur-like creature, upon which its pupils contracted slightly.

Judging from its aura and its ability to conceal itself, it was most likely the one that had sent Han Li flying into this yellow bubble.

Instead of rushing back into the fray, Han Li was carefully watching the pair of titanic monsters before him, waiting to see what they were going to do next.

Right at this moment, the centaur-like creature sprang forward as a gust of ferocious wind swept up all around it, and a new lightning spear had already taken shape in its grasp as it sprang toward the one-eyed giant, stabbing the spear toward the giant's heart with incredible speed and venom.

A murderous gleam surfaced in the giant's eye as it let loose a thunderous roar, and dazzling light erupted from its body.

All of the yellow sand that filled the surrounding area rose up into the air before rapidly converging, forming hundreds of sharp yellow spikes that pierced viciously toward the centaur-like creature.

A hint of surprise flashed through the three-headed centaur's eyes upon seeing this, and bright azure light erupted from its body as it raised its lightning spear horizontally in front of itself. Countless arcs of lightning sprang forth from the spear, instantly forming a net of lightning to shield it from the spikes up ahead.

The yellow spikes crashed into the blue net of lightning incessantly amid a string of resounding booms, and the resulting shockwaves from the clashes sent the centaur-like creature flying back by over 1,000 feet.

However, after manifesting those yellow spikes, the one-eyed giant couldn't help but throw up a mouthful of reddish-brown blood, and the fury in its eyes had become even more pronounced.

It cast a wary glance toward the giant yellow ape in the other direction, then retreated by over 1,000 feet, forming a roughly equilateral triangle with the golden ape and the centaur-like creature.

At the same time, a swirling vortex of yellow light slowly appeared on the wound on its lower abdomen, and the flesh around the wound gradually turned from red to black, then turned into stone.

As the vortex continued to revolve, more and more of the wound turned into stone, and the entire wound was quickly completely filled like the surface of a lake freezing over.

Golden light flashed from Han Li's body upon seeing this, and he quickly shrank down to revert back to his human form, then flipped a hand over to summon his High Zenith Invisibility Talisman.

As the talisman released a burst of purple light, Han Li's body gradually became more and more indistinct before finally vanishing on the spot.

The one-eyed giant faltered slightly upon seeing this.

The centaur-like creature was also rather taken aback by Han Li's sudden disappearance, but it then immediately turned its attention toward the one-eyed giant with a fierce look in its six eyes.

Chapter 82: Clash

The one-eyed giant could sense the centaur-like creature's hostile gaze, and it also directed its attention away as a cold gleam flashed through its eye as it crouched down slightly to lower its center of gravity in preparation for battle.

Electricity flashed within the eyes of one of the centaur-creature's heads, and lightning patterns lit up all over its azure scales. Arcs of blue lightning sprang forth, encircling its entire body, then formed a lightning halberd that was almost as long as the centaur-like creature was tall.

The halberd had arcs of lightning flashing around it, and it was clearly also formed by lightning itself. However, it was far more substantial than the lightning spears from before, and there were many strange patterns on its surface, giving it the appearance of an actual treasure with formidable powers.

The centaur-like creature raised its lightning halberd, then pushed off the ground forcefully with its two hind hooves, launching itself directly toward the one-eyed giant at an incredible speed.

As it charged forward, it swept its lightning halberd through the air, and a tightly packed series of halberd projections instantly appeared before hurtling toward the one-eyed giant.

The giant let loose a low roar as it raised one of its feet, then stomped it heavily down onto the ground. The earth instantly trembled violently as large plumes of dust rose up alongside countless grains of translucent yellow sand, forming a tornado of yellow sand that surged up into the giant's grasp, then formed a giant staff that was close to 1,000 feet in length.

The giant grabbed onto the staff with both hands, and the staff immediately began to radiate bright yellow light before being swept directly toward the oncoming lightning halberd projections.

A mountainous expanse of staff projections was instantly unleashed, obscuring a large section of the sky as they sped toward the lightning halberd projections.

A string of loud explosions rang out as the lightning halberd projections were destroyed by the staff projections, exploding into bursts of dazzling blue lightning that gradually faded into nothingness.

Right at this moment, an opening suddenly appeared amid the dense mass of staff projections, and a blue lightning halberd flew through the opening, aimed directly at the giant's throat.

The one-eyed giant seemed to have already anticipated this, and it withdrew its staff, upon which all of the staff projections in the air also returned to the staff. It then swept its staff through the air to knock the lightning halberd away, but the halberd merely circled around in the air before flying toward the one-eyed giant again.

The centaur-like creature was constantly making circular motions with its arms, and the lightning halberd danced in front of it like a roaming dragon at its behest, releasing countless blue halberd projections that swept toward the one-eyed giant.

Countless tiny arcs of lightning were flashing incessantly amid the vast expanse of halberd projections, and even the air seemed to have been set alight as the acrid scent of something burning wafted through the area.

As for the one-eyed giant, it was wielding the staff as if it were an extension of its own body, unleashing a series of staff projections that resembled a massive yellow bird that was spreading its wings and taking flight, soaring directly toward the blue halberd projections.

A string of loud cracks and pops rang out incessantly as the yellow light and blue lightning intertwined, and neither side was able to overcome the other.

Resounding booms rang out occasionally, and each one was accompanied by the crumbling of a burst of yellow light or the explosion of a burst of blue lightning. Powerful shockwaves spread through the air in all directions, causing the surrounding space to warp and quiver violently.

As the battle raged on, the surface of the massive bubble that encompassed this entire area was also rippling violently like the surface of a disturbed lake, looking as if it could be destroyed at any moment.

Under the concealment of the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman, Han Li had already backed away to around 4,000 to 5,000 feet away from the pair of titanic creatures, and he was watching the ongoing battle intently from afar.

He had originally planned to sneak away while the two creatures were locked in battle so that he could leave this mysterious bubble and resume his journey to the Immortal Realm, but the scene unfolding before his eyes was making him rather hesitant.

After a moment of contemplation, he decided to stay and watch the battle for now.

After an indeterminate period of time, the battle finally began to take a slight turn.

It seemed that the one-eyed giant was gradually running out of stamina due to the injury that it had previously sustained, and it was beginning to struggle to keep up with its assailant.

In contrast, the centaur-like creature's attacks were only becoming more and more ferocious as the battle wore on, and the blue halberd projections began to dominate the yellow staff projections.

Amid the chaos, a burst of yellow light suddenly appeared on the one-eyed giant's feet.

At the same time, it let loose an explosive roar, and the ground beneath its feet instantly began to quake violently. An enormous mass of translucent yellow sand swept up from the ground in a frenzy, forming a massive screen of sand that rose up several thousand feet into the air.

In the face of the screen of sand, all of the halberd projections instantly crumbled away, and the halberd-wielding centaur-like creature was also caught off guard, finding itself separated from its opponent by the screen of sand.

The one-eyed giant immediately turned and fled in the other direction upon seeing this.

Immediately thereafter, dazzling yellow light erupted from the screen of sand, which took on an extremely substantial form.

A hint of derision appeared on the centaur-like creature's three faces, and it turned its left-sided head slightly so that its gaze was turned in the same direction that was directly forward of its central head.

Azure and blue light then appeared in the two pairs of eyes on its left and central heads, and a burst of powerful fluctuations emerged from the spot where the lines of sight of the two pairs of eyes met.

Arcs of blue lightning emerged out of thin air alongside countless azure blades of wind, and they quickly converged to form an azure and blue ball of lightning that was 70 to 80 feet in size.

The two-colored ball of lightning flashed through the air before crashing into the yellow screen of sand.

A massive bulge instantly appeared on the screen of sand where it was struck by the ball of lightning, but it managed to keep the ball of lightning at bay.

However, right at this moment, the ball of lightning began to glow with dazzling radiance before exploding violently.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as countless arcs of blue lightning sprang through the air like a series of tiny lightning wyrms. Each arc of lightning was also accompanied by peerlessly sharp azure blades of wind that swept forth in all directions, instantly tearing a hole that was several hundred feet in size into the center of the screen of yellow sand.

The centaur-like creature immediately passed through the hole in the screen of sand, then raced after the one-eyed giant in hot pursuit, traveling at such an incredible speed that it was able to cover a distance of several thousand feet in the blink of an eye.

However, in the next instant, it abruptly stopped cold in its tracks. As it turned out, the one-eyed giant was nowhere to be seen.

Right at this moment, a burst of radiant light suddenly erupted from a certain point behind the screen of sand, and the one-eyed giant re-emerged. Its aura had waned significantly, but there was a fierce look on its face.

Instead of fleeing from the battle, it had concealed its aura and hidden itself within the screen of sand, waiting for the centaur-like beast to come after it.

At this moment, the thing that was radiating the dazzling light was none other than the previously murky and gray eye on the giant's head.

The centaur-like creature was immediately struck by a sense of foreboding, and it swiveled around before hurling the blue lightning halberd in its grasp directly toward the one-eyed giant.

Almost at the exact same moment, the giant's eye flashed before releasing a thick beam of white light.

In the instant that the lightning halberd came into contact with the beam of white light, it instantly vanished into thin air, then abruptly reappeared in front of the one-eyed giant before piercing into its chest right where its heart was situated. The halberd then exploded amid an eruption of countless arcs of lightning, blasting a massive hole into the giant's chest and causing it to topple backward like a crumbling mountain.

The beam of white light struck the centaur-like creature almost at the exact same moment, and its body was instantly enveloped by a burst of peculiar fluctuations, which made its movements and its magic power circulation hundreds of times slower and more sluggish than normal.

The centaur-like creature was greatly alarmed by this, and it desperately attempted to draw upon its magic power to dispel these strange fluctuations, but despite how feeble they appeared, these fluctuations proved to be extremely tenacious and refused to be dispelled, despite the centaur-like creature's vast reserves of magic power.

Right at this moment, spatial fluctuations erupted behind it, and a giant golden ape leaped out of thin air with bright golden light radiating from its fists, which were hurtling directly toward two of the centaur-like creature's three heads.

The centaur-like creature was greatly startled by this unexpected turn of events, and it reflexively recoiled to try and evade the attacks.

At the same time, the gust of azure wind revolving around it suddenly departed from its body, then transformed into an extremely life-like azure wind dragon, and the wind dragon sped directly toward the giant golden ape as it manifested a single horn on its head.

However, the giant golden ape made no effort to take evasive measures as the semi-transparent True Extreme Membrane appeared over its body, and its fists continued to hurtle through the air.

Due to the debilitating effects of the beam of white light, the centaur-like creature was far too slow to evade the attacks, and two loud, gruesome crunches rang out as its left and central heads were struck before instantly exploding, sending blood and intracranial fluids splattering in all directions.

At this point, the azure wind dragon had also reached the giant golden ape, and the horn on its head began to glow with scintillating light while releasing countless azure runes.

The semi-transparent film was torn apart by the sharp horn, and a long gash was instantly sliced into the giant golden ape's chest.

The giant ape let loose a painful roar as it clasped one hand over the gash on its chest, while swatting its other palm toward the centaur-like creature's third head like lightning.

A look of alarm and horror appeared in the eyes of the centaur-like creature's remaining head, and black light flashed in its eyes as countless black runes emerged before revolving around its body.

In the next instant, the centaur-like creature abruptly vanished into thin air.

As a result, the giant golden ape's attack fell upon nothing but empty air. However, it didn't falter in the slightest as it released its enormous spiritual sense, and at the same time, a layer of blue light appeared within its eyes as it quickly swept its gaze over the surrounding area.

However, even with both his spiritual sense and his Brightsight Spirit Eyes scouring the area at the same time, he was still unable to find any trace of the centaur-like creature, and it was as if it had truly vanished.

Meanwhile, the azure wind dragon was still attacking the giant golden ape relentlessly, quickly inflicting many more gashes onto the giant ape's body with its peerlessly sharp horn.

The giant golden ape flailed its arms wildly through the air to protect its vital regions, and blue light flashed within its eyes, while its glabella split open to reveal an inky-black demonic eye amid a cloud of black qi.

His Brightsight Spirit Eyes and Law Destruction Eye lit up in unison before releasing three beams of spiritual light, two blue and one black.

The three beams of spiritual light fused as one in mid-air in a flash, forming a black and blue ball of light.

The ball of light was around the size of a human fist, and it was glittering and translucent, presenting an intriguing sight to behold.

Chapter 83: Flash of Inspiration

Immediately thereafter, the giant golden ape opened its mouth to release a burst of azure light, which vanished into the ball of black and blue light in a flash. A burst of spiritual light appeared on the surface of the ball of light, and countless black and blue runes of different sizes emerged before rapidly revolving around it.

All of a sudden, countless threads of black and blue light erupted out of the ball of light before flying through the air in all directions, instantly intertwining to form a black and blue net that encompassed an area with a radius of several kilometers.

This was an ability that Han Li had developed by chance by combining his Brightsight Spirit Eyes and Law Destruction Eye. However, using the ability would instantly exhaust the entirety of his current supply of magic power.

As soon as the giant black and blue net took shape, a certain section of it instantly shuddered before warping slightly as if it had come into contact with something.

The giant golden ape instantly sped toward that spot on the net like lightning, leaving the azure wind dragon behind.

The azure wind dragon let loose an enraged roar before immediately setting off in hot pursuit.

The golden ape sped through the air like a gust of wind, appearing at the irregular spot on the giant net in the blink of an eye. Before the azure wind dragon had a chance to catch up to it, it reached out with a dazzling golden hand before slamming it viciously through the air.

A resounding boom rang out alongside violent fluctuations, and a vast expanse of black runes emerged before crumbling away in unison.

Immediately thereafter, the centaur-like creature stumbled out of thin air with a horrified look on its remaining head.

Before it had a chance to react, the giant golden ape's other fist was already crashing down with devastating force.

The centaur-like creature's movements were still extremely sluggish, and it hurriedly crossed its arms in an attempt to protect its own head.

Right at this moment, the giant ape let loose a cold harrumph, and the centaur-like creature instantly felt as if a sharp spike had been driven straight into its brain, causing it to let loose an agonized howl while its entire body completely stiffened.

The golden fist instantly passed through the gap between the centaur-like creature's arms before striking its only remaining head.

The creature's final head instantly exploded like a watermelon, and its enormous body spasmed for a moment before plummeting toward the ground. At this point, the azure wind dragon had caught up to the giant golden ape, and it was just about to drive its horn into the ape's heart from behind, but its body suddenly crumbled away as it let loose an anguished howl.

Immediately thereafter, an azure shadow shot out of the centaur-like creature's headless body.

An intrigued look appeared in the giant golden ape's eyes upon seeing this.

The azure shadow was none other than a miniature three-headed centaur-like creature that was enveloped within a gust of azure whirlwind. It appeared to have already attained a substantial form, much like a cultivator's nascent soul.

Black light flashed from one of the miniature centaur-like creature's heads, and the same black light appeared all over its body as it quickly vanished into thin air, leaving only a trail of afterimages in its wake.

The giant golden ape let loose a low roar, and black light flashed from its glabella as its Law Destruction Eye emerged, then released a thin thread of black light that disappeared in a flash.

The space over 1,000 feet away then shuddered as the miniature centaur-like creature stumbled out into the open with an alarmed expression on all three of its faces.

All of a sudden, silver light flashed around it, and a series of crisscrossing silver chains of fire appeared, instantly forming a massive net of silver flames that converged toward the center.

Azure light flashed from the miniature centaur-like creature's left-sided head, the azure whirlwind revolving around its body transformed into an azure pillar of wind that enveloped its body from all sides, preventing the silver net of fire from closing around it.

However, during this brief moment, the giant golden ape had already arrived on the scene, and a string of cracks and pops rang out as the muscles on its arms bulged before it threw a ferocious punch at the pillar of azure wind.

In the face of the almighty punch, the azure pillar of wind was instantly destroyed, and the miniature centaur-like creature inside let loose a blood-curdling howl before exploding like a shattered egg.

At this moment, most of the giant golden ape's body had already been stained red by its own blood, but it paid no heed to its own injuries as it turned around without pause to charge toward the one-eyed giant that had fallen onto the ground not far away.

The one-eyed giant had sustained extremely severe injuries, having had its heart pierced through by the centaur-like creature's lightning halberd, but it possessed extremely impressive life force and was still able to ward off the cold embrace of death.

At this moment, the hole on its chest had been filled by a layer of fine yellow sand once again, but its aura was still extremely feeble, and it seemed to be barely capable of any movement.

An alarmed and horrified look appeared on its face at the sight of the approaching golden ape, and it let loose a loud roar, upon which the yellow sand around it quickly took on the shape of a massive boat, which began to carry its body away into the distance. At the same time, its eye began to glow with white light again.

A beam of white light shot out of the eye before hurtling directly toward the giant golden ape, and a grim look appeared in the golden ape's eyes upon seeing this.

It didn't know what type of attack this white light was, but thinking back to what had happened to the centaur-like creature after it had been struck by the same attack, it knew that this was definitely not something to be treated lightly.

With that in mind, golden light flashed from its body, and it quickly shrank back down into its human form.

Right at this moment, white light flashed within the giant's eye, and the beam of white light changed directions as if it were a living creature, aiming itself downward and continuing to hurtle toward Han Li at an incredible speed.

Han Li was greatly alarmed to see this, and he wanted to take evasive measures, but it was already too late.

In the instant before the beam of light was about to reach him, he was struck by a flash of inspiration, and he pulled off the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck before tossing it toward the oncoming beam of white light.

In the instant that the beam of white light came into contact with the Heaven Controlling Vial, it instantly vanished into the vial, while the vial itself displayed no reaction whatsoever.

Han Li's mouth gaped open slightly in surprise upon seeing this, following which an elated look appeared on his face, and he withdrew the vial with a wave of his hand, then immediately continued in his pursuit of the one-eyed giant.

The giant's eye had sprung wide open upon seeing this, and it was completely unable to believe what it had just witnessed. However, it then immediately returned to its senses and drew upon all of its remaining magic power before injecting it into the boat beneath it, causing it to glow brightly with yellow light while also accelerating drastically.

Meanwhile, Han Li adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form once again before opening his mouth and letting loose a resounding roar.

A burst of white shockwaves instantly surged forth in a frenzy, quickly encompassing an area in a radius of several thousand feet, causing the space in its wake to warp and twist appreciably.

Given the one-eyed giant's remarkable physical resistance, the soundwaves were naturally unable to inflict much damage onto it from so far away, but the sand boat beneath it wasn't all that resolute to begin with, and it was instantly shattered.

As a result, the one-eyed giant was immediately sent tumbling out of the sky.

Right at this moment, golden light flashed beneath it as the giant golden ape instantly arrived on the scene, then slammed its fist viciously into the giant's head.

The giant's head instantly exploded, sending a vast expanse of red and white liquid splattering through the air.

A ball of dim yellow light flew out of its body, and it was none other than the one-eyed giant's nascent soul.

However, as soon as it emerged, it was instantly caught within a silver net of fire that converged from all directions to trap it within.

Countless silver runes then flew out of the fiery net before adhering themselves tightly to the nascent soul's body, instantly forming a silver seal that completely immobilized it in mid-air.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the one-eyed giant's nascent soul didn't get a chance to do anything before it was captured.

It had failed to anticipate that Han Li had learned from his previous experience with the centaur-like creature's nascent soul, leading him to release the Essence Fire Raven in advance for an instant capture.

The giant's body crashed heavily down onto the ground, and all of the spirit patterns all over the body dimmed, following which it began to crumble away, quickly disintegrating into countless grains of translucent yellow sand.

However, its murky gray eye remained, and it rolled down onto the ground.

Not far away, Han Li reverted back to his human form before drifting down onto the ground.

At this moment, he was inspecting the small green vial in his hand, seemingly contemplating something.

He then raised his head before making a beckoning motion with his hand, releasing a burst of suction force that drew the giant's gray eye into his grasp.

At the moment, the eyeball appeared to be no different from an ordinary stone bead that was completely devoid of any aura. However, the fact that it was able to release beams of light that were imbued with the power of the law of time clearly indicated that it was no ordinary object.

For some reason, Han Li was struck by the urge to touch the Heaven Controlling Vial to the eye, but doing so resulted in no change at all to either the eye or the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Han Li wasn't overly disappointed by this, and he didn't think much of it as he placed the small green vial around his neck again. He then summoned a green jade box before carefully storing the eye into it.

At this point, the silver flame that had trapped the giant's nascent soul had already reverted back into its fire raven form, and it flew back to Han Li's side.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the one-eyed giant's nascent soul, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

He didn't know exactly what uses there were for nascent souls of creatures comparable to to True Immortals, but he was certain that even in the Immortal Realm, these things had to be extremely precious.

However, he had no time to ponder this matter at the moment. With a sweep of his sleeve, he adhered several talismans to the giant's nascent soul, then withdrew his Essence Fire Raven and stored the nascent soul into a wooden box before stowing it away.

He then made his way over to the body of the centaur-like creature several thousand feet away, then also tossed it into a storage bracelet.

Only after doing all of that did he allow himself a moment to catch his breath.

That battle had truly been an exhausting one, but thankfully, he had sustained only minor external injuries.

He looked around to find that the small island had already been severely damaged during the course of the battle, with countless ancient trees felled and a vast volume of debris littering the ravaged ground.

Only some places that were further away and weren't affected by the battle were able to maintain their original state.

Han Li closed his eyes and released his spiritual sense, which instantly encompassed the entirety of this landmass.

Moments later, he raised an eyebrow as a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flew toward a certain direction deep into the dense forest.

Chapter 84: Statue

The forest was filled with all types of different flora, and even with Han Li's vast wealth of experience, he felt like an overawed child in a candy shop.

There were all types of strange and exotic plants stretching as far as the eyes could see, some of which were considered to be exceedingly rare in the Spirit Realm, but were as commonplace as average weed here. Furthermore, all of them were quite advanced in age, and the majority of them were over 1,000 years old, with some specimens even in the tens of thousands of years.

There were also some spirit plants that Han Li didn't recognize, but most of them contained astonishing spiritual power or possessed peculiar appearances or fragrances, and he naturally didn't shy away from adding them all to his collection.

Even though he had already briefly inspected the space within the mysterious bubble with his spiritual sense earlier, he still couldn't help but be stunned by the sights that he was being greeted by, and he was very pleased with his decision not to leave prematurely.

Close to two hours later, Han Li drew to a halt in a rather spacious area in the forest. The trees here were very sparse, and there weren't any spirit medicines growing here either, so it was rather barren in appearance.

Over 1,000 feet in front of him was a giant cave that resembled an enormous rucksack, with its dark and shadowy opening directly facing him.

Han Li stood on the spot and briefly inspected his surroundings, and only after ascertaining that there was nothing amiss did he make his way over to the cave before peering inside.

The cave led diagonally downward, and the sound of howling wind was ringing out incessantly from within.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes as he made his way into the cave.

The inside of the cave was quite dim and a little damp. Water droplets were constantly dripping down from the ceiling and walls of the cave, and the floor was also very soft and loamy.

Han Li followed the natural slope of the cave as he made his way downward, and after walking for around 15 minutes, the direction of the cave's curvature suddenly changed. Furthermore, a series of white crystals that were giving off a cold light began to appear on the rock faces of the cave.

Initially, the crystals were rather sparse, but the further Han Li advanced, the more concentrated the crystals became, and they gradually illuminated the entire path.

After walking for another 15 minutes, he finally reached the end of the cave, where he arrived in a massive underground cavern that was several thousand feet in size.

There were countless white crystals embedded onto the ceiling of the cavern, and they were giving off a cold light that filled the entire space.

Furthermore, the sound of flowing water could be clearly heard down below. As it turned out, there was an underground river passing through here, forming a small lake in the cavern, and the lake was surrounded by translucent yellow sand.

The white light radiating from the crystals was reflected by the rippling water, casting ripples of light onto the surrounding rock faces, presenting a beautiful sight to behold.

However, Han Li was in no mood to be appreciating the scenery here. Instead, his gaze was firmly fixed on a giant rock that was protruding out of the water directly at the center of the cavern.

The rock resembled a miniature landmass that was over 300 feet in size, and there was a strange tree that was roughly 100 feet tall growing on it.

The tree was rather similar to a walnut tree, but it was completely bare and devoid of any leaves. However, there were a series of walnut-like fruits hanging from its branches.

Han Li leaped up into the air before landing at the foot of the tree to inspect it at close quarters.

As a result, he discovered that the tree was riddled with a type of profound pattern that he had never seen before. These patterns didn't appear to have been engraved onto the tree by anyone. Instead, they seemed to be naturally occurring patterns.

The walnut-like fruits hanging from the trees were even more peculiar. Their surfaces were riddled with extremely twisted patterns that resembled strange human faces, some of which resembled wizened elderly men, while others resembled newborn infants.

However, regardless of what the patterns on the fruits were like, every single one of the fruits was giving off astonishing earth-attribute spiritual energy.

It was exactly because he had noticed this spiritual energy that he had been drawn to this place.

Han Li stroked his chin as a contemplative look appeared on his face, and a theory began to emerge in his mind.

This space within the mysterious bubble most likely belonged to the one-eyed giant, and the centaur-like creature had taken such a massive risk to engage the one-eyed giant in battle precisely for this strange walnut tree.

Han Li couldn't identify this tree, nor the fruits that it bore, but one thing was for certain: the fact that a pair of monstrous creatures that were comparable to True Immortals in power were willing to fight over this tree meant that it was definitely no ordinary entity.

However, none of that was important anymore. Right now, this place belonged solely to him.

……

In the Immortal Realm.

In the sky above a nameless mountain range, gusts of fierce wind were howling incessantly amid a dense layer of dark clouds, while snow fell persistently from the heavens.

Some trees that had folded over under the weight of the thick blankets of accumulated snow could still be seen near the foot of the dozens of mountains in the mountain range, but above that, all of the mountains were covered entirely in snow and ice.

The only sounds that could be heard were the howling of the wind and the rustling of the snow, and there weren't any signs of living creatures in the area, either.

However, right at this moment, a sharp female voice suddenly rang out from deep within the tallest mountain in the mountain range, and the voice passed through the snow and wind without being muffled or drowned out in the slightest.

"Who dared to kill my spirit pet? I don't care who you are, I'm going to find you and tear you to shreds, then seal your soul away beneath this mountain for the rest of eternity!"

The voice was filled with rage, and the entire snowy mountain trembled under the weight of its fury.

Countless massive slabs of snow that had accumulated over the course of countless years slid off from the mountain, then came crashing down to send even more snow tumbling down from the mountain, causing a chain reaction that quickly resulted in a full-blown avalanche.

……

In a certain region of the sea in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

The bright sun was hanging directly in the center of the bright and clear sky, and there were only faint traces of clouds drifting through the air. A faint breeze was blowing over the surface of the sea, stirring up a series of small waves.

On the rippling surface of the sea was a black island that was several thousand kilometers in size, and the island was bordered by an extremely irregular circle of countless black rocks. Looking down at the island from above, it resembled an enormous leaf.

There were many boats moored at a dock situated to the north of the island, but the dock itself was completely empty and devoid of people.

There was a wide bluestone path leading into the island from the dock, and it extended all the way into the dense forest on the island.

At the end of the path was a primitive village with densely packed buildings, concealed amid the dense forestry.

At this moment, many parts of the village had been set alight, and thick smoke was rising up into the air, while thunderous war cries were ringing out incessantly. The radiance of countless treasures could be seen, and a nauseating gorey smell was wafting through the air.

Amid a set of ruins, close to 1,000 cultivators were locked in a chaotic battle. The cultivators were split up into two sides, and their numbers seemed to be roughly evenly matched.

The cultivators on one of the two sides weren't human. All of them were extremely physically imposing with green skin and tusks protruding out of their mouths, and most of them were wielding weapons that fell under the categories of maces and hammers. Furthermore, each of them had a layer of faint white light over their skin.

There were also some yellow-armored mace-wielding warriors interspersed among these foreign cultivators, but all of them had sickly yellow skin and didn't appear to be living beings. Instead, they resembled moving wax statues.

In the opposing faction, most of the cultivators were humans, but there were also some strange crimson-armored warriors among them.

The skin of these warriors bore the same hue as their armor, and even in the heat of battle, they were completely expressionless, giving them the appearance of emotionless puppets.

On a section of elevated terrain, a crimson-armored warrior that was wielding a crimson spear leaped down before plunging its spear viciously down toward one of the oncoming yellow-skinned warriors.

Before the crimson spear had even struck its target, a crimson vortex erupted from the tip of the spear, sending countless bursts of crimson light raining down from above.

A resounding boom rang out as a huge hole was blasted into the yellow-skinned warrior's chest, and some type of yellow fluid came pouring out incessantly from the wound as it stumbled back a few steps involuntarily.

However, in the next instant, it bent its knees slightly before springing up like lightning while swinging its mace through the air, releasing countless mace projections to form a ferocious yellow hurricane that swept viciously toward the crimson-armored warrior.

The crimson-armored warrior was caught off guard by the attack, and its head instantly exploded, but at the last second, it hurled its spear through the air, sending it piercing directly through the yellow-skinned warrior's head.

The two fell to the ground almost at the exact same moment, and one of them disintegrated into a puddle of crimson liquid, while the other dissolved into a pool of yellow fluid.

Elsewhere, a short and stubby elderly man suddenly emerged from behind a semi-collapsed wall with a crimson jade vial in his grasp, and the opening of the vial was facing a foreign cultivator that was chasing after him in hot pursuit several hundred feet away.

The elderly man gently patted the bottom of the vial, and countless crimson threads shot out of the vial amid a flash of crimson light, then intertwined to form a pillar of crimson light that shot directly toward the foreign cultivator.

As soon as the crimson pillar of light came into contact with the layer of white light over the foreign cultivator's body, it was instantly slowed down. Even though it wasn't completely dispelled, its power had been instantly reduced by close to a third.

The foreign cultivator stumbled unsteadily from the attack, and blood gushed out of its mouth, but it didn't sustain any substantial injuries and continued to charge toward the elderly man as it let loose a furious roar.

Similar scenes were taking place all over the entire village.

The yellow-skinned warriors and the crimson-armored warriors were all extremely fierce and courageous in battle, displaying no regard for their own safety. However, they were roughly evenly matched both in terms of power and numbers, so they were unable to sway the state of the battle.

However, all of the foreign cultivators were protected by those strange layers of white light, which buffered the power of all of the attacks that were directed at them. As a result, they were able to quickly gain the upper hand in the battle, and the human cultivators were soon forced back into retreat, converging toward the center of the village.

Meanwhile, on a white stone plaza at the center of the village, several dozen black-robed figures were seated around a massive statue with their legs crossed, chanting a complex incantation.

There were people from all demographics among the black-robed figures, and all of them had rather pale complexions as they held their left arms in front of them with their left sleeves rolled back.

There was a thin gash on all of their left wrists, and blood was flowing out of those gashes before trickling down onto the ground in front of them.

A series of channels had been carved onto the ground to form a complex array, which was directly connected to the statue at the very center of the plaza.

The statue was roughly 100 feet tall, and it depicted a young scholarly man holding a book in his hand while casting his gaze into the distance.

If Han Li were present, he would be surprised to find that the young scholarly man bore some resemblance to him. However, when looking at the bodily proportions, it was clear that Han Li was taller than the man that was the subject of the statue.

In front of the statue was a gray-robed elderly with his arm crossed in front of him and his hands gripping onto his opposite shoulders as he prayed to the statue with a reverent expression, "Almighty Ancestral God, please heed the call of your devoted bloodline and descend!"

Chapter 85: Ancestral God

The channels on the ground around the statue of the young scholar had already been filled with blood, and all of the blood was converging toward the foot of the statue.

As the white-haired elderly man uttered his prayers in a trembling voice, a layer of crimson light on the surface of the statues began to pulse erratically, while a crimson vortex was revolving incessantly in front of the elderly man, releasing bursts of peculiar fluctuations.

All of a sudden, a faint buzzing sound rang out, and light flashed from the crimson vortex as a crimson-armored warrior emerged from within. It insepcted its surroundings momentarily with a wooden expression, then sprang up into the sky and rushed directly toward the battlefield outside the plaza.

Moments later, the crimson vortex flashed again, and another crimson-armored warrior emerged before joining the battle outside.

Right at this moment, a little black-robed girl who was seated on the plaza suddenly collapsed and fell to the side.

Her face was deathly pale, and even her lips were completely devoid of color. The gash on her wrist was still open, but she no longer had any more blood to give.

A sympathetic look appeared on the white-haired elderly man's face upon seeing this, but all he could do was wave a dismissive hand.

Among the dozen or so people waiting off to the side, a burly man immediately strode forward and carried the little girl away, then fed her a red pill.

The spot that was vacated by the little girl was quickly taken by a girl who was roughly the same age as her.

The little girl had a rather fearful look on her face, but she immediately sat down ith her legs crossed without any delay, then replicated what everyone else was doing, rolling up her left sleeve before pulling out a small knife that she held against her wrist.

She then closed her eyes in a fearful manner and bit down onto her own lower lip before slashing the knife across her wrist.

A bright red gash instantly appeared, and a stream of blood began to trick down onto the channel in front of her.

……

The altar was operating at full capacity, periodically producing a crimson-armored warrior to join the battle, but that was only delaying the inevitable defeat of the human camp.

As time slowly passed by, the sounds of the battle taking place outside drew closer and closer, and the people on the plaza began to fall deeper and deeper into despair.

The altar array around the statue of the scholarly young man was the basis of their tribe's heritage. If it were to be conquered by their foreign enemies and the statue were destroyed, then their tribe would've well and truly fallen.

At this point, all of the human cultivators outside had already been forced back into a protective circle around the array, making one final desperate effort to keep their enemies at bay.

High up in the sky, bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly as several balls of dazzling light clashed violently, following which around a dozen figures emerged from within.

Six of those figures were green-skinned foreign beings with scorching bloodlust and battle intent in their eyes, and the tusks that were prturding out of hteir mouths were gleaming with a cold light.

The green-skinned foreign beings were very physically imposing to begin with, and they were led by a purple-robed man who was signficantly taller than even his brethren, standing in mid-air like an impregnable tower.

His aura was extremely vast, belonging to a Grand Ascension cultivator, and the five green-skinned foreign beings accomanying him were all at the mid-Body Integration Stage or the late-Body Integration Stage.

These foreign beings also had the same layer of white light over their bodies, but theirs were far more substantial than the layers of white light enveloping the bodies of their brethren.

The six green-skinned foreign beings were opposed by five human cultivators who were led by a slightly portly scholarly young man who was at the late-Body Integration Stage, but the rest of the group were all only at the early-Body Integration Stage, so it was clear that they were going to no match for their opponents.

In this dire situation, the scholarly man's heart was filled with despair, but after taking a glance at the giant statue on the plaza, he gritted his teeth as a determined look appeared in his eyes.

Right at this moment, ball of dazzling white light suddenly appeared in front of the group of human cultivators, then exploded violently to release countless rays of light that instantly engulfed the entire group.

A burst of incredibly powerful shockwaves erupted from the epicenter of the explosion, forming several ferocious tornadoes that swept through the air in all directions.

Several figures rapidly shot out of the white light before plummeting toward the plaza.

The edge of the plaza collapsed with a resounding boom, and a crater that was over 100 feet deep apepared on its surface.

However, several streaks of light quickly flew out of the plaza, revealing themselves to be the group of human Body Integration cultivators, but at this point, their auras were in complete disarray, and their clothes had been torn to shreds.

The scholarly man's face was as pale as a sheet, and he was holding a broken shield, while blood was trickling incessantly down from the corners of his lips.

It had taken everything he had to ensure that the entire group survived, but in doing so, he had to pay a heavy price.

"Chief!"

All of the humans on the scene were struck by a sense of panic upon seeing this.

The scholarly man wiped the blood from his lips with his sleeve, then waved a hand at everyone as a gesture of reassurance.

He then raised his head to look up at the sky, and discovering that the foreign beings hadn't immediately descended after them in pursuit, he made his way over to the foot of the statue before casting an inquisitive gaze toward the white-haired elderly man.

The elderly man shook his head as he replied with an anguished expression, "There's been no response from our Ancestral God."

A wry smile appeared on the scholarly man's face as he murmured to himself, "Esteemed Ancestral God, are you really going to abandon your people? Your loyal servants?"

Meanwhile, the purple-robed foreign being and the elders from the same race had already flown into the air above the plaza, and the purple-robed man chortled, "Are you still pleading to that useless Ancestral God of yours even now, Luo Feng? How about you be smart for once and follow the Ancestral God of our Cold Crystal Race?"

"In your dreams, Tuhar! Don't forget that your Ancestral God was once defeated by the Ancestral God of our Dark Veil Island!" the scholarly man countered in an enraged voice.

"So what? Stop living in the past, what matters is the present! Nowadays, our Ancestral God is still protecting our tribe, while your Ancestral God has already been in slumber for the past 10,000 ever since he sustained those injuries. Has he woken up yet? Are you sure he's not dead already?" Tuhar scoffed with a derisive sneer.

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he wanted to issue a retort, but he had nothing to say as everything that Tuhar had said was correct.

Their Ancestral God had indeed been in a state of slumber for the past 10,000 years, and he had virtually no connection at all with the tribe. In particular, he hadn't answered any of the calls made by the tribe in the past 1,000 years.

Now that they were being invaded by foreign enemies, all they could do was try and use the blood of their people to awaken their Ancestral God, but thus far, it had all been to no avail.

Through this statue left behind by their Ancestral God, they were able to summon some ancestral warriors, but that was only delaying their inevitable downfall.

"You're dreaming if you think you can stop us with these ancestral warriors of yours, Luo Feng. I suggest you surrender right now. Otherwise, I'm going to slaughter your entire tribe!" Tuhar yelled in a menacing voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a hand through the air, and the surrounding Cold Crystal beings instantly converged as they attacked with renewed ferocity.

The cultivators of Dark Veil Island were already just barely clinging on for dear life, and in the face of this aggressive assault, several parts of their defensive line were instantly torn apart.

Their enemies were about to reach the plaza, and even Luo Feng was in a state of despair.

Right at this moment, a burst of faint buzzing rang out, and the azure statue suddenly began to tremble as a burst of rumbling sounded.

Immediately thereafter, the statue began to radiate dazzling black light that was becoming brighter by the second.

The white-haired elderly man who was closest to the statue was the first one who noticed this change, and he immediatley yelled with elation, "It's our Ancestral God! Our Ancestral God has answered our call!"

All of the humans on the island faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which ecstatic looks on their faces, and morale was instantly elevated to an unprecedented high, so much so that the crumbling defensive line was beginning to stabilize itself again.

In contrast, the Cold Crystal beings had become extremely uneasy and tentative.

If the Ancestral God of the human race really could descend, then even their Grand Ascension Stage chief would be no match.

"That's impossible!" Tuhar exclaimed in an incredulous voice as he stared intently at the statue down below.

The light emanating from the statue grew brighter and brighter before all of a sudden, it exploded violently into a vast expanse of inky-black light.

The black light flashed a few times before transforming into a black vortex that was several hundred feet in size.

Bolts of black lightning were flashing within the vortex, threatening to tear the surrounding space apart amid deafening thunderclaps.

With the emergence of the black vortex, a layer of dark clouds also appeared in the previously clear sky, and bolts of lightning were also flashing within the clouds.

All of the world's origin qi within a radius of several hundred kilomters suddenly began to tumble and churn violently like boiling water.

Everyone on the battlefield was greatly alarmed by this sudden turn of events, and they all reflexively stopped what they were doing as they observed the unfolding phenomena with awestruck expressions.

The number of arcs of black lightning in the vortex was rapidly increasing, and in the end, all of them converged toward one spot to form a huge ball of black lightning that was crackling loudly.

All of a sudden, the black ball of lightning warped before elongating to form a pitch-black spatial rift that was over 100 feet in length.

A humanoid figure stumbled rather unsteadily out of the rift, but quickly steadied himself, revealing him to be an azure-robed man.

The spatial rift flashed erratically a few times, then slowly sealed over and vanished.

In the next instant, the black vortex in the sky also gradually dissipated, and the churning world's origin qi quickly returned to normal, while the dark clouds up above also disappeard.

The azure-robed man was looking a little disheveled, but there was a hint of elation on his face.

However, as he steadied himself and caught sight of the masses of people around him, his brows immediately furrowed slightly.

The azure-robed man was none othre than Han Li, who had finally successfully traversed through the interrealm gap after a herculean struggle.

However, at this moment, his magic power was completely exhausted, and his physical body was severely taxed.

His Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor had also completely shattered within the spatial storm, but he had no time to think about that as he was busy processing the jarring sight that he was being greeted by.

"Esteemed Ancestral God! You've finally returned!"

An ecstatic look quickly appeared in Luo Feng's eyes at the sight of the azure-robed man, and he immediately fell to his knees before kowtowing in Han Li's direction.

Chapter 86: Forcing Back the Enemy

"Esteemed Ancestral God!"

Everyone on Dark Veil Island, particularly its younger residents, instantly let loose cries of elation upon witnessing Luo Feng's actions, and they all backed away kneeling and kowtowing to Han Li as well.

However, the slightly older residents of the island and the elders seemed to be rather hesitant, as if they had noticed something amiss.

"What are you standing there for? Hurry up and greet our Ancestral God!" Luo Feng yelled as he glared at the elders.

"Ah... We pay our respects to the esteemed Ancestral God!" The elders hurriedly did as they were told, falling to their knees and kowtowing like everyone else.

Ancestral god?

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he was quite perplexed by what he was seeing.

After a brief moment of initial confusion, he was able to quickly make sense of the situation. This human tribe, which was led by the scholarly man, was clearly being attacked by these foreign beings, who were led by the purple-robed man. Furthermore, the human tribe was clearly in a terrible state. In fact, it was no exaggeration to say that they were one step away from defeat.

Never did he think that he would encounter something like this after only just returning to the Immortal Realm. If it weren't for the fact that there was only a single Grand Ascension cultivator present, and no one else was able to pose any threat to him, he would've immediately departed without any hesitation.

After all, no matter what the outcome of this battle was, it had nothing to do with him.

High up in the sky, Tuhar was watching Han Li with a rather hesitant expression.

They were on the verge of wiping out this human settlement on Dark Veil Island, and never did he think that a roadblock would appear in their way now.

A Body Integration Stage Cold Crystal being with a mustache on his face approached Tuhar, then asked via voice transmission, "What do we do, Chief? Should we go back and..."

Tuhar hesitated momentarily, then replied through gritted teeth, "We finally have these accursed humans cornered, we can't afford to retreat now! We battle to the end!"

"But if that man really is the Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island..." the mustached Cold Crystal being was rather hesitant.

"You really think that man is the Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island? Look at how young he looks! And how did he even turn up? Did he suddenly burrow his way out of the ground? On top of that, I can tell that his aura is very feeble, so he must be carrying severe injuries.

“There's no need to fear him in this state, even if he is the Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island. All we need to do is kill him here, and it'll truly be over for Dark Veil Island!" Tuhar said as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately shot forth like lightning, instantly appearing directly above Han Li before looking down at him with a cold expression.

The moustached man and the other three foreign Body Integration Stage beings also immediately followed close behind, forming an encirclement with Tuhar to surround Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li was looking straight into Tuhar's eyes with his hands clasped behind his back, looking completely unfazed.

With Tuhar and the elders leading the charge, the rest of the Cold Crystal beings immediately erupted into thunderous war cries as they resumed their attack on the plaza.

The humans also threw themselves back into the battle, but this time, their morale was significantly boosted by Han Li's arrival.

Luo Feng swept his gaze across the surrounding area, then turned to Han Li, and he wanted to say something, but by then, Tuhar had already attacked.

A vast expanse of blue light suddenly emerged from his body, forming a mountainous blue python head projection behind him.

The python projection had a massive curved horn on its head, and it opened its cavernous mouth to release a wave of countless blue ripples that surged violently toward Han Li.

A burst of glacial power emanated from the blue ripples, and a layer of frost began to spread over the ground, while even the surrounding air seemed to have been frozen solid.

At the same time, Tuhar made a grabbing motion with both hands, and the blue light around him instantly transformed into a pair of short blue spears that fle out of his grasp. A layer of blue glacial flames appeared on the surface of the spears mid-flight, and they transformed into a pair of blue ice dragons that were over 100 feet in length, pouncing toward Han Li from both the left and the right.

Almost at the exact same moment, the other five Body Integration Stage foreign beings also launched a string of attacks at Han Li with their respective treasures.

Han Li calmly raised a hand upon seeing this, extending a palm out of his sleeve toward the oncoming wave of blue ripples.

A burst of tremendous force crashed into the blue waves, and the latter were instantly destroyed amid a burst of loud crackling, vanishing into nothingness in the blink of an eye.

Right at this moment, a bone-chilling sensation surged toward Han Li as the pair of blue ice dragons pounced on him with ferocious might.

Han Li didn't even bat an eyelid as he swept his other hand through the air, and a series of ripples appeared in the space before him as if a giant invisible hand had just swept past.

A pair of dull thumps rang out, and the two ice dragons let loose anguished howls before completely shattering, reverting back into a pair of short blue spears that Han Li grabbed out of mid-air with ease.

Tuhar's face paled slightly upon seeing this, following which an incredulous look appeared in his eyes.

The attacks unleashed by the treasures wielded by the other Body Integration Stage Cold Crystal beings also quickly fell upon Han Li, but they were repelled with ease by the semi-transparent True Extreme Membrane that appeared over his body, and the attacks weren't able to leave even the slightest mark on his body.

"Impossible!" the Body Integration Stage Cold Crystal beings exclaimed in unison, and they immediately realized that they had made a terrible mistake.

Before they had a chance to do anything, Han Li swept a hand through the air, and pair of short blue spears were instantly sent flying, piercing through the chests of the moustached Cold Crystal being and another one of his Body Integration Stage companions.

In the instant that they were struck by the blue spears, dazzling white light instantly emerged on the surface of their skin, but the light barriers were unable to impede the ble spears in the slightest. In the next instant, both of their bodies were completely pulverized by the unfathomable power imbued within the spears, and their nascent souls didn't even have a chance to escape before they were destroyed.

Immediately thereafter, a series of blurry fist projections abruptly appeared in the air in front of the remaining Body Integration Stage Cold Crystal beings before striking them like lightning.

They were completely unable to react to attack, but layers of white light also instantly appeared over their bodies, forming a protective barrier in an attempt to ward off the fist projections.

However, the light barriers were shattered with ease, and the fist projections instantly reduced the Cold Crystal beings to mincemeat amid a string of dull thumps.

It had taken Han Li less than a second to lay waste to the group of Body Integration Stage Cold Crystal beings, but by this point, Tuhar had already recovered from his astonishment.

He immediately turned and sped away as a streak of white light, fleeing into the distance at an incredible speed.

At the same time, a bracelet on his wrist flashed several times in succession, releasing several light barriers of different colors that enveloped his entire body, while a suit of blue crystalline armor also emerged to encase him from head to toe.

Right at this moment, Han Li gave a cold harrumph, and even though Tuhar had already flown to several thousand feet away at this point, he was immediately struck by a burst of sharp pain in his head.

As a result, he was stopped cold in his tracks and plummeted out of the sky.

However, a ordinary-looking jade pendant around his neck suddenly exploded with a dull thump, transforming into a series of translucent azure threads that vanished into his head in a flash, providing a cool and refreshing burst of energy that instantly snapped him back to his senses.

However, Han Li had already taken advantage of this opportunity close the gap between himself and Turan, and seven specks of blue light emerged on his chest and abdomen while the muscles on his arm bulged violently, and he threw a devastating punch at Turan.

Turan was greatly alarmed by this, and he immediately raised the large blue sword in his hands to defend himself.

Turan's towering frame was instantly sent flying back like a ragdoll, and not only was the blue sword in his hands shattered, the light barriers around him were also destroyed, while the suit of crystalline armor that he was wearing became riddled with cracks.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but he then instantly appeared in front of Tuhar in a wraith-like manner before unleashing another devastating blow, releasing a burst of terrifying force that caused the space before him to ripple violently.

The suit of armor and the layer of white light that Tuhar's body was encased in were instantly shattered, and he didn't even get a chance to cry out before his body and his nascent soul were completely pulverized.

A shimmering blue bracelet shot back before landing in Han Li's grasp in a flash.

He released his spiritual sense to briefly inspect the contents of the bracelet, then tossed it into his own storage bracelet before casting his gaze downward, only to find that the entire plaza had fallen completely silent.

Everyone from both sides was rooted to the spot with dumbstruck expressions, and the battle had completely ceased.

Luo Feng was the first one to return to his senses, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he yelled in elation, "Long live our Ancestral God! Kick these pieces of foreign scum off our island!"

"Long live our Ancestral God!"

Everyone else in the human camp also quickly returned to their senses, and their collective joyful voices erupted into the heavens as they charged toward the Cold Crystal beings with unprecedentedly lofty morale.

The Cold Crystal beings still outnumbered the humans on the battlefield, but with the most powerful beings among their ranks slain in the blink of an eye, their morale was completely crushed, and they were quickly overwhelmed by the human army.

Han Li naturally didn't have much interest in pursuing the remaining Cold Crystal beings, and he descended onto the plaza before stowing away the storage bracelets of the four Body Integration Stage Cold Crystal beings.

At this moment, everyone on the plaza was staring at at Han Li with awestruck expressions, and someone suddenly yelled, "We pay our respects to our esteemed Ancestral God!"

Everyone immediately fell to their knees before echoing this reverent cry, and Luo Feng also kowtowed to the ground in an extremely reverent and respectful manner.

All of the humans on Dark Veil Island were ecstatic to have survived what had seemed like a certain demise, and many of them were even sobbing uncontrollably.

However, the elation in their eyes was outweighed by a sense of admiration and veneration, and they were looking at Han Li like mortals seeing a deity in the flesh.

Han Li swept his gaze over everyone's faces with a calm expression.

He didn't immediately declare to everyone that he wasn't the Ancestral God that he spoke of, nor did he falsely accept his title. Instead, he communicated something directly to Luo Feng through voice transmission.

Luo Feng shuddered slightly upon hearing what Han Li had to say, then rose to his feet before issuing a few instructions to those around him with a solemn expression.

"Elder Hu, I'll get you to take care of treating the injured and tallying our losses. Elder Qi, you'll be responsible for setting up alert measures in case those Cold Crystal beings suddenly make a return. I have to accompany our Ancestral God to the Ancestral God Pavilion. No one is allowed to approach the premises without my explicit instructions."

Everyone immediately accepted the orders assigned to them.

Chapter 87: Earthly Immortal

"Please come with me, Esteemed Ancestral God."

Luo Feng hunched over slightly as he made an inviting hand gesture, leading Han Li toward the Ancestral God Pavilion. All of the surrounding humans immediately bowed as they spread out to open up a path for Han Li and Luo Feng.

Not long after the two of them left the plaza, all of the humans on the plaza yelled in unison, "Farewell, Esteemed Ancestral God!"

Their voices were loud and synchronized, and the phrase was repeated several times, only trailing off into silence after Han Li and Luo Feng had vanished into the forest outside of the plaza.

Throughout this entire process, Han Li didn't turn around even once, nor did he slow down in the slightest.

The two made their way along a winding stone path in the forest all the way to a large, antiquated hall.

The hall was only less than 200 feet tall, so it wasn't all that large compared with the average palace, and the walls were pitch-black, seemingly having been constructed from the common rocks on the island. The hall was also riddled with signs of age and wear, but the color of the pillars, doors, and windowframes were still quite vibrant, indicating that they were clearly periodically repainted.

The small plaza in front of the hall and the stone staircase leading up to it had all been swept very cleanly, with barely even a single fallen leaf to be seen.

Han Li looked up to find a black plaque hanging above the entrance of the hall, bearing the words "Ancestral God Pavilion" in large golden characters.

Luo Feng quickly made his way over to the hall, then extended a respectful bow before pushing the doors open and inviting Han Li into the hall.

Upon entering the hall, Han Li was greeted by the sight of a black stone statue that was a 1:1 replica of Dark Veil Island's Ancestral God, and looking at its features, the statue did indeed bear somewhat of a resemblance to him.

Han Li inspected his surroundings briefly before withdrawing his gaze and turning to Luo Feng, then said in a direct and straightforward manner, "Seeing as it's only you and me in here, let me make things clear to you. I'm not the Ancestral God that you speak of, and I only turned up here today purely by chance."

A horrified look immediately appeared on Luo Feng's face upon hearing this, and he hurriedly fell to his knees once again as he implored, "Esteemed Ancestral God, if you hadn't descended today, our Dark Veil Island would've been destroyed for sure! Please don't abandon us! Our entire tribe has been worshipping your reverently for tens of thousands of years, and we're counting on you for our continued protection!"

"If those people hadn't attacked me today, I wouldn't have done anything to them, so there's no need for you to feel any gratitude for what I've done. As the chief of this tribe, I'm sure you know full well whether I'm your Ancestral God or not. If you're hoping that you can swindle me into taking the place of your Ancestral God, then I'm telling you now that it's not going to work," Han Li said in a cold voice.

Luo Feng shuddered upon hearing this, and a fearful look surfaced in his eyes, following which a wry smile appeared on his face.

"To be honest, it doesn't matter to me who you are, Senior. As long as you can agree to stay on our island and pose as our Ancestral God to help us avert this crisis, our entire tribe will dedicate itself fully to serving you and providing you with any cultivation resources that you need."

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but instead of immediately offering a reply, he suddenly asked, "For a start, why don't you tell me about this Ancestral God that you speak of?"

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, then carefully replied, "The Ancestral God that we worship is actually an ancestor of ours who attained immortality through cultivation hundreds of years ago. He has been protecting our tribe for generation after generation, and he is the reason why our tribe has been able to establish a foothold here."

Han Li was silent for a moment before asking, "So those foreign beings that invaded your island today also have an Ancestral God that they worship? Does that layer of white light over their bodies have something to do with the protection provided by that Ancestral God of theirs?"

"That's right. The Ancestral God of their tribe is someone by the name of Patriarch Han Qiu, and he's just a mere Earthly Immortal who only attained immortality less than 200,000 years ago. According to my knowledge, his powers rank near the bottom among all of the Ancestral Gods, and he was even once defeated by the Ancestral God of our Dark Veil Island," Luo Feng replied in a resentful voice.

"What is an Earthly Immortal?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Luo Feng was quite taken aback by this question. "You don't know of Earthly Immortals? Could it be that you only just ascended from a lower realm?"

Han Li offered no response, merely looking at Luo Feng in silence.

Luo Feng knew that he had overstepped his boundaries, and he hurriedly explained, "An Earthly Immortal is an immortal who cultivates through harnessing the power of faith from worshippers in an area that they protect. Generally speaking, the larger the area under their protection, the more worshippers they'll have, and the faster they'll be able to progress in their cultivation."

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, then prompted, "Tell me about the Cold Crystal Race."

He was quite interested in the concepts of Ancestral Gods and Earthly Immortals, but he didn't want to ask any further questions on those subjects for now.

"Just like our tribe, that settlement of Cold Crystal beings is a small tribe situated on the edge of the Black Wind Sea. The island that they reside on is quite close to our Dark Veil Island, so we've always had frequent conflicts with them over things like resources.

“Back when our tribe was the height of its powers, they naturally didn't dare to step out of line, but seeing as our ancestral god has been in a state of slumber for an extended period of time, they've begun to become more and more aggressive," Luo Feng replied in a respectful manner.

Han Li fell into deep thought after hearing what Luo Feng had to say.

Luo Feng naturally didn't dare to interrupt Han Li, and he waited off to the side with his head lowered in reverence.

After a long silence, Han Li suddenly asked, "How far away is this Black Wind Sea from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region?"

"According to my knowledge, the Black Wind Sea is within the scope of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region's jurisdiction, but it's only an insignificant and secluded area. Here is a partial map of the Black Wind Sea," Luo Feng replied as he pulled out a walnut-sized white bead before offering it up to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the bead and closed his eyes as he injected his spiritual sense into it.

Moments later, he reopened his eyes, and a hint of mixed emotions appeared on his face. After another long silence, he said, "I can protect your Dark Veil Island, but there are some things that I must make clear first."

Luo Feng was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly prompted, "Please go ahead, Senior."

"You are correct, I did indeed only arrive in the Immortal Realm today. On top of that, I wasn't received into the Immortal Realm by an Ascension Platform. If you view this to be a problem, then we can pretend as if nothing has happened here, and I can leave right away," Han Li revealed.

"Of course that's not a problem! I'm extremely grateful that you're willing to entrust me with this information, Senior!" Luo Feng hurriedly said.

"In that case, in order to put your people at ease, you can refer to me as your Ancestral God when we're in the presence of others. However, in private, you can refer to me simply as Senior Liu. If the Cold Crystal Race dares to attack again, I'll be sure to step in, but don't forget about your promise of securing the cultivation resources that I need," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

Luo Feng was overjoyed to hear this, and he hurriedly replied, "Rest assured, Senior, we'll do everything in our power to satisfy your needs!"

"Alright, organize a peaceful place for me to stay. I need to rest and recuperate," Han Li said with a nod.

"Please come with me, Senior Liu."

Thus, Luo Feng led Han Li through the Ancestral God Pavilion and into the backyard.

After emerging from the backyard, the two of them passed through a bamboo forest that was filled with purple mist, then arrived at a small, traditional courtyard.

"This courtyard is where I go into seclusion when I'm trying to break through cultivation bottlenecks. No one will disturb you here, so you can rest assured," Luo Feng said.

Han Li briefly inspected the courtyard before giving a nod of approval and leading the way inside.

……

Close to half a day later.

In a dark blue region of the sea tens of thousands of kilometers away from Dark Veil Island was a white island that was sevearl thousand feet tall.

The area of the island was comparable with Dark Veil Island, but it was very long and thin in shape, resembling a willow leaf. Vegetation was quite sparse on the island, and the ground was riddled with gray rocks that reflected the light of the sun.

There were a series of white dome roof buildings that were constructed in accordance with the slope of the mountains on the island, and the closer one drew to the top of the mountain, the fewer and sparser the buildings became.

By the time one reached the highest point on the island, there were virtually no buildings around, only a spindle-shaped plaza that was several thousand feet in length constructed along the ridge of the mountain.

The plaza was riddled with curved or ring-shaped patterns that were connected with one another to form an extremely beautiful and intricate array.

At the center of the array stood a gray statue that was over 100 feet tall, depicting a burly and imposing man in a suit of armor with beautiful patterns engraved onto its surface. The man was also wearing a hollow helmet with a pair of curved tusks protruding out of his mouth and a head of slight curled long hair trailing down his back, giving him a dashing and gallant appearance.

At this moment, there was a circle of Cold Crystal beings kneeling around the statue with their heads lowered and their arms crossed over their chests while chanting something, seemingly performing some type of ritual.

Moments later, two balls of blue light suddenly appeared beneath the visor of the gray statue, and a rumbling voice rang out from within.

"How did it go? Hmm? Why don't I see Tuhar?"

A slightly portly elder of the Cold Crystal Race stepped forward with a grief-stricken expression, then cupped his fist in a respectful salute as he replied, "Esteemed Ancestral God, please allow me to explain..."

A short while later, the Cold Crystal being concluded his recount of events, and he wiped the sweat from his forehead with his sleeve, then continued, "That's roughly what happened. Chief Tuhar and several of our elders have already perished in battle. You have to stand up for us, Esteemed Ancestral God!"

After a brief silence, the same rumbling voice rang out from within the gray statue once again.

"There's no way that it was Luo Meng who descended onto Dark Veil Island. If he's actually recovered from those injuries that he suffered 10,000 years ago, there's no way that he would've allowed all of you to return alive, given his personality."

"In that case, should we raise another army and launch a second attack on Dark Veil Island?" the elder of the Cold Crystal Race asked in a careful voice.

"There's no need for that. That man may not be Luo Meng, but he's certainly no slouch, either, given that he was able to kill Tuhar and the others so easily. If you launch another attack, you'll only be sending more of our people to their deaths. You can go for now, I'll take care of the rest," the statue replied.

"Yes, Esteemed Ancestral God." The elder of the Cold Crystal Race immediately extended a respectful bow before departing with his brethren.

After everyone had departed, the voice from the statue murmured to itself, "Gu Gu, Hu Tu, and Lu Kun are also interested in conquering Dark Veil Island and splitting the spoils, so I'll naturally have to put them to work as well. However, there's one thing that I can't hand over to them. That thing is pivotal for whether I'll be able to successfully advance in my cultivation..."

As the voice trailed off, the two spots of blue light on the statue also gradually vanished.

Chapter 88: Earthly Deity Avatar

Inside the courtyard, Han Li was flicking incessantly through the air to release a series of streaks of azure light, which quickly revealed themselves to be azure array flags. The array flags quickly vanished into the air around the courtyard, following which an azure light barrier appeared to encompass the entire courtyard.

After doing all of that, he sat down with his legs crossed and closed his eyes to meditate.

As time passed, the sky gradually darkened, and day transitioned into night.

Han Li opened his eyes and took a glance up at the starry night sky, then flipped a hand over to produce a pill that he swallowed. After that, he took a deep breath before activating his Big Dipper Origin Arts, and seven blue specks of light immediately appeared on his chest and abdomen.

The starpower in the night sky converged to form seven pillars of starlight that descended from the heavens, and as they starpower entered Han Li's body, his pale complexion slowly began to improve.

The night quickly passed by, and in the morning, Han Li opened his eyes as he exhaled.

Not only had all of his physical fatigue been alleviated, even the damage that he had sustained while passing through the interrealm gap had been completely healed.

He took a moment to stretch, then made his way into a side room in the courtyard.

The room wasn't very large, only around 70 to 80 feet in size, and aside from a bamboo cabinet and several sandalwood tables and chairs, there was only a cushion directly at the center of the room. However, everything was very clean and tidy, indicating that the room was clearly very well looked after.

Han Li sat down onto the cushion with his legs crossed, then flipped a hand over to produce a jade box, which he opened to reveal a yellow walnut.

The patterns on the surface of the walnut formed a human face, and it was giving off astonishing earth-attribute spiritual qi fluctuations. This was one of the fruits from the strange walnut tree that Han Li had obtained from that mysterious space within the bubble.

He had been in quite a hurry earlier, so he didn't get a chance to carefully examine the fruit, but now, he finally had the opportunity to make a closer assessment.

Thus, he immediately released his spiritual sense and injected it into the walnut for a thorough examination.

As a result, he was immediately stunned by what he saw.

The earth-attribute spiritual qi imbued within the walnut was downright astounding, but it had been compressed to the extreme so that it could fit inside the fruit.

Due to the Heaven Controlling Vial, Han Li was quite experienced when it came to identifying all types of spirit medicines and ingredients, particularly when it came to judging their age.

He didn't recognize this walnut, but given the vast volume of the world's origin qi imbued within it, it had to be at least 100,000 years old.

However, just this alone still wasn't enough to warrant having two demon beasts comparable in power to True Immortals fighting over it.

With that in mind, Han Li continued to carefully examine every single inch of the walnut with his spiritual sense.

After examining the walnut for close to 20 times, he finally noticed something interesting.

The incredibly dense earth-attribute spiritual qi within the walnut seemed to be completely chaotic and haphazard, but there was actually a certain pattern to the way that it was flowing and circulating.

It seemed that these spiritual qi fluctuations would periodically display a rather peculiar state of fusion, and an extremely faint yet special aura would emanate from this type of fluctuations.

Could it be...

Han Li's heartbeat began to accelerate as a thought occurred to him.

This special aura seemed to be rather similar to the power of laws, but also a little different.

After examining the walnut for a while longer, he was still unable to arrive at a concrete conclusion.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce a wooden box.

He removed the lid of the box to reveal a miniature yellow figure with several talismans plastered onto its body. It was none other than the nascent soul of the one-eyed giant from that mysterious space within the ywllow bubble, and its eyes was half-open in a rather disoriented and drowzy state.

Han Li grabbed onto the nascent soul with one hand, and threads of black light emerged from his fingertips before directly entering the nascent soul's body.

In order to uncover the secrets behind those strange human-faced walnuts, the quickest way was naturally to search the giant's soul.

A pained look appeared on the nascent soul's previously wooden and emotionless face, following which a layer of yellow light surfaced over its body.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. There seemed to be some type of strange power residing within the nascent soul, making it very difficult for Han Li's spiritual sense to infiltrate into it.

He gave a cold harrumph as the black light on his hand brightened further, and he gradually increased the forcefulness with which he was enforcing the soul search technique.

The yellow light emanating from the nascent soul's body also became brighter and began to flash violently. A painted look appeared on the nascent soul's face, and it opened its mouth as if to let loose an agonized scream, but it was unable to make any sound under the restrictive effects of the talismans adhered to its body.

Finally, Han Li's spiritual sense pierced through the layer of strange power within the nascent soul before reaching deep into the soul itself, and a hint of elation welled up in Han Li's heart at this development.

However, in the next instant, his expression abruptly changed drastically, and the semi-transparent True Extreme Membrane instantly appeared over his body.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of scintillating yellow light erupted out of the nascent soul, and it exploded violently into an incandescent yellow sun that engulfed Han Li's entire body.

Moments later, the yellow light faded to reveal Han Li once again, and he remained completely unscathed, but there was a dark look on his face.

He hadn't anticipated that the power within the one-eyed giant's nascent soul would be so aggressive, so much so that it had instantly led to the nascent soul's self-detonation as soon as Han Li's spiritual sense pierced into it.

As a result, he wasn't able to glean much information at all, only a few fragments of the one-eyed giant's memories. It seemed that the giant would always consume one of those human-faced walnuts every 10,000 years or so, and that seemed to have a remarkable positive effect on its cultivation.

Han Li heaved a faint sight, then glanced at the human-faced walnut for a while longer before stowing it away.

It seemed that he would have to explore other avenues to find out the origins of this fruit. At the moment, he had only just returned to the Immortal Realm, so he had more important things to attend to.

After a brief moment of further contemplation, he stood up and left the courtyard.

As it turned out, Luo Feng was waiting for him outside the courtyard. "Luo Feng pays his respects to Senior Liu."

"Why are you here, Chief Luo?" Han Li asked as a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

"I came to see if this residence was to your liking, Senior Liu. Also, here are some of the cultivation resources that I've gathered according to your instructions. Unfortunately, due to the short notice, I've only managed to gather some of the items on your list, but I'll send out people to gather the rest as soon as possible, so please bear with me," Luo Feng said with a fawning expression as he produced a black bracelet before offering it to Han Li with both hands.

Han Li reached out to accept the bracelet, then briefly inspected its contents with his spiritual sense before giving a nod.

Luo Feng immediately heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this.

"You came at just the right time. I wanted to ask you if there was a scripture library or something of that nature on this island. There are some things that I want to examine," Han Li said as he stowed the bracelet away.

"There is indeed such a place on our island, Senior Liu. Please come with me," Luo Feng hurriedly replied before leading the way as he flew away into the distance.

Han Li rose up into the air and followed along behind Luo Feng.

As he did so, he quickly inspected his surroundings to find that much of the damage left behind by the battle that had taken place the previous day had already been repaired, and reconstruction efforts had also already begun on the collapsed buildings.

At the same time, many mortals with no cultivation bases had appeared on the previously deserted dock on the island, as well as some of the surrounding towns.

The battle from the day before had wreaked widespread destruction over the island, but it hadn't had much of an impact on the towns inhabited by these mortals.

At this moment, the mortals in those towns and some cultivators had gathered together in one place, and they were performing a type of ritual of worship in front of series of statues depicting the Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island.

"There are many mortals residing on all of the islands in the Black Wind Sea, and they count on the cultivating families on the islands for their protection. During the battle yesterday, all of them went into hiding. The cultivators on the islands have always had a history of regular conflict, but generally speaking, they won't attack the mortals on the other islands," Luo Feng explained after noticing the subject that Han Li's attention had been drawn to.

Han Li nodded in response. The situation here reminded him of the Scattered Star Seas back in the Human Realm. [1]

Moments later, the two of them arrived in front of a large two-story pavilion.

"Esteemed Ancestral God!"

"Chief!"

There were several Spatial Tempering cultivators stationed at the pavilion, and they were greatly startled by the sight of Luo Feng and Han Li. All of them hurriedly extended respectful salutes with reverent looks on their faces.

Luo Feng paid no heed to them and led Han Li directly into the pavilion.

On the first floor of the pavilion was a series of neatly arranged bookshelves, which were laden with all types of scriptures, scrolls, and objects like jade slips.

Han Li swept his gaze around the room to find that this scripture library was quite small, far smaller than the one at the Cold Flame Sect.

"My apologies, Senior Liu. Our tribe is quite weak, so we haven't been able to gather many scriptures. The first floor is filled primarily with cultivation arts and historical accounts, while the second floor contains some scriptures related to treasures and pills," Luo Feng said with an apologetic look in his eyes.

"It's fine. I'll be alright here on my own. I'm sure there are many things that you have to attend to on Dark Veil Island, so there's no need to accompany me," Han Li replied in a nonchalant voice.

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "Yes, Senior Liu."

After that, he turned and departed, yet right as he was about to fly away, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and he stopped in his tracks, then made his way back to the scripture library before waiting patiently outside.

Han Li slowly browsed through the bookshelves, and given his incredibly powerful spiritual sense, he was naturally able to read through all of the scriptures at an incredible speed.

The scriptures collected by Dark Veil Island were quite chaotic, and just as Luo Feng had said, most of the scriptures on the first floor were either historical accounts pertaining to the Black Wind Sea or cultivation arts for those at or below the Grand Ascension Stage.

What Han Li wanted to find was information on Earthly Immortals, but unfortunately, there were very few resources here containing such information.

However, he was eventually rewarded for his efforts. After scouring through virtually the entirety of the first floor, he finally found several old jade slips that contained some information on Earthly Immortals.

Close to an hour later, Han Li set down the final jade slip before opening his eyes.

There wasn't much information contained in these jade slips, but they had still given him a relatively clear understanding of Earthly Immortals and Ancestral Gods.

Just as Luo Feng had described, Earthly Immortals were just one type of immortals, and the only remarkable about them was the special method through which they cultivated.

According to the scriptures, Earthly Immortals could manifest powers of laws using the power of faith from their followers.

However, the powers of laws manifested through this type of external assistance were severely limited in that the Earthly Immortal could only unleash those powers of laws in the region where their faith resided. As soon as they left that area, the powers of laws manifested would become completely ineffective.

Due to the fact that gathering the power of faith formed the foundation for an Earthly Immortal's cultivation, each Earthly Immortal had a statue erected from a special material that was capable of storing and refining the power of faith, forming an Earthly Deity Avatar that was unique to Earthly Immortals, and these Earthly Deity Avatars were able to better harness the powers of laws than even the Earthly Immortals themselves.

Under normal circumstances, the Earthly Immortals would generally be hidden, with only their Earthly Deity Avatars active in the outside world. If that avatar were to be destroyed, then the Earthly Immortal would suffer severe backlash. In more serious cases, the Earthly Immortal could even lose the ability to control their powers of laws, thereby rendering all of their previous efforts completely wasted.

[1]. For more information on the Scattered Star Seas, please refer to RMJI Chapter 389: Heavenly Star City and the Star Palace.

[Back]

Chapter 89: Immortal Treasure

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he processed the information that he had just read.

Even though Earthly Immortals were restricted by their territory, it was still a rather tempting prospect for him to be able to master the power of laws through this special method of cultivation.

Back in the Spirit Realm, he had witnessed the power of laws on more than one occasion. In particularly, he had firsthand experience of just how mighty the power of laws were on the occasions where he used Profound Heavenly Treasures that contained the power of laws of heaven and earth, such as the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword.

This was a type of power that the average cultivation art, secret technique, or even spirit treasure simply couldn't compare with. [1]

However, at the same time, mastery over the power of the laws was something that was extremely luck-dependent. Even someone who possessed a treasure that was imbued with the power of laws could spend their entire life pursuing this goal without ever achieving it. If it were possible to master the power of laws by beoming an Earthly Immortal, then that was certainly an option that was worth considering.

Given the current circumstances, it was very likely that the Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island had already perished, so there most likely weren't going to be any issues if Han Li wanted to take his place and become the Earthly Immortal of this region.

With that in mind, he suddenly swept a hand through the air, and the shadow that he cast onto the ground rippled sligtly, following which a dark figure emerged, revealing itself to be none other than Mo Guang.

Following his emergence, Mo Guang inspected his surroundings with a wooden expression, then said, "Congratulations on finally returning to the Immortal Realm, Fellow Daoist Han. However, I can sense that the world's origin qi here is very sparse. Could it be that you ascended to somewhere extremely secluded?"

"That's right. The place we're currently at is called the Black Wind Sea, and it's an extremely remote area in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region," Han Li replied in a calm voice.

"The Black Wind Sea... I seem to have heard that name before, but I don't have a very clear recollection of it. This place does seem to be very remote, but that could be a blessing. At the very least, you won't have to worry about having your identity exposed or being detected by your enemies in the Immortal Realm for now," Mo Guang said.

"Indeed, that was also part of my considerations," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

The remote nature of this location was indeed one of the reasons why he had decided to stay here for now.

"Why have you summoned me, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"How much do you know about Earthly Immortals, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang?" Han Li asked in a direct and straightforward manner.

"Earthly Immortals? I do know a thing or two about them. These immortals manifest the power of laws by gathering the power of faith, and they're considered to be extremely rare in the Immortal Realm. Why do you ask, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"Extremely rare? Why is that? Aside from the fact that Earthly Immortals are restricted by the areas that they preside over, what other drawbacks are there?" Han Li asked instead of answering Mo Guang's question.

"Earthly Immortals are able to manifest the power of laws by harnessing the power of faith, but there are many limitations to such a method of cultivation. Not only are they unable to use their power of laws outside of their area of jurisdiction, due to the fact that their magic power has been contaminated by the power of faith, it'll be far less pure than the magic power of other immortals of the same caliber.

“On top of that, harnessing the power of faith is an extremely slow process, which will result in Earthly Immortals generally progressing far slower in their cultivation than the average immortal," Mo Guang replied.

"That does sound like a lot of limitations..." Han Li mused with a contemplative expression.

There were quite a few Earthly Immortals in the Black Wind Sea, but that was most likely only due to the special geographic environment of this area.

From the scriptures he had read, he had learned that the entire Black Wind Sea was surrounded by an enormous storm that raged constantly, forming a barrier that completely isolated it from the outside world. Very few immortals from the outside were able to force their way into this place, and the only way to get to the outside world from here was through a teleportation array situated on one of the central islands in the Black Wind Sea.

Due to this special environment, there were many cultivating families and mortals in the Black Wind Sea, thereby making it an ideal location for Earthly Immortals to stamp down their marks.

"Even among Layman Immortals, very few are willing to become Earthly Immortals, given the opportunity," Mo Guang continued.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this before asking, "Layman Immortals? What are those? Are they another type of immortals?"

"Those in the lower realms believe that all immortals are True Immortals, but in reality, only immortals who have mastered the power of laws can be truly referred to as True Immortals. Those who haven't mastered any powers of laws are generally only referred to as Layman Immortals, and there's a great number of such immortals. In fact, the vast majority of immortals fall into the category of Layman Immortals.

“Due to their lack of mastery over the power of laws, Layman Immortals can only progress in their cultivation by culitvating immortal spiritual power. However, seeing as they aren't protected by the power of laws, it's far more difficult for them to transcend tribulations and make progress than it is for True Immortals," Mo Guang explained.

"I see..." Han Li murmured to himself.

"Speaking of which, the path of the Profound Immortal that you've pursued means that you're acutally also a type of Layman Immortal. Profound Immortals primarily dedicate their efforts to cultivating their physical bodies and do not pursue mastery over the power of laws. Those who believe in attaining the power of laws through pure cultivation of the physical body are extremely rare among Layman Immortals, far more so than even Earthly Immortals," Mo Guang continued.

"Thank you for your detailed explanations, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang," Han Li replied with a nod.

"There may only be a wisp of my soul left, but I've still retained most of my memories about the Immortal Realm. If you have any questions in the future, you can feel free to ask me," Mo Guang said, then vanished back into Han Li's shadow before he had a chance to say anything else.

Han Li stood on the spot with his eyes slightly narrowed, processing the information that he had just received.

Moments later, he heaved a faint sigh, then made his way up toward the second floor of the scripture library.

"Immortal treasures draw upon the power of laws of heaven and earth, granting them unfathomable might. Their abilities differ depending on the power of laws that they contain..."

As Han Li was reading through the content of one of the scriptures, he couldn't help but think of the Profound Heavenly Fortune Blade and the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, the two Profound Heavenly Treasures that he had used back in the Spirit Realm. [2]

The Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword was a treasure that ranked in the top three on the Chaotic Myriad Spirit Roll, possessing the unfathomable ability to disregard the laws of heaven and earth of a realm. In this regard, it was rather similar to the immortal treasures being described.

With that in mind, Han Li turned his attention back to the scripture and continued his reading.

Several minutes later, he closed the scripture, having developed a rough understanding of the concept of immortal treasures.

According to the scripture, Profound Heavenly Treasures were treasures that were born from the power of a realm, and they were a type of immortal treasure. In the Immortal Realm, they were collectively known as Essential Spirit Treasures, and they often appeared in the form of spirit trees right as a realm first came into existence.

After that, the spirit tree would be nurtured by the essence of heaven and earth, allowing it to bear spirit flowers or spirit fruits that were capable of disregarding the laws of heaven and earth of that realm. These spirit flowers and fruits were exceedingly rare, generally with only a maximum of four or five of them able to arise in a certain realm.

The cycle through which these spirit trees bore flowers and fruits was also very unique. The process was normally calculated by units of hundreds of thousands of years, but the flowers and fruits that arose would quickly wilt within the span of a few hours to a few days at the very most.

Such a lengthy growth period coupled with such a brief window of time before these spirit flowers and spirit fruits wilted away made them virtually impossible to obtain.

According to the scripture, aside from Essential Immortal Treasures, there also existed another type of immortal treasure known as Acquired Immortal Treasures. These immortal treasures weren't nurtured by the essence of heaven and earth. Instead, they were treasures that were imbued with the power of laws that were refined by immortals.

Neither type of immortal treasure was more powerful than the other, and the power hierarchy was primarily dependent on how much power of laws the treasures possessed, and the types of power of laws that they could wield.

Additionally, the power of the wielder was also an important factor of consideration.

In terms of numbers, Essential Immortal Treasures were far rarer than Acquired Immortal Treasures, but due to the fact that the former often had potential for further evolution through nurturing, they were generally preferred by high-grade immortals.

Of course, both Essential Immortal Treasures and Acquired Immortal Treasures were extremely rare, even in the Immortal Realm, and very few Layman Immortals possessed such immortal treasures. What was even rarer than these immortal treasures were the immortals capable of refining Acquired Immortal Treasures.

At this point in his reading, Han Li couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh as he thought back to the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword that he once possessed.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and his lips quivered slightly as he communicated something through voice transmission.

Mere moments later, Luo Feng appeared on the second floor of the scripture library before cupping his fist in a respectful salute. "What are your instructions, Senior Liu?"

Han Li turned to him before asking in a direct and straightforward manner, "Are there any immortal treasures on Dark Veil Island?"

"I'm afraid not, Senior Liu. Our Ancestral God had previously made attempts to obtain such a treasure, but that wish was never fulfilled. In fact, there are very few Ancestral Gods in the entire Black Wind Sea who possess immortal treasures, let alone our Dark Veil Island," Luo Feng replied with a wry smile.

Han Li didn't have high hopes to begin with, but he still couldn't help but feel a little disappointed upon hearing this.

However, he was quickly able to collect himself, then continued, "From the scriptures that I've read, I've learned that Ancestral Gods can harness the power of faith to manifest the power of laws. I'm sure the Ancestral God of your Dark Veil Island must've also mastered a certain power of laws through this method. Which type of law was it?"

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "Ancestral God Luo Meng mastered the power of the law of water, which is quite commonplace in the Black Wind Sea. Most of the Ancestral Gods on the nearby islands also mastered this type of power of law."

"I see..." Han Li was silent for a moment before a thought occurred to him, and he continued, "On our way here to the scripture library, I noticed many of the people on the island worshipping an Ancestral God statue. Is that statue the Earthly Deity Avatar of your Ancestral God?"

"That statue and all of the other statues on the island are only ordinary statues erected for the purpose of gathering the power of faith. We can communicate with our Ancestral God through them, but they're not true Earthly Deity Avatars. There is only a single statue that serves as our Ancestral God's Earthly Deity Avatar, and it's currently sealed within a restricted zone on the island," Luo Feng replied in a rather hesitant manner.

Han Li was clearly quite intrigued by this, and he immediately instructed, "Where is this restricted zone? Take me there."

Luo Feng was silent for a moment before replying, "Truth be told, Ancestral God Luo Meng's Earthly Deity Avatar was shattered after it was severely wounded by a formidable foe 10,000 years ago, and now, only its head remains. If you would like to see it, then I would be more than happy to take you there right away."

"Lead the way," Han Li instructed in a concise manner.

[1]. For more information on the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1359: Undercurrents.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on the Profound Heavenly Fortune Blade, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1659: Profound Heavenly Fortune Blade.

[Back]

Chapter 90: Search

On the northwestern part of Dark Veil Island was an extremely steep cliff that was over 1,000 feet tall, and the area at the foot of the cliff was riddled with sharp and jagged black rocks.

Waves were crashing into the cliff incessantly, sending foamy spray erupting in all directions.

The cliff face was severely ravaged with countless holes of different shapes and sizes eroded into its surface by the relentless crashing waves. Furthermore, most of the cliff face was covered in green moss and white patches of salt deposits, giving it a patchy and mottled appearance. Some white crabs were occasionally swept out of the holes on the rock face by the seawater that gushed in.

At this moment, Han Li and Luo Feng were hovering in the air above the sea while facing the cliff.

"This is where the remains of Ancestral God Luo Meng's Earthly Deity Avatar reside," Luo Feng said as he pointed at an ordinary-looking hole on the cliff face, which was several dozen feet in size and had also been carved out by erosion.

The hole did look slightly bigger than those around it, but aside from that, there was nothing remarkable about it at all. However, as soon as Han Li attempted to extend his spiritual sense into it, he immediately noticed something quite interesting.

He discovered that as his spiritual sense swept over the hole, it was diverted away by some type of barely detectable force, directing it toward the rock face off to the side.

If it weren't for the fact that his spiritual sense was far more powerful than the average cultivator of his caliber, he wouldn't even have been able to detect that his spiritual sense was being disrupted.

"Interesting..." Han Li murmured to himself as he activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes and peered into the hole.

There was a faint vortex of water vapor slowly revolving deep within the hole, and it was giving off extremely feeble law fluctuations.

"Ancestral God Luo Meng is still yet to reawaken after falling into a state of slumber 10,000 years ago. The Origin Water Seal here is becoming weaker by the day, and it most likely won't even be able to conceal this play anymore after 1,000 more years," Luo Feng sighed as he flew into the hole.

He quickly made a series of hand seals, releasing a string of blue incantation seals in quick succession, all of which vanished into the water vapor vortex deep in the cave in a flash.

The vortex quivered slightly, and the water vapor receded to open up a circular passageway that was as tall as an adult human.

"Please come with me, Senior Liu."

With that, Luo Feng flew into the passageway and vanished in a flash, and Han Li quickly followed along behind him.

Connected to the passageway was a dark corridor that was constructed from bluestone blocks. The corridor was long and winding with no end in sight, and there was a white fluorescent stone embedded into the wall every several dozen feet to illuminate the path ahead.

With his powers, Han Li had nothing to be concerned about, and he trailed along behind Luo Feng in silence.

The corridor sloped gradually downward, and the lower they went, the denser the water-attribute spiritual power in the surrounding area became.

After advancing for 15 minutes, Han Li estimated that they were already several kilometers deep underground. Finally, they reached the end of the corridor, and a bluestone door appeared up ahead.

Luo Feng flipped a hand over to produce an azure badge, which released a burst of azure light into the stone door at his behest.

The stone door slowly opened amid a burst of loud creaking, revealing a square stone chamber that was over 100 feet in size.

It wasn't entirely accurate to call the space a stone chamber as the walls and ground were all bumpy and uneven. Instead, it was more like an underground cave with countless semi-transparent blue stalactites that resembled blue glass hanging down from the roof of the cave.

There were similar materials on the surrounding walls as well, and through them, one could just barely make out the flowing seawater outside. As such, it was clear that they were already submerged deep in the sea.

Han Li swept his gaze around the stone chamber to find that it was completely empty aside from a black stone platform at the very center, which stood at around half the height of an adult human.

There were a series of thin and winding channels engraved onto the surface of the stone platform, and these channels extended all the way downward, spreading over the entire ground.

On the platform was the head of a statue that was no different in size compared with a normal human's head, and it bore a slight resemblance to Han Li's face. This was none other than the visage of Ancestral God Luo Meng.

However, in contrast with the statues that Han Li had previously seen, this head was entirely blue in color, and it seemed to have been carved out of some type of special crystalline material. The head was sparkling under the illumination of the fluorescent white beads around it, and it was releasing extremely rich water-attribute spiritual power.

The face of the head was as smooth as a mirror and was extremely life-like, but its neck was very coarse and rugged, making it look as if the head had been forcibly snapped off from the rest of the body.

Han Li stood a step away from the head, scrutinizing it with an unblinking gaze, and an extremely peculiar sensation suddenly welled up in his heart.

He felt as if this head wasn't an inanimate object. Instead, it was like a living creature that was capable of breathing.

He gently closed his eyes before releasing his spiritual sense, instantly filling the entire stone chamber.

Luo Feng was standing right behind Han Li, and he instantly felt a burst of unfathomably powerful spiritual sense surge toward him from all directions before engulfing him in an instant. He couldn't help but sway unsteadily in the face of this almighty spiritual sense, and cold sweat immediately began to pour down his forehead.

Han Li paid no heed to Luo Feng as he focused his attention on projecting his spiritual sense onto the head before him.

As a result, he discovered that there was a type of energy that was invisible to the naked eye that was converging toward the head from all directions.

This type of energy appeared to be extremely feeble, looking as if it could be blown away by even a stiff breeze, but there was a massive quantity of this energy, and it filled virtually the entire stone chamber.

There was a speck of light within the head that was also invisible to the naked eye, and it was flashing in a rhythmic fashion in a cadence that was very similar to the rhythm of a cultivator's breathing during meditation. With each cycle of inhalation and exhalation, the speck of light would fluctuate in brightness while slowly absorbing the faint traces of energy around it.

It looks like this is that so-called power of faith, Han Li thought to himself as he withdrew his spiritual sense.

At this point, Luo Feng's face had already paled significantly, and he immediately heaved a long sigh of relief. Han Li had only released his spiritual sense for a brief moment, but the back of Luo Feng's robes was already completely drenched in cold sweat.

He took a deep breath, then made his way over to an unremarkable-looking stalactite that was hanging down from the roof of the cave before tapping it a few times.

A string of cracks rang out from the ground below, and a small stone platform slowly emerged, upon which sat a stone box.

Luo Feng opened the box to reveal an antiquated jade slip, then carefully scooped it out of the box before offering it up to Han Li with both hands.

"Senior Liu, please accept this. I'm sure it'll be useful to you."

"What's this?" Han Li asked as he casually accepted the jade slip.

"This is the Myriad Water Immortal Arts, the cultivation art that was once used by Ancestral God Luo Meng. I heard that immortals who've ascended to the Immortal Realm from lower realms must switch to practicing immortal cultivation arts in order to convert their magic power into immortal spiritual power.

“Seeing as you came to the Immortal Realm through alternative avenues rather than through an Ascension Platform, I presume you don't have a suitable cultivation art to use yet, so this Myriad Water Immortal Arts should be useful to you," Luo Feng explained.

"I see. That's very thoughtful of you, Chief Luo Feng," Han Li replied with a nod.

"You're far too kind, Senior Liu. Where we are right now is a place where underwater spirit veins meet, so the water-attribute spiritual power here is extremely abundant. If you wish to cultivate the Myriad Water Immortal Arts, this would be a great place to go into seclusion," Luo Feng said with a smile, clearly very relieved to have achieved his objective of bestowing the cultivation art upon Han Li.

Han Li offered no response as he roughly read through the contents of the jade slip.

The Myriad Water Immortal Arts was a water-attribute immortal cultivation art that would theoretically be able to support his cultivation to the late-True Immortal Stage, but unfortunately, it conflicted greatly with the original cultivation art that he was using, so its potential was severely limited for him.

With that in mind, he returned the jade slip to Luo Feng.

"Senior Liu..." Luo Feng was rather perplexed by this.

"This is a good cultivation art, but unfortunately, water-attribute cultivation arts don't suit me. Is there anywhere else I can obtain immortal cultivation arts from in the Black Wind Sea?" Han Li asked.

Luo Feng considered the question for a moment before replying, "Our Black Wind Sea is a very remote place, so there are extremely few immortal cultivation arts to be found here. Most of them are held in the possession of the Ancestral Gods, and they're very reluctant to share their immortal cultivation arts with others.

“After all, if their cultivation arts were to fall into the hands of others, that could expose their weaknesses to their enemies. The only place to obtain other immortal cultivation arts would be on Black Wind Island at the center of the Black Wind Sea. Large auctions are held there once every century, and there could be immortal cultivation arts put up for auction there."

"I see. How much time is there until the next auction is scheduled to be held?" Han Li asked as an intrigued look appeared in his eyes.

"The next auction is around a dozen years away. However, all of the items that appear on these auctions are generally extremely expensive," Luo Feng replied.

"I see. By the way, there's something I need you to do for me," Han Li said.

"Please go ahead, Senior Liu," Luo Feng hurriedly prompted.

……

Four or five months passed by in the blink of an eye.

During this time, the Cold Crystal Race launched no further attacks, much to the relief of everyone on Dark Veil Island.

In the chief's hall, Luo Feng was pacing back and forth in a slightly agitated manner while occasionally making his way over to the entrance of the hall to look out into the distance with an expectant expression.

During the past few months, he had been instructed by Han Li to find secret techniques and cultivation arts related to sealing nascent souls, but secret techniques of this nature were extremely rare, and he had only managed to find three or four of them thus far.

Judging from Han Li's reactions when he was presented with those secret techniques, it was clear that none of them were to his liking, and that was making Luo Feng rather uneasy.

As a result, he had no choice but to send a Body Integration Stage elder of the tribe to Black Wind Island with a large sum of spirit stones to try his luck there.

Black Wind Island was the most lavish place in the Black Wind Sea, and it was the place that everyone in the Black Wind Sea went to if they were searching for something.

However, it had already been three days since the elder's projected return date, and he still wasn't back yet.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light appeared in the distant sky, rapidly approaching from afar.

Luo Feng was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately rushed out of the hall.

The streak of white light quickly arrived in front of the hall, revealing a middle-aged man.

"You're finally back, Elder Hanliang. How did it go?" Luo Feng hurriedly asked.

"I encountered some trouble on the way back, so I had to take a detour. I spent most of the spirit stones, but thankfully, I was able to acquire what you asked for," the elder replied as he pulled out a jade box, within which were around a dozen jade slips.

"Thank you for your efforts. Go and take a good rest," Luo Feng said as a relieved look appeared on his face, then eagerly picked up the jade box before quickly rushing off to visit Han Li.

Chapter 91: Attempt

Inside a secret chamber in the courtyard that Han Li was staying, the ground and the table were littered with scrunched-up balls of paper, presenting a rather messy sight.

On these scrunched up pieces of paper were all types of complex and profound array runes, and Han Li was seated beside the table, in the process of rapidly inscribing runes down onto more pieces of paper.

Moments later, he raised his head and heaved a long sigh as he set down the brush in his hand.

Recently, he had been racking his brains, tapping into all of his memories and expertise in the art of arrays in an attempt to remove the chains of laws on his nascent soul, but unfortunately, he hadn't made any substantial progress.

Even though he had designed several restrictions that looked as if they could remove those chains of laws, they were only feasible in theory, and after careful consideration, none of them were deemed to be viable in practice.

The biggest problem was that he knew far too little about the eight chains of laws that his nascent soul was bound by. If he could find out what type of power of laws was imbued within these chains, perhaps there would be a sliver of hope.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light flew in from outside before transforming into a voice transmission talisman.

Han Li drew the voice transmission talisman into his grasp, then injected his spiritual sense into it, upon which a hint of elation appeared on his face as he stood up and left the room.

Shortly thereafter, he returned with a jade box in his hand, within which were roughly a dozen jade slips.

He pulled out one of the jade slips before pressing it against his own forehead and injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Moments later, his brows furrowed slightly as he set down the jade slip, then repeated the process with another one of the jade slips.

Soon, most of the jade slips in the box had already been examined, but his brows were only furrowing tighter and tighter.

These jade slips did indeed all contain secret techniques related to seals on nascent souls, and they were more advanced than the ones that been previously brought to him, but they still weren't useful at all for his current predicament. Then again, this wasn't really much of a surprise. The resources on Dark Veil Island were far from abundant, and this was most likely already the limit of what they could do for him.

He hadn't placed much hope in Luo Feng anyway, so he wasn't overly disappointed.

Looks like I'll have to make some time to pay Black Wind Island a visit.

With that in mind, he picked up another azure jade slip before pressing it to his own forehead.

However, this time, after a brief inspection, his expression changed slightly, and he examined the contents of this jade slip for a long time before finally setting it down as a hint of excitement appeared in his eyes.

The jade slip contained a secret technique by the name of Origin Separation Heavenly Refinement, and it was a secret technique designed to seal magic power rather than nascent souls, but after some deliberation, Han Li discovered that the secret technique shared many similarities with the eight chains that his nascent soul was bound by.

At the end of the jade slip was a note, which stated that this secret technique was derived from another secret technique by the name of the Origin Separation Law Chains.

"Origin Separation Law Chains... Could it be that those are the very same chains as the one's on my nascent soul?" Han Li murmured to himself.

He couldn't be sure of this, but just that notion alone was enough to make this secret technique worthy of careful consideration. Through studying this secret technique, perhaps he would be able to find a way to remove the chains of laws on his nascent soul.

Han Li picked up the rest of the jade slips before inspecting their contents one by one, but unfortunately, they didn't yield anything useful to him.

He took a deep breath as he tossed all of the other jade slips into his storage bracelet, then picked up the jade slip that contained the Origin Separation Heavenly Refinement secret technique before pressing it against his own forehead again.

Several days later, Luo Feng received an instruction from Han Li to gather a list of materials, and that came as quite a relief to Luo Feng, who had been feeling rather uneasy.

Even though the materials that he had been asked to gather were all quite expensive, thankfully, the required quantities weren't very large, so gathering them wasn't going to be much of a problem.

……

Half a month later.

A string of dull thumps suddenly rang out from within the peaceful courtyard.

Immediately thereafter, around a dozen pillars of white light rose up all around the courtyard, then formed a white light barrier to encompass the entire area.

After that, a vast expanse of yellow light appeared around the courtyard, forming a yellow light barrier to join the white one.

A sharp screeching sound then suddenly rang out as seven or eight large silver flags appeared around the courtyard, releasing countless silver runes that formed a huge cloud of silver mist, which encompassed the entire area within a radius of several hundred feet around the courtyard.

At this point, the sun was already setting, and the entire Dark Veil Island was basked in an orange afterglow.

Luo Feng and the elders of the island were standing on a tall platform, looking at the courtyard from afar, which had already been inundated by silver mist, and surprised looks had appeared on all of their faces.

"What is Senior Liu doing causing such a commotion?" The question had been raised by Luo Hanliang, the elder who had been sent to Black Wind Island in search of the secret techniques that Han Li had requested.

"We don't need to try and figure out what Senior Liu is doing, and we certainly shouldn't be asking questions," Luo Feng said in a stern voice.

Luo Hanliang still had a perplexed look on his face, but he replied, "Yes, Chief."

"Elders, even though there have been no further attacks from the Cold Crystal Race, this period of peace is only temporary. On top of that, we're all aware that the Cold Crystal Race isn't the only power targeting our island.

“Right now, it's no exaggeration to say that the fate of our entire tribe rests entirely on the shoulders of Senior Liu, so we absolutely cannot afford to do anything that may induce his ire," Luo Feng said with a serious expression as he turned to face the elders.

The elders hurriedly spoke up in agreement.

Luo Feng was silent for a moment, then continued, "Pass down my orders. From this day forth, all entry points into our island are to be sealed off. At the same time, we must increase the number of people patrolling all parts of the island at all times. Some suspicious individuals have appeared on our island of late, and we must keep a closer eye on them. We absolutely cannot afford to have Senior Liu's identity exposed."

The elders immediately accepted their orders before quickly flying away, leaving only Luo Feng behind. He continued to watch Han Li's courtyard from afar, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Meanwhile, a massive array was slowly operating on the ground in the courtyard. Countless intertwining silver patterns on the ground were flashing erratically while fluctuating in brightness, and there were seven silver pillars in the surrounding area, all of which were also riddled with runes and positioned in the configuration of the Big Dipper. It was a setup that was very similar to the array on the Origin Realm Temple's Star Gathering Platform.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed at the center of the array in a completely still manner.

Time slowly passed by, and the sun soon completely set, plunging the entire island into darkness.

On this night, the stars were particularly bright, and they were flashing incessantly.

Han Li took a glance up at the night sky, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he began to chant an incantation, then released an incantation seal onto the array with a sweep of his hand.

The array immediately began to radiate scintillating light, and bursts of enormous spiritual power fluctuations surged through the area. Even though he had set up three layers of restrictions in the courtyard, they were still unable to completely mask the fluctuations.

At this point, Han Li had no attention to spare to such trivial matters as he made a rapid series of hand seals.

The operation of the array sped up considerably, and the Big Dipper in the night sky abruptly brightened as they released beams of bright starlight down from the heavens, converging toward the courtyard to form seven pillars of starlight.

Instead of landing on Han Li, these pillars of starlight landed upon the seven silver stone pillars in the array.

All of the array patterns on the stone pillars instantly lit up, and the pillars themselves also took on a glittering and translucent appearance.

As more and more starlight continued to rain down from above, the patterns on the stone pillars glowed brighter and brighter, and all of a sudden, they began to move as if they were living creatures, forming seven eye-shaped designs.

Immediately thereafter, a string of seven dull thumps rang out in succession as a beam of starlight that was roughly as thick as a human thumb shot out of the seven eye-shaped diagrams, then injected themselves into seven parts of Han Li's body, including his lower abdomen, his chest, and his glabella.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a pained look flashed across his face, and seven specks of blue starlight appeared on his lower abdomen.

The starpower that was being injected into his body flashed slightly, then transformed into a series of thin silver threads that began to flow through his meridians.

At the same time, the magic power in his dantian also began to slowly circulate through his meridians.

The thin threads of starlight and Han Li's magic power flowed through his meridians in unison, but no conflict arose between them, and they were able to coexist in peace.

Han Li took a deep breath as he made a hand seal, and white light began to radiate from his hands.

Countless tiny white runes then appeared in his meridians amid a burst of fluctuations, and his magic power and the starpower in hi sbody were instantly encompassed within these white runes, causing them to brighten in unison before fusing together.

As a result, they formed a series of bright silver threads of light that were as bright as lightning, and those threads of light began to rapidly surge through his meridians while releasing a unique aura.

These threads of light were formed by a fusion of starpower and Han Li's magic power through the use of a secret technique, and they had been created with the express purpose of removing the chains in his nascent soul.

"I hope this works," Han Li murmured to himself, following which the threads of silver light flowed through his meridians before gathering his dantian, where they intertwined to form a silver net of light around the nascent soul before instantly closing in from all directions.

Right at this moment, Han Li activated his Spirit Refinement Technique, and his vast spiritual sense instantly filled his entire dantian, forming countless translucent threads of spiritual sense that shot toward his nascent soul through the gaps in the silver net of light.

Right as the silver net and the threads of spiritual sense were about to make contact with the nascent soul, a faint buzzing sound rang out, and those eight black chains emerged on the surface of the nascent soul's body amid a flash of black light.

The chains then began to tremble violently as if they were sensing a threat, releasing a vast expanse of black mist throughout the area.

The silver net of light and the threads of spiritual sense crashed into the black mist amid a string of cracks and pops, and both sides were rapidly whittling away at one another.

After an indeterminate period of time, as more and more silver threads of light and threads of spiritual sense continued to emerge, the black mist was gradually torn apart.

Finally, some of the threads of spiritual sense and silver light were able to tear through the mist before striking the black chains.

The black chains shuddered violently, and the black light glowing on their surfaces quickly faded.

A hint of elation welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

It seemed that the silver threads of light were effective on the black chains.

With that in mind, his threads of spiritual sense transformed into a series of translucent blades at his behest, then struck the black chains with vicious might.

A string of loud clangs rang out, and the translucent blades instantly shattered into specks of light upon making contact with the black chains, but the trembling of the chains was also becoming more and more pronounced.

Right at this moment, the eight black chains rustled violently in unison, clattering together audibly before abruptly lighting up.

Countless tiny black runes then emerged from the chains to ward off the threads of spiritual sense.

The threads of silver light were also enveloped by countless black runes before seemingly melting away, and the black chains, which had dimmed slightly, quickly returned to their original state.

Chapter 92: Ninth Chain

Han Li's expression darkened slightly at the sight of this abrupt turn of events, but he then quickly composed himself again.

Given how strange those black chains were, it was only to be expected that they wouldn't be removed so easily.

After taking a moment to catch his breath, he launched a renewed assault, and an even denser expanse of threads of silver light surged incessantly into his dantian before hurtling toward the black chains.

A string of loud cracks and pops rang out, and the silver threads of light were still instantly shattered upon making contact with the black chains, but the chains themselves were also being constantly weakened.

Meanwhile, the blades formed by Han Li's spiritual sense continued to come crashing down.

In the face of these waves of attacks, the black runes around the chains became dimmer and dimmer.

However, Han Li wasn't all that elated to see this.

The black runes were being whittled away, but at this point, his magic power was also close to running out.

Even though he had made extensive preparations, storing the maximum amount of magic power that he could in his dantian and all of his organs, it seemed that this was still far from enough.

Han Li let loose a low roar as he drew upon all of his remaining magic power, causing all of the silver threads of light in his dantian to transform into eight glowing palms of silver light in a flash. The silver palms passed through the remaining black runes, then grabbed onto the eight black chains before tugging violently.

The black chains were instantly stretched taut, and a burst of sharp pain speared in Han Li's nascent soul.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly, but a hint of excitement welled up in his heart.

Ever since his nascent soul was sealed by these black chains, he had been unable to feel it at all, but he had finally re-established some form of connection with it.

He immediately activated his Spirit Refinement Technique to maximal capacity, and all of his spiritual sense surged into his dantian before splitting into two, forming a pair of translucent giant axes amid a flash of light.

Several bolts of silver lightning then erupted out of the silver palms before wrapping themselves around the hilts of the giant axes, then raised them before bringing them down with tremendous force to strike the taut black chains.

A resounding boom rang out as the black chain shuddered violently, and a series of cracks appeared on the spot where it had been struck by the ax.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he sent the giant ax crashing down once again.

Right at this moment, spatial fluctuations erupted around him, and a black chain appeared out of thin air, then vanished into his body in a flash before he was able to do anything.

The surrounding starlight array had been completely unable to impede the black chain.

After entering Han Li's body, the black chain wrapped itself around his nascent soul in a flash, connecting together with the other eight chains.

Countless black runes then emerged on the surface of the nine black chains, and they released bursts of dazzling black light that instantly pierced through the silver hands gripping onto the chains, causing them to disintegrate into nothingness.

The pair of giant axes also instantly shattered upon contact with the chains, crumbling away into countless specks of translucent light.

……

Meanwhile, in a hall deep in a certain desert in the Immortal Realm.

The zombie-like man had a single hand outstretched in front of him, and his entire body was enveloped in dazzling black light, within which countless black runes were flashing incessantly.

The chains around him were dancing wildly like countless tentacles, crashing into the ground and the walls to cause a thunderous commotion.

The zombie-like man then set down his raised arm, and the black light glowing from his body quickly subsided, while the chains around him also settled down and fell onto the ground.

"Seeing as you're a disciple of mine, I'll help you one last time," the zombie-like man murmured to himself, then closed his eyes.

……

Inside the courtyard, Han Li instantly rose to his feet before inspecting his surroundings with blue light flashing in his eyes and a furious look on his face.

At the same time, he released his spiritual sense without any hesitation, instantly encompassing an area of the surrounding with a radius of thousands of kilometers around Dark Veil Island, but he was unable to discover anything in the end.

A short while later, he slowly sat back down with a grim expression.

The black chain that had just suddenly appeared had to have been sent from afar by an extremely powerful individual.

It seemed that the one who had placed this seal upon his nascent soul was far more formidable than he imagined.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he hurriedly injected his enormous spiritual sense into his dantian once again, forming a layer of translucent light that enveloped his nascent soul.

Perhaps this was nothing more than a futile effort, but he was hoping that doing this would cut off some connection between his nascent soul and the outside world.

After doing all of that, Han Li sat down once again with his legs crossed, then flipped a hand over to produce a Cloud Crane Herb that was in the thousands of years old before devouring it.

Even though his final attempt had ultimately failed, what was quite encouraging to him was that this method really did present a possibility for him to rid himself of these black chains.

The black chain that had appeared out of nowhere at the end had thwarted his plans, but as long as he had sufficient magic power to support his efforts, even with the addition of this new chain, he was confident that he would be able to break through this restriction.

……

A month later, in a peaceful courtyard on Dark Veil Island.

Seven massive pillars of white light were trailing down from the heavens, encompassing the entire courtyard.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes shut in the courtyard, and countless specks of white light were slowly dancing around him like fireflies, occasionally coming into contact with his skin, only to quickly spring back up into the air again.

At this moment, there was a thin veil of white light draped over the courtyard, but it was giving off bursts of gentle yet extremely rich starpower fluctuations.

Right at this moment, the seven specks of blue light on Han Li's chest and abdomen gradually faded, and the white light around him also slowly dissipated, while the seven pillars of light descending from the night sky quickly disappeared.

He slowly opened his eyes to look up at the starry night sky, and a wry smile appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "As expected, it didn't work..."

During this past month, he had explored several methods to try and increase the amount of magic power in his body, but none of them had yielded any results.

During the past few days, he had begun to continue cultivating his Big Dipper Origin Arts, trying to find a way to further advance his Organ Refinement Origin Arts.

However, even though he could still draw starpower down from the heavens, the seven profound apertures in his body were already completely filled and unable to absorb any more starpower.

Han Li sighed as he continued to look up at the Big Dipper Origin Arts in the night sky, and his vision gradually began to blur, making it appear to him as if several of the stars in the Big Dipper were about to overlap and fuse together.

Right at this moment, a thought suddenly occurred to him: if he couldn't increase the amount of magic power in his body, then why didn't he just cultivate an avatar?

Han Li stroked his chin as he began to carefully ponder this notion.

Using an avatar to cultivate and accumulate magic power would allow him to bypass the problems presented by his sealed nascent soul. As long as his avatar could provide him with sufficient magic power, then he would be able to remove those troublesome black chains.

However, where was he going to get an avatar from?

Han Li had previously cultivated the Profound Nascent Formation Arts [1] and had once successfully cultivated a Wood Spirit Nascent, but this cultivation art required the refinement of a second nascent soul, which was a process that not only required the fulfillment of a very rigorous set of prerequisites, it also required the expenditure of a huge amount of time and energy, both of which were exactly the things that he couldn't afford to waste right now.

Out of all of the other avatar techniques that he knew of, all of them required a great deal of time investment as well, so they were also unfeasible to him.

Right as he was feeling stumped by this predicament, the thought of that head in the restricted zone on Dark Veil Island suddenly sprang into his mind, and his eyes immediately lit up.

Hold on, an Earthly Deity Avatar is also an avatar!

With that in mind, Han Li immediately stood up from the ground, then swept a hand through the air to release a streak of light out of his sleeve, which sped away toward a certain part of the island.

……

A few minutes later, two figures appeared in the restricted underwater zone situated in the northwestern part of Dark Veil Island.

One of them was Han Li, and he was accompanied by Luo Feng, who had a perplexed look on his face.

He had been cultivating in his cave abode just now when he suddenly received a voice transmission talisman, and he instantly traveled to the underwater cavern as instructed, but he had no idea why he had been summoned here.

"Is there something I can do for you, Senior Liu?" he asked.

"I have something that I want to ask you later," Han Li replied in a concise manner without offering any further explanation.

After that, he strode over to the stone platform before reaching out and lifting up the blue statue head.

After inspecting the head for a moment, blue light flashed within his eyes, and he extended a finger toward the head's glabella.

Luo Feng was quite alarmed to see this, and he was struck by an instinctive urge to stop Han Li, but in the end, he didn't do anything, merely remaining on the spot with his mouth gaped open slightly and his body inclined forward.

In the instant that Han Li's fingertip came into contact with the statue's glabella, a burst of light that was invisible to the naked eye had appeared on the head of the statue before surging through the air like rippling water.

The burst of light wasn't very bright, nor did it carry any destructive force, but in the instant that it came into contact with Han Li's body, he immediately shuddered as an incredulous look appeared on his face.

To his surprise, the chains within his nascent soul's body were faintly resonating with this burst of light, swaying slightly as the light continued to ripple through the air.

After a brief moment of contemplation, a burst of azure light suddenly lit up from Han Li's hand, and a wisp of pure magic power shot out of his fingertip before entering the statue head.

A storm seemed to have suddenly been stirred up within the statue head, and boundless power of faith surged and churned violently, releasing several bursts of light blue magic power that clashed directly with the azure magic power that Han Li had just released.

The azure magic power was very pure, but there was only a tiny wisp of it, and it was instantly dispelled on contact.

Han Li was ecstatic to see those bursts of blue magic power, and he withdrew his fingertip from the statue's head before turning to Luo Feng as he asked, "Regarding the Earthly Deity Avatar of your Dark Veil Island's Ancestral God, did it possess any other abilities aside from its ability to use the power of laws?"

At this point, the statue head had returned to normal, as had everything else in the underwater cavern.

Luo Feng was quite relieved to see that the statue head was unharmed, and he replied, "Ancestral God Luo Meng's Earthly Deity Avatar possessed no nascent soul, but it was able to use other abilities by converting the power of faith into magic power."

[1]. For more information on the Profound Nascent Formation Arts, please refer to RMJI Chapter 657: Profound Nascent Formation Arts.

[Back]

Chapter 93: Prerequisites

"I see..." Han Li murmured to himself with a contemplative expression.

With that, it was confirmed that not only was an Earthly Deity Avatar able to manifest the power of laws using the power of faith, it could also convert the power of faith into magic power.

Hence, if he were to begin pursuing the path of an Earthly Immortal and refine an Earthly Deity Avatar of his own, there was a chance that he would be able to use that avatar to assist him in removing the restrictions on his nascent soul.

Furthermore, judging from the faint resonance that the power of faith in the statue head had displayed with the chains in his nascent soul, it seemed that refining an Earthly Deity Avatar was going to have some additional unexpected benefits that would aid him in his endeavor to free his nascent soul.

However, this was still going to be quite a troublesome path to pursue.

After all, once he embarked on this path, the risk of his magic power being contaminated by the power of faith would arise, and if he weren't careful, he could be permanently reduced to an Earthly Immortal.

However, it certainly wasn't impossible for him to pursue this path until his nascent soul was freed, taking measures to ensure that his magic power remained uncontaminated by the power of faith during this process, then abandon this path and pursue other paths of cultivation.

On the surface, Han Li appeared to be quite calm, but internally, he was feeling intensely conflicted.

After a while, Han Li turned to Luo Feng and said, "There were quite a few resources pertaining to Earthly Immortals in the scripture library, but most of them were only introductory texts that don't actually describe how one can pursue the path of cultivating as an Earthly Immortal. Do you know anything about this subject, Chief Luo?"

Luo Feng was rather taken aback to hear this. "Could it be that you're also interested in pursuing this path, Senior Liu?"

"Just tell me what you know for now," Han Li replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"Generally speaking, most Earthly Immortals will choose to become an entity similar to the Ancestral God of our tribe, then over time, through generations upon generations of reproduction, an Ancestral God will slowly accumulate the power of faith through their followers, and only after a process of accumulation and acclimation is completed will they truly be able to pursue the path of cultivating as an Earthly Immortal," Luo Feng explained.

"Can the power of faith only be provided by one's direct descendants?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Other people can also provide the power of worship, but generally speaking, the power of worship that they provide will be rather impure, making it virtually impossible to harness for Ancestral Gods who are still yet to become Earthly Immortals. In contrast, the power of worship from one's direct descendants will be most devout, and it'll also have the highest level of compatibility with the Ancestral God.

“As time passes, the number of one's descendants will naturally increase, so most people who pursue this path will choose to spend some time to expand their clans first," Luo Feng explained.

"I see. Go on," Han Li prompted.

"Due to the fact that an Earthly Immortal's rate of cultivation and potency of the power of laws that they manifest is dependent on how much power of faith they're able to harness, in order for them to accelerate their progression, they have to constantly expand their territory while also securing as much resources as possible. Only then will they be able to produce more descendants and expand their clans as quickly as possible."

Luo Feng currently possessed the most advanced cultivation base out of all of the local residents of Dark Veil Island, and he had already been cultivating for a very long time in the Black Wind Sea, so he was quite knowledgeable about the process of becoming an Earthly Immortal and the steps that had to be taken for future progression.

However, Han Li couldn't help but feel a little disappointed after hearing Luo Feng's description.

Pursuing the path of an Earthly Immortal wasn't as easy as he imagined, and given his current situation, there was no way that he would dedicate an extended period of time to developing a large clan.

As for future expansions of territory, that was undoubtedly going to encroach upon the interests of other Ancestral Gods, so he would inevitably find himself swept up in a constant cycle of conflicts, and that was definitely not something that he wanted to have to deal with.

"Are there any other ways to pursue this path, Chief Luo?" Han Li asked.

"There is a way that allows one to become an Earthly Immortal without having to go down the Ancestral God path," Luo Feng replied after a brief hesitation.

"I'm assuming some special requirements must be met, right?" Han Li asked.

"Indeed. Almost all of the high-grade cultivators in the entire Black Wind Sea have heard of this method that allows one to directly cultivate as an Earthly Immortal, but barely anyone has ever successfully gone down that path because two prerequisites have to be met first," Luo Feng replied with a wry smile.

"Go on," Han Li prompted.

"The first prerequisite is that the Earthly Deity Avatar used by the cultivator cannot be cultivated using normal materials. Instead, it must be refined using something that is inherently imbued with the power of laws.

“The second prerequisite is that the Earthly Immortal cultivation art used must be one that can allow the cultivator to directly skip over the Ancestral God stage, so essentially, it has to be a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art that directly harnesses the impure power of worship of normal people," Luo Feng explained.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Truth be told, not only does our tribe not possess a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art, there most likely aren't that many even in the entire Black Wind Sea. As for the materials required to cultivate an Earthly Deity Avatar, Ancestral God Luo Meng has left some materials on the island in the past, but with my limited knowledge, most of them are materials that I don't recognize, so I'm not sure if any of them contain the power of laws. I can take you to inspect those materials in person if you'd like," Luo Feng offered.

"Please lead the way, Chief Luo," Han Li replied with a nod.

Thus, the two of them quickly left the restricted zone, and shortly thereafter, they appeared in an underground secret chamber.

The secret chamber wasn't very large, and there were around a dozen wooden shelves inside, upon which were placed many materials, including demon beast materials, some spirit medicines, and some types of ore.

These items seemed to be quite rare, but that was only for Spatial Tempering and Body Integration cultivators.

Luo Feng was clearly also aware of this, and he led Han Li straight to a green jade shelf at the very back of the secret chamber. The jade shelf was completely enshrouded beneath a layer of blue light, and there was a small collection of items visible on the shelf.

"These are all of the things that Ancestral God Luo Meng left behind, Senior Liu," Luo Feng said.

He then pulled out a blue badge to release a burst of blue light, which instantly dispelled the blue light barrier around the shelf in a flash.

With the removal of the blue light barrier, it was revealed that most of the items on the shelf were a type of round black ore that was giving off peculiar glacial fluctuations, indicating that it seemed to be some type of special material.

Aside from these pieces of ore was a miscellaneous collection of items, including several orange pieces of wood that were giving off a faint fragrance, a piece of golden ore, a pair of broken halberd treasures, and a palm-sized white jade badge.

Han Li picked up these items one by one, and after a careful examination, he couldn't help but shake his head in disappointment.

He was able to identify the orange wood and golden ore as two types of precious tool refinement materials. He didn't recognize the black ore, but there was clearly no power of laws imbued within them anyway.

As for the pair of halberds, they would've been a powerful set of spirit treasures in the past, but for some reason, their spiritual nature was severely diminished, so they weren't anywhere near as powerful as they once had been.

Luo Feng couldn't help but heave a faint sigh at the sight of Han Li's disappointed expression.

He was hoping that Han Li would be able to become an Earthly Immortal. That way, he wouldn't be able to leave the Black Wind Sea and would have to remain on Dark Veil Island. Given enough time, the Luo Clan would be able to produce a new Ancestral God.

If it weren't for this possibility, there was no way that he would’ve brought Han Li here so easily.

Right at this moment, the white jade badge on the shelf seemed to have caught Han Li's interest.

Luo Feng was rather taken aback to see this. "Is there something special about this badge, Senior Liu?"

He had examined all of the items here countless times before, and he had never noticed anything special about the jade badge.

Han Li didn't immediately offer a response. Instead, he carefully examined the jade badge for a while longer before replying, "I can't quite put my finger on it right away, but there seems to be something strange about this badge. I'll take it back with me for further examination."

"That's not a problem at all," Luo Feng immediately replied.

"Also, I'll have to trouble you to keep an eye out for high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation arts and materials imbued with the power of laws. Notify me right away if you find anything," Han Li instructed.

"Rest assured, Senior Liu, you can count on me," Luo Feng replied.

……

A short while later, Han Li returned to the secret chamber in the courtyard that he was staying in, and he sat down onto his cushion with a contemplative look in his eyes.

If he wanted to remove the seal on his nascent soul in a short time, it seemed that the only possible solution was to pursue that unorthodox Earthly Immortal path.

However, he had to satisfy the two prerequisites first.

The Black Wind Sea was a vast place, and there were several secret regions in it. Those regions were extremely perilous places, but they were also home to some rare materials and exotic demon beasts, so perhaps it was possible to find some materials imbued with the power of laws in there.

With that in mind, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and a flipped a hand over to produce a certain object. It was the eye of the one-eyed giant that he had slain in that mysterious bubble.

The light released by the eye was able to significantly slow down the target, and that had left a deep impression on him.

He had examined this object before, but back then, he had been quite pressed for time, so he wasn't able to conduct a very thorough examination.

If this eye contained a hint of power of laws, then that would save him a lot of effort.

He began to chant an incantation, and blue light flashed within his eyes, while his Law Destruction Eye emerged on his glabella.

The three eyes lit up in unison before each releasing a beam of light, two blue and one black, which converged at a single point before slowly fusing together.

Han Li then began to make a series of hand seals, and the three beams of light quickly completely fused as one to form a black and blue eyeball that was releasing waves of black and blue light, which enshrouded the eye that he was holding.

At the same time, he also released his spiritual sense, manifesting a series of threads of spiritual sense that enveloped the eye before seeping into it.

Moments later, a hint of elation welled up in Han Li's heart.

Through the examination of his spiritual sense, he had made some encouraging discoveries.

Deep inside the eye were several extremely faint specks of white light.

After making this observation, Han Li immediately transformed his threads of spiritual sense into a cloud of mist so that he could better examine these specks of white light.

A short while later, he opened his eyes, and there was more than a hint of excitement flashing within them.

It was very faint, but was certain that those specks of white light contained a hint of law fluctuations.

Chapter 94: An Ancestral God's Last Words

Han Li suppressed the excitement in his heart as he thought about how to proceed.

Sure enough, he had guessed correctly in that the beams of light that the one-eyed giant had been capable of releasing out of its eye were indeed imbued with some type of power of laws.

However, he still wasn't sure exactly what type of power of laws the eye contained.

However, given that most of the abilities that the giant had unleashed were of the earth attribute, and it possessed the ability to increase the force of gravity, Han Li speculated that the eye was imbued with the power of gravitational laws, a branch of the laws of earth.

Ultimately, it didn't really matter to Han Li. Regardless of what type of power of laws the eye contained, all that mattered to him was that it was an object that contained the power of laws.

The black and blue eye in front of Han Li dissipated at his behest, and a weary look appeared on his face.

He flipped a hand over to produce a Cloud Crane Herb before devouring to replenish his depleted magic power reserves, then placed the eye back into his storage treasure.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce another object. This time, it was the human-faced walnut that he had already previously briefly examined with his spiritual sense.

He pursed his lips before beginning to chant an incantation again, and his eyes and the Law Destruction Eye on his glabella each released a burst of light to form that same black and blue eye.

The black and blue ripples enveloped the human-faced walnut, and the threads of spiritual sense also reappeared before seeping into the walnut.

Time slowly passed by, and as Han Li opened his eyes, a faint smile appeared on his face once again.

The black and blue eye vanished in a flash, and his spiritual sense also receded out of the walnut.

He devoured another Cloud Crane Herb, then played with the human-faced walnut in his hand with a hint of elation in his eyes.

It was very feeble, but he was certain that he had sensed a hint of laws of earth imbued within the walnut.

After that, he pulled out a few more human-faced walnuts before examining them one by one, and sure enough, the outcome was the same.

It seemed that he was extremely fortunate, considering these walnuts were things that he had obtained completely by chance in the interrealm gap.

So one of the prerequisites for cultivating as an Earthly Immortal has been fulfilled, but I have to think carefully about which one I should choose between the eye and the walnut.

Han Li exhaled as his eyes narrowed slightly in contemplation.

According to the information that he had received from Luo Feng, the type of law that an Earthly Deity Avatar was going to manifest depended greatly on what type of power of laws was imbued within the materials used to refine the statue.

Furthermore, this type of special Earthly Deity Avatar that he was going to refine was going to have a direct correlation with the type of power of laws imbued within the material used.

However, Han Li quickly shook his head and rid himself of that train of thought.

It was still too early to be pondering this matter. His top priority at the moment was to track down a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation first.

He carefully stowed the human-faced walnut away, then flipped a hand over to produce another object. This time, it was the white jade badge.

Blue light flashed within his eyes, and through the use of his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he could see that the white jade badge was enveloped within a faint layer of blue light.

This layer of blue light struck Han Li with a rather strange feeling, indicating that it was definitely no ordinary restriction.

There were many wavy projections that could be seen within the blue light, and it was imbued with a hint of water-attribute fluctuations. It was clear that Ancestral God Luo Meng was the one who had cast the restriction onto this jade badge, but it seemed that Luo Feng and the others were completely unable to detect it at all.

A hint of curiosity appeared in Han Li's eyes, and he flicked his fingers through the air in quick succession, releasing around a dozen streaks of white light that landed in the surrounding area, revealing themselves to be a series of white array flags.

Dazzling white light radiated from the array flags to form a lotus-flower-shaped white array that was revolving incessantly.

Han Li tossed the white jade badge through the air, and it was instantly caught by the white array, hovering in mid-air above it.

He then made a hand seal before releasing a series of incantation seals, and countless hite runes emerged from the lotus flower array before converging toward the jade badge and surging into it in a frenzy.

The layer of blue light on the jade badge's surface immediately brightened as it attempted to ward off the white runes, but under Han Li's manipulation, the white runes were constantly changing forms and attacking the layer of blue light from different angles, gradually breaking through the restriction before seeping into the jade badge.

The restriction placed on the white jade badge was certainly not an easy one to break through, but thankfully, Han Li was an expert in array and restrictions, and in addition to that, his enormous spiritual sense and Brightsight Spirit Eyes allowed him to identify the weaknesses in the restriction, thereby giving him a significant advantage.

As time slowly passed by, the layer of blue light on the jade badge dimmed further and further, and before long, there was only a thin layer of it left.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly sped up in his hand seals, and the white lotus flower array abruptly brightened as countless white runes emerged.

All of the runes converged together to form around a dozen sharp white spikes, which stabbed into the jade badge with vicious force.

Finally, the layer of blue light on the jade badge flashed one last time before disintegrating.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, yet right as he was about to grab the jade badge, some of the runes on the badge abruptly began to move as if they were living creatures.

Immediately thereafter, scintillating white light erupted from the badge, forming a series of white clouds, from within which bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly.

Han Li was greatly alarmed by this, and he immediately sprang to his feet.

Large white clouds continued to surged out of the jade badge before revolving around it, quickly forming a strange vortex that was several dozen feet in size.

A black hole appeared at the center of the vortex, and initially, it was only around the size of a human fist, but as the vortex continued to revolve, the hole grew larger and larger. After just a few seconds, it had expanded to the size of a millstone, and violent spatial fluctuations were emanating from within it.

The hole was pitch-black and unfathomably deep, making it impossible to see where it led to.

Han Li quickly composed himself as he observed the strange passageway before him, then closed his eyes before releasing his spiritual sense toward it.

However, moments later, he opened his eyes as a wry smile appeared on his face.

There was some type of strange power within the passageway that was keeping out his spiritual sense, preventing him from examining what was inside.

This burst of power certainly wasn't weak, but with his enormous spiritual sense, he would be capable of forcing his way through it if he so pleased. However, at the moment, half of his spiritual sense was dedicated to sealing off his nascent soul from the outside world, so he was unable to dedicate his wholehearted effort to the cause.

After remaining on the spot for a while with a hesitant look on his face, he decided to leap into the black hole.

Within the hole was a passageway that was around 10 feet in size, within which was a vast expanse of white light, while a dark exit as suspended in space up ahead.

Upon emerging from the exit, Han Li was immediately greeted by a fragrant aroma in the air.

He reflexively held his breath as he inspected his surroundings with furrowed brows, upon which he discovered that he was situated in a lush forest that was only around a half a kilometer in size.

The entire surrounding area was enshrouded in a layer of dense mist, and it seemed that this was a small secret area.

After a brief inspection of the area, he discovered that the world's origin qi here wasn't any more abundant than it was in the Black Wind Sea, so it didn't seem to be any cultivation paradise.

Most of the surrounding trees were over 1,000 feet tall with perfectly straight trunks, and only near the tops of the trees did branches emerge to support large green canopies, casting large areas of shade that gave the entire forest a rather dark and dim appearance.

There were very few shrubs growing in the forest, and no animals could be seen, either. Overall, it a forest that certainly wasn't teeming with life.

Through the gaps between the trees, Han Li could see that there was an open area that appeared to be something like a plaza deep in the forest.

He passed through the forest to find that it wasn't a plaza that he had spotted. Instead, it was only a clearing with not a single tree in an area with a radius of around 100 feet.

There was only a large purple flower growing at the center of the clearing. The flower resembled a peony in shape, but it was as large as a lotus flowers. It was entirely purple in color, with leaves that were similar to banana leaves, but it's stamen resembled a chicken's crest, giving it a very peculiar appearance.

This flower was the source of the peculiar aroma that Han Li had caught a whiff of earlier.

Several dozen feet away from the flower was a two-story wooden building that was no more than 30 feet tall. Due to disrepair and lack of maintenance, the window and doorframes had all rotten away, and most of the roof had already collapsed, while slippery moss was growing all over the walls, giving the entire thing a very dilapidated appearance.

To the left of the building's entrance was a gray corpse, which was half propped-up against the wall behind it. Its skeletal hands were extended out in front of it, as if it were reaching for something, and its fingers were pointed right at the large purple flower.

Han Li examined the corpse for a moment, following which his eyes suddenly lit up, and a peculiar look appeared on his face.

He quickly made his way over the body, then crouched down to conduct a closer inspection.

The body's clothes were already rotten and in tatters, resembling patches of mud that were draped all over the corpse's body, and a thick layer of dirt and dust had settled onto the set of remains.

However, even though the dirt and dust, Han Li could see that the bones beneath were still glowing faintly, presenting quite an intriguing sight and indicating that the corpse belonged to a powerful cultivator.

With a gentle sweep of Han Li's hand, a light breeze instantly blew past, removing the clothes and debris on the set of remains to reveal a shimmering white skeleton.

The sound of something falling to the ground then rang out, and as it turned out, several jade slips and a storage ring had slipped out of the corpse's grasp.

Han Li picked up one of the jade slips, then inspected it momentarily before pressing it against his own glabella and injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The jade slip contained nothing more than a short message:

"If a descendant of our Luo Clan has managed to enter this place, do not be alarmed. I am your Ancestral God, Luo Meng, and I have already been in seclusion here for over 9,000 years since my avatar was destroyed.

“I intended to nurture a Soulbirth Flower in order to reforge an Earthly Deity Avatar, but I was attacked by powerful enemies over 3,000 years before the flower is due to reach full maturity. I was able to kill the enemy, but I'm afraid that the injuries I sustained during the battle are too severe to recover from..."

Moments later, Han Li opened his eyes before heaving a faint sigh. As it turned out, Luo Meng had already perished here over 1,000 years ago, and all of the people of his tribe were still completely oblivious.

However, perhaps it was exactly because of this that no news of this managed to spread to the outside world. As a result, even though the Cold Crystal Race and the other opposing forces of Dark Veil Island were already itching to get their hands on a slice of the pie, they still waited until only recently before launching their attacks.

This was already a bright silver lining on what was otherwise a terribly dark cloud.

Chapter 95: Heaven Controlling Vial Malfunction

Instead of stowing the jade slip away, Han Li set it down beside Luo Meng's remains.

Even though he was already dead, he was able to leave some final words behind before his demise. As for whether he had intentionally refrained from informing his people of his imminent death in order to delay attacks from opposing forces, that was something that was impossible to find out.

However, at the conclusion of his final words, he mentioned that if any members of his clan managed to ascend to immortality, then they could use the materials that he had left behind to refine an Earthly Deity Avatar, thereby becoming the new Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island.

Those who pursued the Great Dao were often said to be heartless and uncaring, but given that pursuing the path of the Earthly Immortal depended on a foundation of bloodline and faith, Earthly Immortals shared more ties with others than the average immortal did, and as a result, they were less aloof and apathetic.

"Fellow Daoist Luo Meng, I am unable to become the new Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island, but I will do everything in my power to protect your clan and your people. In exchange, I'll take the materials that you left behind as compensation," Han Li said to the set of remains.

He then withdrew his gaze before picking up one of the remaining jade slips on the ground and pressing it against his own glabella.

Moments later, a faint smile appeared on his face.

This jade slip contained the refinement method for an Earthly Deity Avatar, and it was exactly what he was currently looking for.

According to the method stipulated in the jade slip, not only was the refinement process for an Earthly Deity Avatar extremely complex, the materials required were also extremely rare and diverse. The most special and vital material among them was a spirit plant known as the Soulbirth Flower.

While refining an Earthly Deity Avatar, a whole flower had to be used, and Soulbirth Elixir had to be extracted from the flower before being refined together with the other materials.

The older the flower was, the better the effect that it would have on the refinement process, and the more intelligent the refined avatar would be. However, at the very least, it had to be over 10,000 years old. Otherwise, it would be impossible for it to achieve the effect of manifesting a soul for the avatar. If the flower were over 100,000 years old, then the soul that it manifested would be close to perfect.

At the end, the jade slip also provided a description of the Soulbirth Flower, stating that before reaching 100 years of age, the plan would only have leaves and no flower. Only after reaching 100 years old would a white flower blossom from the plant, and after 1,000 years, the flower's petals would turn from white to red.

After 5,000 years, the petals would turn from red to purple, then to an even darker shade of purple after 8,000 years, while also growing a chicken-crest-shaped stamen. Upon reaching 10,000 years of age, a golden stripe would appear on each flower petal, and with each passing block of 10,000 years, a new stripe would emerge.

As for whether it would display any other transformations after 100,000 years, there were no records of that in the jade slip, perhaps because 100,000-year-old specimens of this flower were simply far too rare.

Aside from being used to refine Earthly Deity Avatars, this flower was also immensely beneficial for an Earthly Immortal in breaking through cultivation bottlenecks. However, the nurturing process was extremely difficult, and there were barely any specimens left that were over 1,000 years old.

Hence, even specimens above 5,000 years of age were extremely rare even in the entire Black Wind Sea, let alone 10,000-year-old specimens. Demand for the flower far outweighed supply, and it was often the case that no such flower could be found in the market no matter how much money was offered.

The large purple flower beside Han Li was naturally none other than the Soulbirth Flower, and judging from its appearance, it had to already be over 8,000 years old. If it were to appear in the Black Wind Sea, it would undoubtedly start a war among countless Earthly Immortals.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he picked up another jade slip.

The content recorded in this jade slip was rather special. Not only was it worded in a very special way, the meaning that it was trying to convey was also extremely complex and profound.

Initially, Han Li was rather perplexed by what he was seeing, but after some careful examination, he was elated to find that the jade slip contained the method to refine the power of faith.

This included the method to harness the power of faith, as well as how to convert it into magic power and how to use it to manifest the power of laws.

As for the final remaining jade slip, that contained a record of Luo Meng's cultivation insights, as well as his analysis pertaining to cultivating as an Ancestral God.

Han Li only briefly read through this jade slip and didn't examine it in great detail, but some of the content inside had managed to catch his attention.

Due to the special geographic location of the Black Wind Sea, the area of the sea here far exceeded that of the landmasses. Hence, out of all of the world's origin qi here, the most commonplace type was of the water attribute.

As a result, it was far easier to cultivate and manifest the laws of water here than other types of power of laws. Additionally, due to the nature of the geography here, the powers of those who used the laws of water were enhanced, thereby giving them a natural advantage over wielders of other types of power of laws.

It was exactly because of this that it was far easier to find Earthly Immortal scriptures related to the laws of water, and as a result, there was a severe shortage of all resources that contained the power of laws of water in the entire Black Wind Sea, with many wars of different scales waged over such resources.

After stowing those three jade slips away, Han Li's gaze fell upon the storage ring, and he began to inspect its contents.

Sure enough, the ring contained the water-attribute Earthly Deity Avatar refinement materials mentioned in the jade slip from before, and that included the same blue crystal material that had been used to craft the head of that statue of Luo Meng.

Han Li stowed all of those items away without any hesitation, then returned his attention to the Soulbirth Flower not far away.

After a brief moment of contemplation, the strode over to the flower, then removed the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck before pulling out the stopper and carefully pouring the drop of green liquid inside onto the flower.

This drop of green liquid had already appeared prior to his departure from the Spirit Domain Realm. However, after arriving in the Black Wind Sea, he had spent all of his time and efforts on removing the chains that were binding his nascent soul, so he hadn't gotten a chance to use the drop of green liquid prior to this point.

With this vial, he would definitely be able to mature the flower to 10,000 years old, and if time permitted, he was even planning to mature it all the way to 100,000 years old.

After that, he searched through the entire forest and the wooden building without discovering anything else worthy of note, so he returned to his secret chamber through the spatial passageway.

In the instant that he emerged, the entire spatial passageway began to tremble and buzz as it released a vast expanse of white light, then rapidly shrank down before vanishing without a trace.

The white jade badge emerged once again with spiritual light flashing on its surface, and it was hovering in mid-air while giving off faint spatial fluctuations.

Han Li grabbed onto the badge before stowing it away into his storage bracelet.

It seemed that this badge was the key to Ancestral God Luo Meng's final resting place.

Now that the restriction on the badge had been removed, it was essentially a domain treasure, which was certainly going to come in useful in the future.

With that in mind, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed in the secret chamber, then pulled out the jade slip that contained the Earthly Deity Avatar refinement method and carefully studied it.

Time slowly passed by, and the sky gradually darkened. A bright full moon soon appeared in the sky, heralding the arrival of nighttime.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open as he rose to his feet, then appeared in the courtyard outside in a flash.

He looked up at the moon in the sky, then removed the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck before placing it onto the ground.

It didn't take long before rays of white light shone down from the heavens onto the small vial, forming a series of specks of white light. Soon, a huge white halo had appeared around the vial, presenting a dazzling sight to behold.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this.

The phenomenon arising from the Heaven Controlling Vial's absorption of moonlight was far more spectacular than it had been in the Spirit Domain Realm. Back in the Spirit Domain Realm, a drop of green liquid could be produced every two days as long as there was sufficient moonlight. Given the current situation, was it possible for a drop of green liquid to be produced in just a single day?

Han Li was rather excited by this thought, and he swept a hand through the air to release an incantation seal, producing a layer of azure light that encompassed the phenomenon taking place around the Heaven Controlling Vial.

After that, he sat down with his legs crossed beside the small vial and pulled out the same jade slip from before to continue his reading.

The night quickly passed by, and Han Li reopened his eyes before dispelling the layer of azure light with a swipe of his hand. However, as he picked up the Heaven Controlling Vial, a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

The vial's stopper couldn't be removed, which meant that no green liquid had been produced.

"Perhaps it still has to be two days," Han Li murmured to himself with a resigned shrug, then closed his eyes again and continued to study the contents of the jade slip.

Only after day had transitioned into night, the phenomenon arising from the vial's absorption of moonlight appeared again, did he cast the same layer of azure light onto the vial for concealment purposes.

However, the next morning, Han Li discovered, much to his befuddlement and concern, that the vial still couldn't be opened.

Could it be that the world's origin qi in the Immortal Realm isn't even as abundant as it is in the Spirit Domain Realm?

He immediately rejected this absurd thought as soon as it appeared in his mind.

That night, he placed the Heaven Controlling Vial down in the courtyard once again, and this time, he did nothing else but stare directly at the vial for the entire night.

He didn't notice anything amiss while the vial was absorbing moonlight, but the next morning, there was still no green liquid, and Han Li was beginning to grow a little anxious and frustrated.

Aside from his shrewd and careful decision-making, the primary factor that had allowed him to progress to this point in his cultivation journey was the Heaven Controlling Vial. If the Heaven Controlling Vial were to lose its ability to produce that green liquid, then he would be losing his biggest cultivation asset.

As an example of how this was going to impact him, it was going to be extremely difficult for him to get his hands on a 10,000-year-old Soulbirth Flower without the help of the Heaven Controlling Vial.

However, it was still too early to be jumping to conclusions. After all, this was the Immortal Realm, and it was a different place from the Spirit Domain Realm and the Spirit Realm.

Thus, he didn't give up hope and continued trying.

The fourth day passed by without any green liquid produced.

The same applied to the fifth day, and the sixth day...

In the blink of an eye, over 10 days had already passed by.

At night, the Heaven Controlling Vial was still absorbing moonlight as usual, but no green liquid was produced.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li was looking at the Heaven Controlling Vial with a grim expression.

Even back in the Human Realm, it had only taken seven or eight days at most for the vial to produce a drop of green liquid, yet now, twice that amount of time had already passed by, and the vial was still completely empty. This was something that had never happened before, and it left him at a complete loss for what to do.

During this period of time, two possible reasons for this had sprung into his mind, the first of which was that perhaps this was a result of his return to the Immortal Realm.

According to Ma Liang, [1] The True Immortal who had descended into the Spirit Realm, the Heaven Controlling Vial belonged to a major power in the Immortal Realm known as the Nine Origin Daoist Temple.

Now that the vial had returned to the Immortal Realm, it was very much possible that some change that he was unable to detect had taken place within it.

The second possibility was that the vial had been affected by the beam of light that was imbued with the power of laws that it was struck by during Han Li's battle against the one-eyed giant.

Han Li gently exhaled as a calm look returned to his eyes.

The Heaven Controlling Vial was his most important treasure, but that didn't mean that he couldn't live without it.

Furthermore, there was nothing to indicate that the vial's ability to produce green liquid was completely gone. At the very least, it was still absorbing moonlight every night, so he would just have to wait and see.

[1]. For more information on Ma Liang, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2276: Ma Liang.

[Back]

Chapter 96: Re-emergence of the Green Liquid

With that in mind, Han Li temporarily stowed the Heaven Controlling Vial away. His plan was to continue to let it absorb moonlight every night to see if any changes arose.

As for the maturation of the Soulbirth Flower that was required to refine his Earthly Deity Avatar, he would just have to find another way.

Thus, he returned to his secret chamber and made his way over to a wooden table.

At this moment, there was a jade plate sitting on the table, and on the plate was a head-sized blue object. It was none other than the head of the Earthly Deity Avatar that had previously been worshipped in the underwater cavern.

During his previous visit to the underground cavern with Luo Feng, he had borrowed the head for examination.

He picked up the head from the jade plate before placing it onto the ground, then sat down onto his cushion with his legs crossed and began to chant an incantation.

A layer of azure light rose up over his body, then enveloped the blue head and carrying it forward, suspending it in mid-air in front of him.

He then began to make a series of strange gestures with his hands, like the movements used by people from primitive, savage tribes when praying to the heavens. At the same time, he began to chant another complex incantation.

As he was doing all of this, a layer of strange blue light appeared over the surface of the head, and the light was flashing incessantly while an indistinct sound that resembled the collective prayers being uttered by countless people rang out from within.

Specks of blue light then began to emerge in the surrounding area before converging into the head.

These specks of blue light were none other than the power of faith that the head of the Earthly Deity Avatar was gathering from all of its followers all over Dark Veil Island.

As the blue light continued to flash, it began to release an indescribable burst of energy fluctuations, sending ripples that were visible to the naked eye spreading through the air, causing the secret chamber and even the entire courtyard to tremble incessantly.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but his chanting was becoming more urgent.

The blue light emanating from the head flickered a few times before returning to a stable state.

This was a significant amount of power, consisting of all of the power of faith that had accumulated over the course of the past 10,000 years, but unfortunately, Luo Meng had already perished and was unable to control the power gathered within the head of his Earthly Deity Avatar.

Han Li had used the method recorded in the jade slip to try and get a sense of what the power of worship was like in preparation for the cultivation of his own Earthly Deity Avatar in the future.

Right at this moment, Han Li's expression changed slightly, and made a beckoning motion with one hand, upon which a gap opened up in the restriction surrounding the secret chamber to grant passage to a shimmering white talisman.

He drew the talisman into grasp before injecting his spiritual sense into it, then immediately stopped what he was doing, placing the blue head back onto the jade plate on the table before departing from the secret chamber.

In the courtyard outside, Luo Feng was waiting with a respectful expression.

"It's not like you to request an audience with me so urgently, Chief Luo. Could it be that there's been some news about a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art?" Han Li asked.

An elated look appeared on Luo Feng's face as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute toward Han Li. "Indeed, Senior Liu, that's exactly why I've come to see you. Yesterday, I was holding a gathering with some acquaintances of mine, and one of them told me that a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art was going to appear during the next auction to be held on Black Wind Island. I immediately came here to pass this information onto you, Senior Liu."

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, and he nodded in response. "Thank you for your efforts, Chief Luo. If I recall correctly, there are still more than 10 years to go until the auction is scheduled to be held. During this time, I'll have to trouble you to continue to keep an eye out for news regarding Soulbirth Flowers and other high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation arts."

"Rest assured, Senior Liu, you can count on me." Luo Feng nodded in response before cupping his fist in a parting salute.

However, Han Li stopped him before he could leave. "Hold on a second, Chief Luo."

"Is there something else you need, Senior Liu?" Luo Feng asked with an inquisitive expression.

Han Li opened his mouth to say something, but then seemed to decide against it, and in the end, he replied, "No. I just want to let you know that I'll remember everything you've done for me during this time."

Luo Feng was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly waved his hands as he said, "You're far too kind, Senior Liu. I'm just doing what's expected of me."

After that, the two of them chatted for a while longer before Luo Feng departed.

Han Li looked on as Luo Feng faded into the distant sky, then returned to his secret chamber.

He was about to tell Luo Feng about the remains of Luo Meng that he had discovered, but in the end, he decided that this wasn't the right time to do so.

This piece of news had far-reaching implications. In particular, the knowledge of the existence of that 8,000-year-old Soulbirth Flower was very dangerous and could potentially lead to a great deal of trouble, so it was best to withhold this information for a later date.

......

One morning, half a month later.

The sun was just beginning to rise on the horizon, and warm sunlight was shining down from the sky, casting shimmering reflections on the surface of the sea.

The entire Dark Veil Island was basked in a warm glow, and large numbers of island residents and cultivators were gathered in front of the Luo Meng statues on the island in a collective ritual of prayer.

The small courtyard that Han Li was staying in was also illuminated by the bright sunlight.

In the courtyard's secret chamber, Han Li opened his eyes with a thoughtful look on his face.

Through his examination of the Earthly Deity Avatar head left behind by Luo Meng in the past half-month, he had developed some insights on how to gather and convert the power of faith.

In other words, if he could refine an Earthly Deity Avatar of his own and obtain a suitable high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art, then harness and convert the power of faith from the people of Dark Veil Island, there was a 50% to 60% chance that he would be able to free his nascent soul from those mysterious chains and recover his cultivation base.

However, the Heaven Controlling Vial was still unable to produce any green liquid, so it appeared that he would have to pin his hopes for securing a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art and a Soulbirth Flower of sufficient age entirely on the auction to be held on Black Wind Island.

"The auction is scheduled to be held more than 10 years away from now, and that's still too long," Han Li murmured to himself, then left his secret chamber and made his way over to a certain spot in the courtyard in a familiar routine to pick up his Heaven Controlling Vial.

As soon as he picked the vial up from the ground, he immediately raised an eyebrow. It seemed that the vial was significantly heavier than it normally was.

A thought quickly occurred to him, and hurriedly tried to remove the vial's stopper.

This time, he was able to remove the stopper without any effort, and he hurriedly peered into the vial through its opening, upon which an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

A soybean-sized drop of dark green liquid was slowly flowing over the inside of the vial on the bottom.

It had managed to produce green liquid again!

However, this drop of green liquid was slightly different from what Han Li was used to seeing. Its color was much darker, closer to black than green, and it basked the entire inside of the vial in a green glow.

Han Li held the vial in his hand and examined the drop of liquid inside over and over again before his excitement finally subsided.

Even though he was already prepared for the worst, he had still been hoping for the best. After all, if the vial really did permanently lose its ability to produce that precious green liquid, then that would be a heavier loss to him than the loss of any of his other treasures.

Thankfully, it appeared that the crisis had been averted, and he had reached the light at the end of the tunnel.

In total, it had taken around a month to produce that drop of green liquid, which was far longer than the duration of time previously required at any point.

Han Li couldn't help but wonder how effective the drop of green liquid produced over such a long period of time was going to be.

With that in mind, he eagerly returned to his secret chamber, then quickly activated all of the restrictions inside. After that, he flipped a hand over to produce the jade badge, then opened up the spatial passageway to the secret area.

Inside the secret area, everything was still the same as Han Li had left it.

The Soulbirth Flower was still standing on its own in the clearing, cutting a lonesome figure. However, Luo Meng's remains had already been buried in a small grave next to the wooden hut.

Han Li made his way over to the purple flower, then removed the stopper of his Heaven Controlling Vial without any hesitation before pouring the drop of green liquid onto the center of the flower's stamen.

He watched with an unblinking gaze as the drop of green liquid slowly seeped into the Soulbirth Flower's stamen, and he was feeling rather anxious.

This was the same feeling of anticipation that he had felt back when he first conducted an experiment after learning about the effects of the green liquid.

After waiting for a day and a night, Han Li entered the secret area again first thing in the morning, then made his way over to the Soulbirth Flower.

To his surprise, even though only a day had passed by, the Soulbirth Flower was already displaying some astonishing changes.

A faint golden line had appeared on each of its petals along the edges, as if a thin golden border had been embroidered around the flower petals.

According to the jade slip left behind by Luo Meng, this golden line would only appear on the Soulbirth Flower once it reached 10,000 years of age. This Soulbirth Flower was already around 8,000 years old, so that drop of green liquid had to have had a maturation effect of at least 2,000 years.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face after arriving at that conclusion.

Even though the green liquid was far slower to come by in the Immortal Realm, this one drop of green liquid was several dozen times more efficacious than a drop of green liquid produced back in the Spirit Domain Realm.

After that, he spent another month to verify that the Heaven Controlling Vial did indeed take roughly a month to produce a drop of green liquid, and he was greatly relieved to have that notion confirmed.

At the same time, he was also keeping up with his research into the refinement method of an Earthly Deity Avatar, and he would regularly bring out the statue head for careful examination.

Another three months passed by in the blink of an eye, and during this time, Han Li would run through the detailed steps of the Earthly Deity Avatar refinement method in his mind virtually once every single day.

At this point, he had completely memorized the refinement method, and he was confident that he would be able to successfully refine an Earthly Deity Avatar once the Soulbirth Flower reached full maturity and the rest of the refinement materials were gathered.

Furthermore, under the nurturing of the green liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial, a second golden line had appeared on all of the Soulbirth Flower's petals.

By Han Li's estimates, it required roughly a month in the Immortal Realm for each drop of green liquid to be produced, and one drop of the liquid had a maturation effect of roughly 3,000 years.

At this rate, assuming no mishaps, it would only take him about three or four more years to obtain a 100,000-year-old Soulbirth Flower.

Chapter 97: Three Ancestral Gods

Basked under the light of the setting sun, the entire Dark Veil Island resembled a golden leaf that was floating on the black surface of the sea.

On the island, plumes of smoke were rising up from cooking fires in the mortal villages concealed within the forests, and more and more ships had also appeared on the dock.

Several cultivators of the island were patrolling the area, and they were all very pleased by how peaceful it had been since the last attack from the Cold Crystal Race.

The entire Luo Clan had almost been wiped out during the battle that had taken place close to a year ago, and it was all thanks to their "Ancestral God" that the crisis was averted.

At this point, they had no ambitions other than to remain here peacefully and continue to cultivate while protecting this land that they called home.

All of a sudden, the leader of the patrol team stopped in his tracks before casting his gaze toward the distance.

"What's wrong?" The rest of the team also quickly stopped to see what was happening.

All of a sudden, the surface of the sea in the distance began to churn violently, and a series of massive waves that were hundreds of feet tall rose up before crashing toward the island.

Before long, enormous waves had risen up over the surface of the sea as far as the eyes could see, and all of the waves were converging toward the island, while the surrounding earth rumbled and quaked violently.

The group of cultivators was greatly alarmed to see this, and their leader hurriedly pulled out a cylindrical object before tugging on a fuse, upon which a burst of dazzling light erupted into the heavens.

Unbeknownst to them, the sea in a radius of dozens of kilometers around the entire island was churning violently like boiling water, and massive waves were converging toward the island from all directions.

A streak of light quickly flew out of the Luo Clan's main hall before revealing itself to be Luo Feng.

His spiritual sense had already encompassed the entire island and the surrounding sea, and a grim look had appeared on his face.

Several more streaks of light arrived on the scene from different directions before gathering themselves around Luo Feng, and they were the other Body Integration Stage elders of the island.

They had clearly also noticed what was happening around the island, and all of them were greatly alarmed by what they were seeing.

Right at this moment, all of the giant waves crashing toward the island suddenly converged to form an enormous barrier of water, which rose up all around the island before gathering toward its center.

In the blink of an eye, the entire island had been encompassed beneath a gargantuan transparent barrier of water.

Luo Feng and the others were even more alarmed to see this.

"What's going on, Chief? Could it be..."

"We're being attacked, and these enemies are more powerful than any we've ever dealt with before! Inform Elder Liu right away!" Luo Feng instructed with an urgent expression.

The elder that he had delegated the order to immediately sped away toward Han Li's courtyard without any hesitation.

"Activate all of the island's restrictions!" Luo Feng ordered as he turned to the rest of the elders.

A few seconds later, several bursts of light emerged around the main hall as one restriction was activated after another, covering all of the important locations on the island.

Right at this moment, three incredibly bright streaks of light appeared in the distant sky before flying toward the Luo Clan's main hall at an incredible speed.

In what seemed like nothing more than the blink of an eye, the streaks of light arrived on the scene, then receded to reveal three figures.

The trio was led by an imposing man in a suit of engraved white armor with a hollow visor on his face. The visor only covered the top half of his face, and there was a pair of curved tusks protruding out of his mouth, giving him a very fearsome appearance.

Beside the white-armored man was a black-robed elderly man with a dark complexion, and there was faint blue light glowing within his eyes.

The third person to round out the trio was a blue-robed woman who appeared to be in her forties. She still retained most of her elegance from her younger days, but her beauty was marred by a rather unsightly hooked nose.

What was most peculiar was that the three of them all possessed rather wooden and dazed facial features, as if this were a trio of extremely intricately crafted puppets.

Luo Feng's face instantly turned deathly pale at the sight of the trio, and his entire body shuddered as if he had seen a ghost.

The other elders and some of the older cultivators of the island were also displaying similar reactions.

Most of the younger cultivators of the Luo Clan had no idea who these three people were, but the expressions on the faces of their chief and elders told them everything that they needed to know, and they also became extremely uneasy.

Luo Feng exhaled as if he were trying to expel the fear in his heart, then forcibly composed himself as he asked, "Ancestral God Han Qiu, Ancestral God Lu Kun, Ancestral Goddess Gu Gu, to what do I owe this honor?"

All of the younger cultivators of the Luo Family were horrified to hear this.

Most of them weren't aware of who Lu Kun and Gu Gu were as they were Ancestral Gods of islands that were quite far away from Dark Veil Island, but they all knew that Han Qiu was the Ancestral God of the Cold Crystal Race that had invaded their island not long ago, and it could be said that he had already been a sworn enemy of the Luo Clan for tens of thousands of years.

The three Ancestral Gods were each standing over 1,000 feet away from one another, looking down at the horrified residents of Dark Veil Island, and their already wooden and emotionless eyes were looking particularly cold and forbidding.

"Fellow Daoist Han Qiu, are you sure Luo Meng has already met his demise? I heard that the army of your Cold Crystal Race suffered severe losses during its last invasion of the island," the black-robed elderly man said with a hint of doubt in his voice.

"If he's still alive, then why hasn't he appeared at all in the past 10,000 years? As for the defeat that my army suffered during the last invasion, that was only at the hands of another immortal who recently appeared on Dark Veil Island," the white-armored man harrumphed coldly.

"What? Another immortal? You never mentioned this to us at all, Fellow Daoist Han Qiu! Did you intentionally withhold this information from us?" the blue-robed woman accused in a furious voice.

The black-robed elderly man also turned to the white-armored man with his brows furrowed slightly in displeasure.

"Rest assured, fellow daoists. I've already looked into the matter, and it turns out that this new immortal is a lower realm cultivator who's only just ascended into the Immortal Realm. I don't know how he ended up here, but he's not a cause for concern at all. Also, if there were no immortals on this island, then why would I have invited you two to help me?" Han Qiu asked in an indifferent voice.

The blue-robed woman's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, but she still didn't seem to be entirely convinced.

As for the black-robed elderly man, he also remained silent and refused to take a stance on the matter.

Instead of being frustrated by this, a smile appeared on Han Qiu's face as he said, "How about this? If we succeed here, I'm willing to offer each of you an extra Divine Brightnoon Pill in addition to the reward I originally promised you. That'll serve as compensation for my failure to notify you of the situation ahead of time. What do you think?"

"Seeing as you're displaying so much sincerity, it would be rude for Fellow Daoist Gu Gu and me to doubt you any further," the black-robed elderly man chuckled.

The blue-robed woman also nodded in response.

Han Qiu was very pleased to see this. "I'm glad we're all on the same page now. We're only dealing with a recently ascended cultivator from a lower realm, how could he possibly stand against all three of us at once?"

"In that case, let's not delay any further," the black-robed elderly man said as he sprang into action.

With a sweep of his hand, a burst of rumbling rang out from the sea down below, and dozens of enormous pillars rose up. Each pillar was over 100 feet in diameter, and they extended all the way up into the heavens.

The pillars of water than quickly fused as one to form a gargantuan hand that was several thousand feet in size before crashing down upon Luo Feng and the group of elders around him.

Even before the enormous hand arrived, a gust of ferocious wind swept through the area, and all of the restrictions swayed violently as the fierce wind threatened to blow them apart. In fact, several of the restrictions had already disintegrated into specks of light.

Luo Feng's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he wanted to take evasive measures, but it was already too late, and it seemed that his fate was sealed.

Right at this moment, a sharp screeching sound rang out in the distance, and a streak of azure light arrived on the scene like lightning.

The streak of light contained an azure figure, who launched a fist through the air, releasing a burst of tremendous force.

The enormous force unleashed by the punch left a series of ripples that were visible even to the naked eye in its wake, then crashed into the gargantuan hand of seawater with an earth-shattering boom.

The giant hand instantly exploded upon impact, sending massive volumes of water cascading down in all directions.

A burst of ferocious shockwaves erupted through the air in destructive waves, sweeping up fierce hurricanes that either blew all of the rocks and trees in their path into the distance or pulverized them on the spot.

Thankfully, there weren't any mortals nearby, so not many casualties were suffered.

The azure light around the figure in the sky faded to reveal Han Li, and Han Qiu and the elders' expressions changed drastically upon seeing this.

"Esteemed Ancestral God!" everyone on Dark Veil Island cheered in unison in ecstatic voices.

Luo Feng also heaved a sigh of relief, but a hint of concern then immediately appeared on his face.

Han Li was indeed a formidable cultivator, but he was facing three Ancestral Gods at once!

"What business do you have with our Dark Veil Island, fellow daoists?" Han Li asked in a cold voice as he swept his gaze across the trio before him while withdrawing his outstretched fist.

"Senior Liu, these three are all Ancestral Gods from nearby islands. The one in the suit of white armor is Ancestral God Han Qiu of the Cold Crystal Race, the black-robed man beside him is Patriach Lu Kun, and that woman is referred to as Mistress Gu Gu," Luo Feng explained through voice transmission.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, but his expression remained completely unchanged.

"You seem to have told us that this was going to be an easy battle, but I don't think things are quite as you described, Fellow Daoist Han Qiu. This man is clearly a Profound Immortal, is he not?" Lu Kun said via voice transmission as he turned to Han Qiu with a cold look in his eyes, and Mistress Gu Gu's expression had also darkened significantly.

In contrast, Han Qiu was as calm as ever, and he replied via voice transmission, "According to my knowledge, it hasn't even been a year since he ascended to the Immortal Realm. Even if he is a Profound Immortal, there's no way he would've had enough time to convert the magic power in his body into immortal spiritual power, so we have nothing to worry about."

Patriarch Lu Kun and Mistress Gu Gu exchanged a glance upon hearing this, and neither of them said anything.

"You must be Fellow Daoist Liu. I'm sure I don't need to tell you the reason for our visit. Dark Veil Island is a sworn enemy to all three of our islands, and we've come here today with the goal of wiping out the Luo Clan. This has nothing to do with you, so I suggest you do not get involved. If you leave right now, I can let bygones be bygones and forgive the fact that you killed several members of my clan a while ago," Han Qiu said in a cold voice.

Luo Feng's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, and he snuck a rather uneasy glance at Han Li.

The expressions on the faces of all of the other members of the Luo Clan also changed drastically upon hearing this. The older ones among them were alarmed by the situation, while the younger ones were shocked by what Han Qiu had just said.

Han Qiu had referred to their Ancestral God as Fellow Daoist Liu, and that reminded all of the young members of the Luo Clan of a rumor that had been circulating in their clan, stating that their current Ancestral God was actually someone other than Luo Meng.

The elders of their clan had always fervently denied this notion and prohibited the members of the clan from spreading and discussing the rumor, but it seemed that there was a very good chance that the rumor was actually true.

"I'm afraid I'll have to disappoint you. I made a promise to protect Dark Veil Island, and I don't plan to go back on my word. I suggest you turn back before things get out of hand," Han Li replied with a calm expression, completely ignoring Han Qiu's threat.

Chapter 98: Trapped

"You're awfully arrogant for a little lower realm brat who only just ascended to the Immortal Realm!"

Han Qiu's expression darkened slightly upon hearing what Han Li had to say, and white light flashed around his body as he pointed a finger forward to conjure up a cloud of white mist.

The cloud of mist churned slightly before folding in on itself to form a white ice spike that was several dozen feet in length.

The ice spike was glowing with dazzling white radiance, and it quickly split up into two, then two into four, then four into eight...

In the blink of an eye, countless white ice spikes had emerged, filling virtually the entire sky before hurtling directly toward Han Li in a ferocious barrage.

The ice spikes released a burst of glacial energy as they sped through the air, causing the air temperature in the area to plummet drastically. In fact, the temperatures had dropped so sharply that many icicles had already appeared in the air, and it seemed that the entire area was on the verge of being frozen solid.

Almost at the exact same moment, Patriarch Lu Kun and Mistress Gu Gu also sprang into action.

Patriarch Lu Kun's entire body was enveloped by a layer of blue light as he spread a hand open. Specks of blue light appeared on his palm, then descended through the air before vanishing into the sea down below.

The surface of the sea immediately began to churn violently as an enormous vortex with specks of blue light interspersed throughout appeared, and the vortex was rapidly expanding amid a burst of rumbling that resembled the sound of countless pounding horse hooves.

Meanwhile, Mistress Gu Gu closed her eyes as she made a hand seal, and black light flashed around her as a wisp of black mist rose up from her body before vanishing into one of the clouds up above.

The cloud instantly turned as black as ink, and it began to tumble and churn incessantly while releasing a burst of mysterious fluctuations that attracted all of the water vapor in the area within a radius of hundreds of kilometers, causing the cloud to expand rapidly.

In response, Han Li had already risen up into the air with azure light glowing all around him, directly facing the oncoming barrage of ice spikes as he sped toward Han Qiu's trio.

At the same time, seven specks of starlight appeared on his chest and abdomen, and a string of cracks and pops rang out as his body swelled markedly in stature before he threw a punch through the air.

A burst of immense power erupted forth in a frenzy, causing the entire space to tremble violently before exploding with tremendous force.

Countless white ripples that were visible to the naked eye erupted in all directions from Han Li's fist, and all of the ice spikes that came into contact with the white ripples instantly exploded into countless ice crystals before being blown away.

Han Qiu's expression remained completely unchanged upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal before releasing several incantation seals in quick succession.

All of the shattered ice crystals exploded once again at his behest, forming an enormous cloud of glacial mist that instantly encompassed a large area in a radius of several thousand feet around Han Li while releasing a burst of strong law fluctuations.

Han Li felt as if he had been plunged into a completely white and featureless world, and he immediately swept a sleeve through the air, sweeping up a gust of fierce wind that blew through the surrounding area.

However, the white mist around him only churned slightly in the face of the fierce wind, but didn't scatter or dissipate at all.

Han Li made no further attempt to blow the mist away, choosing to attempt to rush out of the mist instead.

The surrounding mist immediately clung to his body as if it were a living creature, but it wasn't cold enough to be of any concern to Han Li.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li flew out of the cloud of white mist, and bright azure light erupted from his body as he raised an arm to deliver a powerful blow against Han Qiu's trio.

However, a hint of surprise then appeared on his face as he discovered that there was nothing in front of him, and Han Qiu's trio seemed to have evaporated into thin air.

He immediately stopped cold in his tracks before frantically inspecting his surroundings, only to find that the three Ancestral Gods were standing several thousand feet away.

After sweeping his gaze across the surrounding area, Han Li realized what had happened.

It wasn't that Han Qiu's trio had suddenly moved away from where they had originally been standing. Instead, his senses had been disrupted as he was flying through the mist, and as a result, he had inadvertently flown in the wrong direction and emerged from a different section of the cloud of mist from what he had intended.

Immediately thereafter, his brows furrowed slightly as he looked down to discover that there were wisps of white mist that were as thin as strands of hair swirling around his legs and lower abdomen. Bursts of glacial energy were seeping into his body from the mist, gradually numbing his body and making him feel as if he were truly being frozen solid.

Han Li immediately reacted to the situation, conjuring up the semi-transparent True Extreme Membrane over his body to keep out the white mist and prevent it from affecting him any further.

This seemed like a lengthy process, but in reality, the entire sequence had taken place in the blink of an eye.

Before he had a chance to do anything else, a gigantic being emerged from the vortex of seawater down below with a loud splash.

This was a blue giant that was several hundred feet tall, and its body seemed to consist entirely of seawater. It was quite hideous in appearance, with a disproportionately large head compared with the rest of its body, and its limbs also varied in length and thickness, as if it had been thrown together haphazardly without any regard for symmetry and proportions.

The blue water giant rose up into the air, positioning itself directly in Han Li's way as it swatted a massive blue hand directly at him.

Even before the giant hand arrived, a gust of ferocious wind swept through the air, causing the space in its wake to blur and warp, and even Han Li couldn't help but sway unsteadily from the immense wind pressure.

However, Han Li was able to quickly steady himself, then threw a vicious punch in retaliation without taking any evasive measures.

A burst of tremendous force erupted through the air, causing the space up ahead to twist and warp amid a deafening boom.

Countless white ripples emerged once again, then came together to form an enormous white fist projections that struck the blue giant before its attack managed to reach Han Li.

A series of ripples instantly emerged on the section of the giant's body that was struck by the fist projection, forming a swirling vortex.

To Han Li's astonishment, the white fist projection vanished into the vortex, then emerged on the other side of the giant's body before continuing onward and striking nothing but empty air, leaving its target completely unscathed.

Immediately thereafter, the vortex on the blue giant's body sealed over in the blink of an eye, and at this point, its massive blue palm had also reached Han Li.

It was too late for Han Li to dodge the attack, and he was sent flying as if he had been struck by an asteroid, tumbling through the air over a huge distance.

However, he was quickly able to steady himself, and even though his face had paled slightly, he hadn't been harmed by the attack.

Right at this moment, the blue giant came charging toward him again.

"It's only been less than 30,000 years since we last met, but you've made significant strides in your control over this Immaterial Water Giant conjured up by your gentle water laws. This thing is the perfect counter to a Profound Immortal like him!" Han Qiu praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Han Qiu. You've also made some good progress in your glacial ice laws." Despite Patriarch Lu Kun's humble response, the proud look in his eyes betrayed his true emotions.

"I can't even begin to compare with you when it comes to mastery over the power of laws, Fellow Daoist Lu Kun. Now that we've both shown what we're capable of, it's Fellow Daoist Gu Gu turn to show us what she's capable of," Han Qiu chuckled.

While Han Li was being occupied by Han Qiu and Lu Kun, the dark cloud in the sky had already swelled to several dozen kilometers in size, and there were bolts of silver lightning flashing incessantly within it.

Right at this moment, Mistress Gu Gu swept a hand through the air to release an incantation seal, and the entire cloud churned violently amid a flash of lightning.

All of a sudden, a torrential downpour came raining down from the heavens.

The rain was extremely heavy, and what was very strange was that the droplets of rain were connected together, forming strings of rain that cascaded down from above.

Han Li had only just evaded a punch from the blue giant, and he looked up as his brows furrowed slightly.

The strings of rain came falling down, and as soon as they made contact with his body, they immediately began to wrap around him like lengths of rope.

In the blink of an eye, his body had already been bound by several hundred strings of rain.

Silver light surged over the True Extreme Membrane on his skin as he raised his arms in a powerful motion, snapping all of the strings of rain around his body amid a string of dull thuds.

These strings of rain were extremely flexible and supple, and a few dozen or several hundred of them posed no threat to him, but if he were to be bound by thousands or tens of thousands of them, then the consequences would be catastrophic!

Han Li's expression darkened significantly as bright azure light erupted all over his body, and he attempted to fly out of the area encompassed under the dark cloud.

However, the blue giant instantly got in his way, sending its massive palms crashing down upon him.

Han Li thrust his fists through the air in retaliation, and two bursts of tremendous force struck the giant's palms, leaving a pair of white marks in the space in their wake.

Blue light flashed from the giant's palms, and the two bursts of power passed through without being able to inflict any damage upon the giant.

Meanwhile, the giant's palms continued to come crashing down without slowing in the slightest.

Han Li let loose a frustrated roar as he dodged to the side, and in the span of just a few seconds, his body had been bound by several hundred strings of rain once again.

As a result, his movements had become far slower than before, but he was still just barely able to evade the giant's palm strikes.

All of a sudden, the blue giant opened its cavernous mouth, and around a dozen millstone-sized balls of blue water came flying out from within. The balls of water were shimmering with blue light while giving off powerful energy fluctuations as they hurtled directly toward Han Li.

At the same time, it swiveled around and charged toward Han Li once again.

Han Li was completely preoccupied with this unkillable giant, so he was unable to deal with the strings of rain that were wrapping themselves around his body, and his movements became more and more restricted.

However, if one were to look closely here, they would notice that the light radiating from the bodies of the three Ancestral Gods had also dimmed significantly, and this was particularly true for Gu Gu and Lu Kun.

A few seconds later, a translucent blue cocoon had appeared in the air, and Han Li's figure could just barely be made out through it. At this point, he was virtually completely immobilized.

The blue giant had also ceased its attacks, and it was hovering next to the blue cocoon in a completely skilled manner.

"Thank you for your hard work, fellow daoists. You can leave the rest to me now!"

A hint of elation flashed through Han Qiu's eyes as he let loose a low cry, and countless white runes emerged from his body amid a flash of white light, releasing a burst of incredibly powerful law fluctuations that fused into the white mist.

At the same time, the white light radiating from his body was rapidly dimming at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

The white mist immediately began to churn violently as it surged toward Han Li, inundating Han Li along with the blue cocoon around him to form a massive ball of white mist, within which a burst of glacial law fluctuations was swirling incessantly.

Shortly thereafter, the white mist dissipated to reveal a white ball of ice that was several hundred feet in diameter, with Han Li's body completely frozen within it.

Chapter 99: Admission of Identity

Looking at the immobilized figure within the massive ball of ice, both Patriarch Lu Kun and Mistress Gu Gu heaved an internal sigh of relief.

Even though the battle had only lasted less than 20 seconds, the incredible strength displayed by Han Li had been downright astonishing to them. Thankfully, with their combined efforts, they were finally able to trap him.

In contrast, the members of the Luo Clan on Dark Veil Island were greatly alarmed to see this, and horrified expressions had appeared on most of their faces.

"Senior Liu!" Luo Feng let loose a despairing cry, and a hopeless look appeared on his face.

This was what he had been most afraid of.

Han Li was the only one that their Luo Clan could rely on, and now that he had fallen, he didn't even dare to imagine what was going to become of the Luo Clan.

"I must thank you again for your efforts, fellow daoists. I'll admit that I didn't anticipate for this man to be able to oppose our powers of laws with his brute strength alone. If it weren't for your assistance, I would've been in a great deal of trouble here," Han Qiu said with a pleased smile.

"I suggest you put an end to this right now. The longer you delay, the more potential for unforeseen circumstances to arise," Mistress Gu Gu said.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Gu Gu."

A cold gleam flashed through Han Qiu's eyes as he spoke, and a burst of white light appeared in one of his hands as he casually swiped it in the direction of the ball of ice up ahead.

A burst of white light flashed through the air, and a crescent-shaped white blade with a dragon engraved onto its surface appeared alongside a burst of law fluctuations.

The white blade shuddered as it sped through the air as a streak of white light, cutting into the ball of ice in a flash before hurtling directly toward Han Li without slowing down in the slightest.

However, right at this moment, an unexpected turn of events began to unfold.

Han Li was previously completely immobilized within the ball of ice, but all of a sudden, his eyes moved ever so slightly.

Immediately thereafter, countless bursts of golden light erupted from his body, illuminating the entire ball of ice, giving it the appearance of a scintillating golden sun that was hanging in the sky.

A loud crack rang out, and the entire ball of ice shuddered as a series of large cracks appeared on its surface, following which the entire ball of ice exploded violently, sending countless chunks of ice flying in all directions alongside a cloud of glacial mist.

A giant golden ape that was over 300 feet tall sprang out from within, and its entire body was glowing with dazzling golden radiance, while the crescent-shaped white blade had been caught in its furry grasp.

The white blade was trembling violently as it attempted to break free by slicing viciously into the giant ape's palm, sending sparks flying in all directions, but it wasn't even able to leave the slightest mark on the True Extreme Membrane on the surface of the ape's palm.

The trio of Ancestral Gods were greatly alarmed by this abrupt turn of events, and all of the members of the Luo Clan were also completely rooted to the spot.

However, unlike everyone else, there was a hint of elation flashing through Luo Feng's eyes.

The giant golden ape let loose a thunderous, beastly roar, then closed its fingers around the crescent-shaped white blade with all its might.

A dull thump rang out as the blade was pulverized in its grasp, having been crushed into a pile of translucent powder.

Han Qiu shuddered violently, and his aura instantly waned significantly in the wake of the destruction of his bonded treasure.

Mistress Gu Gu and Patriarch Lu Kun exchanged a glance, and both of them could see their own astonishment mirrored in one another's eyes.

Meanwhile, the blue water giant sprang into action once again, charging toward the giant golden ape as it lashed out with its fists.

Bright blue light erupted from its fists as a pair of massive blue fist projections were launched through the air, causing the space in its wake to shudder violently.

Instead of retaliating with its own fists, the giant golden ape took a deep breath, causing its chest to swell appreciably before it opened its mouth to let loose an explosive roar.

A burst of transparent soundwaves swept through the air, causing the space in its wake to twist and warp violently, creating a series of ripples that were visible to the naked eye and even a clusters of black spatial rifts.

In the instant that the pair of blue fist projections came into contact with the burst of soundwaves, the former was instantly destroyed.

In the next instant, the transparent soundwaves swept over the blue water giant's entire body, causing it tremble and warp violently.

Blue light began to flash erratically all over its body, and large pillars of blue light were erupting out of its body before spraying in all directions.

Patriarch Lu Kun's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he made a rapid string of hand seals, releasing several bursts of blue light that vanished into the giant's body.

However, his efforts appeared to be completely futile, and the water giant's condition was worsening by the second. Finally, a loud thump rang out as the giant exploded into countless tiny droplets of water, which then quickly disintegrated into water vapor in the face of the destructive soundwaves.

Patriarch Lu Kun immediately gave a muffled groan as the blue light radiating from his body dimmed significantly.

After letting loose that thunderous roar, the giant golden ape sprang up toward the dark cloud up above, then thrust its arm upward violently as scintillating golden light erupted from its fist.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a mountainous golden fist projection erupted into the heavens before plunging straight into the dark cloud, releasing a burst of indescribably powerful force to form a series of golden hurricanes that tore through the air in all directions.

Mistress Gu Gu was greatly alarmed to see this, but it was too late for her to do anything.

A string of loud cracks and pops rang out as the dark cloud in the sky was brutally torn apart before exploding violently, quickly disintegrating into nothingness.

Mistress Gu Gu let loose a muffled groan as she stumbled back a step, and her aura fluctuated in an unstable manner while the black light radiating from her body also dimmed significantly.

After laying waste to the dark cloud, the giant golden ape swept its gaze over the three Ancestral Gods before settling its attention on Han Qiu, upon which a burst of cold killing intent appeared in its eyes.

Immediately thereafter, its enormous body transformed into a golden shadow as it pounced on the trio of Ancestral Gods.

Whether it was intentional or not, both Patriarch Lu Kun and Mistress Gu Gu sprang away in opposite directions to distance themselves from Han Qiu.

Despite this, the giant golden ape didn't alter its trajectory in the slightest. Instead, it sped up even further as it continued on its original course.

Han Qiu made a rapid string of hand seals while hurriedly staging a retreat, and dazzling white light erupted from his body, forming a white light barrier that enveloped him from head to toe.

Bursts of powerful law fluctuations emanated from the white light barrier, which was also releasing countless white runes that drifted through the air.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a translucent white ice crystal, which began to revolve on the spot, and all of the white runes instantly converged toward it. In the blink of an eye, the combination of the ice crystal and the white runes transformed into a white ice dragon that was over 100 feet in length before launching itself at the oncoming golden ape.

The giant golden ape gave a cold harrumph as it thrust its fist through the air, and a ball of dazzling golden light erupted from its fist amid a burst of dull rumbling. The ball of golden light then transformed into a mountainous golden fist projection in a flash as it continued to hurtle toward the white ice dragon.

The ice dragon opened its mouth to release a thick pillar of white light in retaliation, and waves of white glacial qi swept through the air in all directions in a frenzy, leaving large patches of frost in their wake.

The fist projection clashed with the pillar of light with an earth-shattering boom, and the latter was instantly destroyed.

The golden fist projection was only slowed down slightly before crashing into the white ice dragon's body.

The ice dragon also met the same fate as the pillar of light, exploding into countless ice crystals, while a burst of powerful shockwaves erupted into the heavens.

At this point, the layer of white light around Han Qiu's body was only as thin as a sheet of paper, and he was sent flying back by the devastating shockwaves, hurtling through the sky like an asteroid before crashing into the sea down below with an enormous splash.

The giant golden ape was just about to continue to give chase when a male voice suddenly rang out up above.

"Hold on, Fellow Daoist Liu! Let's be civilized!"

The giant golden ape stopped in its tracks as it raised its head to look up.

Patriarch Lu Kun and Mistress Gu Gu were approaching it, and they stopped a short distance away.

"Your powers are truly incredible, Fellow Daoist Liu. I am genuinely in awe!" Patriarch Lu Kun said with a friendly smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Given your incredible power, we're willing to concede ownership of Dark Veil Island to you. This battle is entirely the result of a misunderstanding, and it wouldn't do any of us any good to continue, so why don't we stop here?" Mistress Gu Gu suggested.

The giant golden ape's eyes narrowed slightly as a hint of blue light flashed through its pupils, and it remained silent as its brows furrowed slightly.

All of a sudden, Han Qiu flew out of the sea in the distance with a loud splash, and his aura was severely diminished, indicating that he had suffered severe injuries.

"Now that you've had a taste of Fellow Daoist Liu's power, I'm sure you're no longer opposed to granting him control of Dark Veil Island, right, Fellow Daoist Han?" Patriarch Lu Kun asked as he turned to Han Qiu.

Han Qiu was silent for a moment before suddenly bursting into laughter. "Indeed, I am truly in awe and admiration of your powers, Fellow Daoist Liu. I have no objections if you wish to take over Dark Veil Island."

The giant golden ape's gaze lingered on Han Qiu for a while longer before it quickly reverted back into its human form amid a flash of golden light.

"I already declared earlier that I have no intention of battling any of you. If you wish to leave, then please go ahead," Han Li said with a faint smile.

With that, the tension in the air was instantly alleviated significantly.

"Fellow Daoist Liu, this may have been a rough introduction, but it's an introduction nonetheless, and I'm pleased to have made your acquaintance. All of the powers in the Black Wind Sea are constantly at war with one another, so given how close our islands are, we need to rely on one another to ward off external enemies. Now that you've taken over Dark Veil Island, you should come and visit us when you get the chance," Patriarch Lu Kun said with a faint smile.

"Indeed. Ancestral Gods like us have no powerful backers or mentors, so we can only cultivate on our own, and it would be invaluable for us to exchange our cultivation insights and experiences with one another. In light of that, all of us gather together every once in a while to discuss cultivation, or exchange resources with each other.

“Given the lofty heights that you've already reached at such a young age, there's a very good chance that you'll be able to advance to the Golden Immortal Stage in the future, so it's very important that you learn more about the powers of laws," Han Qiu chimed in with a nod, and there was a slightly sycophantic tone to his voice as he spoke.

"I'll be sure to visit all of you if I have some spare time in the future," Han Li replied with a nod.

Chapter 100: Cow Head Mask

"Apologies once again for the intrusion, Fellow Daoist Liu. I'll be taking my leave now," Mistress Gu Gu said, then sped away into the distance as a black shadow.

"Farewell for now, Fellow Daoist Liu!" Patriarch Lu Kun cupped his fist toward Han Li and Han Qiu in a parting salute, then also departed.

Thus, Han Qiu was the only one left standing in front of Han Li, and he showed no intention of leaving.

"Is there something else I can help you with, Fellow Daoist Han?" Han Li asked as a cold tone crept into his voice.

"I would also like to apologize for the intrusion, Fellow Daoist Liu," Han Qiu said as he cupped his fist toward Han Li in an apologetic salute.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

After a brief hesitation, Han Qiu continued, "I do indeed have something that I wish to discuss with you, Fellow Daoist Liu."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted in a calm voice.

"According to my knowledge, Fellow Daoist Luo Meng was able to come into possession of a Soulbirth Flower some time ago, and I'm assuming that the flower is now in your possession. Seeing as you're pursuing the path of the Profound Immortal, I'm sure you have no use for such a flower. As such, would you be able to give it to me? Rest assured, I'll be sure to provide you with satisfactory compensation," Han Qiu said as a hopeful look appeared on his face.

"Sorry to disappoint you, but I've found no such flower on the island," Han Li replied with no change in his expression.

Han Qiu's smile immediately stiffened, and his expression darkened ever so slightly.

"I see. In that case, I'll be taking my leave now," Han Qiu said with a parting nod, then flew away as a streak of white light, vanishing into the distant sky in the blink of an eye.

Han Li looked on as Han Qiu departed, and only after he had vanished out of sight did he descend back onto Dark Veil Island.

At some point, the barrier of water above the island had disappeared, and the sea around the island had returned to its former peaceful state, as if nothing had ever happened.

"Senior Liu!"

Luo Feng and Several Body Integration cultivators of the Luo Clan immediately gathered around Han Li with ecstatic expressions, and they were surrounded by many more cultivators at or below the Spatial Tempering Stage.

"We cannot thank you enough, Senior. You have saved our Luo Clan from certain destruction," Luo Feng said with a serious expression, then fell to his knees and kowtowed to Han Li with the utmost respect and reverence.

"Thank you, Senior Liu!"

All of the other members of the Luo Clan also followed suit.

"No need to thank me, Chief Luo. I promised to protect Dark Veil Island, so this is only to be expected of me," Han Li said.

Judging from how these people were no longer referring to him as their Ancestral God, Luo Feng had to have already explained his identity to them.

This was a good thing. After all, this wasn't something that could've been kept a secret for very long anyway.

Luo Feng and the others still wanted to shower Han Li with more words of praise and gratitude, but Han Li excused himself by proclaiming that he needed to rest after that intense battle, and he returned to his courtyard.

……

Several months passed by in a flash.

Han Li was standing beside the wooden hut in the secret area, inspecting the Soulbirth Flower as he reached out to gently stroke one of its petals.

Yet another golden stripe had appeared on the Soulbirth Flower's petals, amounting to a total of three stripes.

At over 30,000 years of age, a golden hue was beginning to peek through the flower's purple petals, giving it a regal aura.

Han Li's gaze was settled on the flower, but he was pondering the battle that he had fought against the Earthly Deity Avatars of the three Ancestral Gods several months ago.

Even though the three Earthly Deity Avatars were ultimately defeated, they had given Han Li more of an insight into the powers of laws, and he became even more interested in attaining this power for himself.

Moments later, he slowly withdrew his hand and stood up straight again.

Right as he was about to turn away, he noticed a flash of light appear in the small wooden hut next to Luo Meng's grave out of the corners of his eyes, following which an object flew out from within.

He turned to discover that it was the head of Luo Meng's statue that had emerged from the wooden hut, and it was hovering in mid-air while glowing with blue light.

Previously, whenever he had tried to observe the power of faith through the statue head, some type of phenomenon would always be triggered, with the most intense occasion causing such severe tremors that the walls around the courtyard he was staying in had been cracked.

In order to avoid further similar occurrences in the future, he had renovated the wooden hut in the secret area, and during the past month, he had spent the majority of his time here, aside from at night, when he was allowing his Heaven Controlling Vial to absorb moonlight.

As a result, the statue head had naturally also been moved into this secret area.

Previously, as long as he didn't try to observe the power of faith within the head using the method contained within the jade slip, the head would remain as still as an inanimate object, and this was the first time that it had flown out on its own.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he approached the head for a closer examination, but a sense of foreboding suddenly welled up in his heart, and he reflexively sprang back to take evasive measures.

All of a sudden, a burst of blue light exploded violently in the air, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping in all directions.

Han Li caught a glance of the Soulbirth Flower of the corners of his eyes, and he immediately rushed over to the flower to shield it from the explosion.

He crossed his arms in front of himself, then drew upon all of his magic power to conjure up an azure light barrier that kept the shockwaves at bay.

The shockwaves crashed into the azure light barrier one after another, then swept away toward either direction, and large plumes of dust and debris were thrown up in the surrounding forest as dozens of trees were felled in an instant.

The newly renovated wooden hut was unable to withstand the shockwaves, and it collapsed once again into an even more dilapidated state than before.

More shockwaves continued to erupt from the statue head for quite some time before gradually receding, and the blue light glowing from within it also faded.

Right at this moment, a cow head mask that was roughly the size of a human head flew out of the statue head without any warning before rushing directly at Han Li.

The entire mask was blue in color, and it was riddled with a type of strange pattern that Han Li had never seen before. Bursts of peculiar fluctuations were emanating incessantly out of the mask, and there was a pair of strange symbols situated at the glabella of the mask, seemingly spelling out the numbers "1" and "5".

Han Li reflexively lashed out with his fist to attack the mask, but the mask immediately took on an insubstantial form, allowing Han Li's fist and arm to pass directly through it as it advanced forward to hover in front of the Soulbirth Flower.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then turned around to see bursts of light blue ripples emerging from the cow mask amid a flash of blue light.

Immediately thereafter, the stiff and rigid-looking lines of the mask's mouth began to move, and it declared, "Wyrm 15, it's already been several years since you last completed a mission for the guild, and your last offering has also expired.

“You must travel to Sea Fig Island to meet up with Wyrm 3 within a month, and he'll take you to complete this mission. If you do not arrive by the deadline, you will be evicted from the Transient Guild and be forced to bear all the consequences."

After the voice trailed off, the fluctuations emanating from the mask disappeared, but it didn't fall to the ground. Instead, it continued to hover in mid-air while flashing faintly with blue light.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he suddenly cast a cold gaze toward the Soulbirth Flower.

All of a sudden, he gave a cold harrumph as he made a strange hand seal, then abruptly reached out and made a grabbing motion. A translucent thread instantly shot out of his fingertip, then pierced straight into the stamen of the Soulbirth Flower.

As his hand was slowly drawn back, the translucent thread quivered as it pulled a frantically writhing black entity out of the Soulbirth Flower.

As soon as the black entity left the stamen of the flower, it began to twist and write violently, revealing itself to be a miniature black figure that was only several inches in size.

The miniature black figure bore a strong resemblance to Luo Meng's statues, and Han Li could tell that its aura was also identical to that of the residual aura in the statue head.

"You're Luo Meng!" Han Li murmured to himself in a surprised voice.

A panicked look appeared on the miniature black figure's face, and its mouth was opening and closing incessantly, but it wasn't able to make any sound. At the same time, wisps of black qi were scattering into the air from its body, and it looked as if it were about to disintegrate.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

This miniature black figure seemed to have been formed by only by a wisp of the aura of Luo Meng's soul. It wasn't actually his soul, and it couldn't even be counted as a soul fragment. Given its current state, it wasn't going to take long before it would disintegrate.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li made a quick series of hand seals, releasing several azure incantation seals that vanished straight into the miniature black figure.

Azure light immediately flashed over its body, and an azure light barrier appeared to envelop the entire miniature black figure like a membrane.

The escaping black qi was impeded by the membrane and unable to dissipate any further, thereby stabilizing the miniature black figure.

Its lips began to move once again, and a hoarse and extremely faint voice rang out from within its body. "Thank you, Fellow Daoist..."

"Don't be in a rush to thank me. What are your intentions hiding a wisp of your soul's aura in the Soulbirth Flower?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

"You are not from our tribe... yet you know my name and were willing to help me stabilize my soul, so I presume you are not an enemy of our Dark Veil Island... Why is it that you've appeared in this secret area of mine?" Instead of answering Han Li's question, the miniature black figure responded with a question of its own.

"I just so happened to be passing through and saved your Dark Veil Island from an invasion from the Cold Crystal Race, and I've continued to stay on the island due to various reasons that I won't explain to you," Han Li replied in a truthful manner.

Luo Meng was silent for a moment, then said, "I see, so our island owes you a great favor... May I ask... where Luo Feng is right now?"

"Regardless of whether you believe what I'm saying or not, answer my questions first, and then we'll talk about other things," Han Li ordered in a cold voice.

Chapter 101: The Transient Guild

Luo Meng shuddered slightly at the sight of the change in Han Li's demeanor, and he sighed, "Please don't be angry, Fellow Daoist. Truth be told... even I'm not very sure of how this happened myself...

“All I remember is that my injuries had become too severe, and I fell unconscious after I left behind my final words... Only several days ago did I suddenly awaken and realize that I had already perished, with only this wisp of my soul's aura remaining in this Soulbirth Flower..."

"If you already woke up several days ago, then why didn't you reveal yourself? Why did you continue to hide in this Soulbirth Flower?" Han Li asked.

"Well... The first reason for this is that I'm too weak in my current form, and I ran the risk of instantly disintegrating out of existence if I left the Soulbirth Flower. As for the second reason... that's because I was wary of your existence," Luo Meng replied in a rather hesitant voice.

"You recognize me?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Truth be told... After I awakened, I was able to use the feeble connection I still had with the statues on the island to see what's recently been happening on the island during my descendants' prayer sessions... Hence, I did find out about the efforts you made to protect our Dark Veil Island," Luo Meng replied after a brief hesitation.

Han Li fell silent as he watched the miniature black figure before him with a cold expression.

Judging from the circumstances, Luo Meng was most likely telling the truth. Following his demise, some of his soul's aura was somehow drawn into the Soulbirth Flower, which had the ability to give rise to souls. After that, the wisp of soul's aura became one with the flower, and that was how it had managed to escape Han Li's detection.

Now that the flower had been matured to a certain extent, its soul-gathering ability had been enhanced, thereby allowing this wisp of soul aura to form a temporary soul fragment. Even though the temporary soul fragment had been bolstered by Han Li's incantation seals, judging from its stuttering speech, it most likely wasn't going to be able to maintain this form for much longer.

Luo Meng was growing a little uneasy in the face of Han Li's silence, and he said in a sheepish voice, "Please forgive me for remaining hidden and trying to fool you, Fellow Daoist... I'm aware that you also wish to pursue the path of the Earth Immortal... so I harbor no delusions that you may help me regain a physical body. As long as you promise me to continue protecting my people, I'm willing to answer all of your questions to the best of my abilities."

"Rest assured, I'm somewhat indebted to your Luo Clan, so I will protect your people as long as the circumstances permit me to do so," Han Li replied.

"I believe you, Fellow Daoist Liu. If you have any questions, then go ahead and ask them. I'll be sure to tell you everything that I know," Luo Meng said with a firm nod.

"First, let's talk about the Transient Guild that this mask just mentioned. What is that all about?" Han Li asked as he took a glance at the cow mask, which was still suspended in mid-air.

"Let's see, how do I put this... The Transient Guild is a very mysterious organization, so I don't know too much about it, and I only joined the organization by chance... However, it was all thanks to this guild that I was able to achieve everything that I went on to achieve..." Luo Meng replied after a brief hesitation.

"Oh? Would you care to elaborate?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"In the past, my cultivation aptitude was quite ordinary. Even though I encountered some opportunities and stumbled my way to the Body Integration Stage, I was perpetually stumped by a cultivation bottleneck and had no hope of further progression...

“After that, I received all types of cultivation resources and guidance in cultivation arts from the Transient Guild, and as a result, I was able to make rapid progress in my cultivation, breaking through to the Grand Ascension Stage before ascending to immortality...

“After that, I continued to cultivate for countless years without being able to manifest any powers of laws, and it was only through the help of the guild again that I was able to become an Earthly Immortal."

"Surely the Transient Guild wouldn't have just provided you with all this assistance free of charge," Han Li said as he raised an eyebrow.

"Of course not... After I became an immortal, I had to return all of the cultivation resources that I used up. For that, I had to serve the Transient Guild for tens of thousands of years without compensation before I was finally able to return my debt... However, after that, I chose to stay in the guild so that I could retain my membership status," Luo Meng explained.

"Is there some type of benefit that you can derive from being a member of the guild even after you become an immortal?" Han Li asked.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Liu. The Transient Guild is a far more mysterious and powerful organization than the average person can even begin to fathom... On top of that, the guild champions a policy of equality, where anyone can exchange for anything with one another... After I sustained my severe injuries 10,000 years ago, I was able to exchange for a Soulbirth Flower from the guild in order to reform an Earthly Deity Avatar," Luo Meng explained.

"That's quite interesting," Han Li mused as he stroked his chin in contemplation.

"It's no exaggeration to say that you can obtain virtually anything you want from the Transient Guild as long as you can afford it... You can even recruit powerful allies from the guild to help you kill enemies." Luo Meng seemed to have recalled some past memories, and a hint of excitement had crept into his voice.

"Surely all things must be balanced. If there are so many benefits to staying in the Transient Guild, then I'm sure you have to pay a hefty price to remain in the guild, right?" Han Li asked.

"Indeed... The Transient Guild isn't an organization that you can remain in as you please. The guild has very strict rules, and at the lower levels, in order to maintain membership status, one has to either periodically offer up large quantities of resources to the guild... or complete missions released by the higher-ups...

“Otherwise, not only will you be evicted from the guild, you'll also have to pay an unimaginable price..." Luo Meng replied with a wry smile.

"What kind of missions do they release?" Han Li asked as a hint of intrigue appeared in his eyes.

"I'm a bit embarrassed to admit this, but I've actually only gone on one mission released by the guild... and it was extremely perilous. It was during that mission that my Earthly Deity Avatar was destroyed while shielding me from a fatal blow, leaving only its head behind. My main body was also severely wounded, but I was fortunate enough to have been able to escape with my life," Luo Meng replied.

"You must've gone into seclusion in this secret area to recover while nurturing this Soulbirth Flower after that mission, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right... It was also from that point that I never participated in any of the guild's other missions... During the following several thousand years, I had always maintained my membership status in the guild by scraping together resources for offerings..." Luo Meng replied.

"In that case, how did you perish in the end? Even if your Earthly Deity Avatar was completely destroyed, surely that wouldn't pose any threat to your life. Besides, the head of your Earthly Deity Avatar still remains intact, so you can continue to harness the power of faith," Han Li said in a puzzled voice.

Luo Meng fell silent upon hearing this, seemingly lost in past memories.

Only after a long while did he shake his head as he replied in a forlorn voice, "I had already recovered from my injuries, but due to the destruction of my avatar, the power of laws that I was able to wield was very limited. Hence, I hid in this secret area for over 8,000 years... But all of a sudden, an enemy of mine somehow managed to track me down.

“As a result, I had no choice but to emerge from this secret area and face him with my true body. In the end, I was able to kill him, but I had also sustained severe injuries during the battle... After that, I was able to return to this secret area, but my old injuries were compounded by new ones, and I was unable to recover..."

"If the missions are so dangerous, surely the guild wouldn't just send anyone to complete them. Could it be that all low-level members of the Transient Guild are beings of the same caliber as Ancestral Gods like yourself?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'm afraid I don't know that..." Luo Meng replied with a shake of his head.

"You may not have any acquaintances in the guild, but seeing as you've gone on a mission, surely you've met some of the guild's other members," Han Li said.

"Allow me to explain, Fellow Daoists... The members of the Transient Guild will only meet while on missions, and no contact is made outside of that... On top of that, during gatherings of guild members, everyone must wear special masks handed down by the guild," Luo Meng explained.

"This is the mask that you're talking about, right? This is indeed quite a special mask. You've already perished long ago, and all that remains is a wisp of your soul's aura. I would say that my spiritual sense is more powerful than the average immortal of my level, but even I was unable to detect anything, yet it was still able to detect your existence," Han Li said as he pointed at the cow mask.

"That's not the only remarkable thing about the mask... Not only is it able to completely conceal its wearer's appearance and aura, it also acts as a treasure to facilitate communication between guild members... As soon as someone loses their membership rights, the mask will immediately self-destruct," Luo Meng replied.

"What do you plan to do about the matter that the mask just spoke of?" Han Li asked.

"What can I possibly do? In my current state, there's no way I can do what the mask asks of me... Even if the guild sends people to investigate, by the time they get here, I will have completely disappeared off the face of this realm... However, if they try to punish my people for my transgressions, I hope that you can keep your promise and help my people avert that crisis," Luo Meng replied with a concerned look on his face.

"You make it sound so easy. If the Transient Guild really is as powerful as you claim, how will I possibly be able to protect this Dark Veil Island on my own?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

"I naturally wouldn't dare to ask you to directly oppose the guild, but I would be eternally grateful if you could save some of my people and preserve the bloodline of my Dark Veil Island," Luo Meng implored in a desperate voice.

"Perhaps there's another way, but I'm not sure if it'll work," Han Li said as a thoughtful look appeared in his eyes.

"What is it?" Luo Meng hurriedly asked.

"How about I go on this mission in your stead?" Han Li asked.

Luo Meng faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which an incredulous look appeared on his face. "As I already mentioned, all of the missions released by the guild are extremely perilous... Are you sure you want to go, Fellow Daoist Liu?"

Han Li was silent for a moment before replying in a truthful manner, "Truth be told, after hearing your description of the Transient Guild, it seems like this organization will be very useful to me. Hence, I require an identity that'll allow me to remain in the guild. If this mask can completely conceal my aura and appearance, then I'm sure no one will notice even if I go in your place, right?"

Chapter 102: Late

"That would be perfect... The members of the Transient Guild only care about the mask, not the person, anyway... Even if they know that there's a different person under the mask, as long as the mask hasn't been destroyed, they would still accept the substitute...

“Also... it's strictly prohibited to leak the identities of guild members... so that makes it even more difficult for anyone to find out that I've been replaced..." Luo Meng said with a relieved smile, but his words were cutting off intermittently, and he seemed to be in a very feeble state.

An extremely thin wisp of black mist slowly seeped out of his shoulder, then began to sway from side to side like a strand of seaweed.

"I can't maintain this form much longer... Fellow Daoist Liu. If you have any other questions... then ask them now before it's too late..." Luo Meng said with a wry smile as he turned to glance at the wisp of black mist emerging from his shoulder.

Another wisp of black mist began to seep out of his calf as he spoke.

"There's nothing more I want to ask you. If you have dying wishes, then go ahead and tell me. I won't turn them down as long as they're within the realm of my capabilities," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

Luo Meng looked up at the heavens as he murmured, "Just keep your promise to protect my people... I wouldn't dare to ask anything more of you... If my Luo Clan can make a resurgence someday, I would be... ecstatic..."

His voice gradually grew feebler and feebler, and his body also began to warp and fade, dissipating into wisps of black mist that quickly disappeared.

Han Li was a little dazed as he stared at the spot where Luo Meng's soul had just vanished. He couldn't help but be moved by Luo Meng's devotion to his people, even in death.

Only after a long while did he return to his senses, and he made a grabbing motion to draw the cow mask into his grasp.

This time, the mask maintained its substantial form and obediently flew into his hand.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he inspected the strange patterns on the mask in a slightly absentminded manner.

……

Close to a month later.

In a region of the sea countless kilometers away from Dark Veil Island, dark gray clouds filled the entire sky, and ferocious gusts of wind were howling incessantly, sweeping up enormous waves.

A streak of azure light pierced through the waves like a peerlessly sharp sword, slicing the waves apart and sending large volumes of water splashing in all directions.

Within the streak of azure light was Han Li, whose facial features were concealed behind the blue cow mask that he was wearing, but his sharp and piercing eyes were visible through the eye holes on the mask.

On the surface of the sea several dozen kilometers up ahead was a round island with a radius of no more than half a kilometer. Looking at the island from afar, it resembled a green leaf that was bobbing up and down in the waves, and that was his destination.

Han Li slowed down slightly, and after flying for close to another 10 kilometers, the island gradually became clearer in his field of view.

There were many sea fig trees growing all over the island, forming a vast expanse of lush greenery. The massive canopies of the trees were intertwined together to form a giant canopy over the entire island, with countless branches that were as thick as adult human arms layering on top of one another to form a sturdy wooden wall.

Countless thin and long lateral roots were trailing down from these dense masses of branches, and they resembled the beard of an elderly man as some of them extended into the soil down below, while others trailed down into the seawater.

Han Li flew over the island before drawing to a halt in mid-air and inspecting the island from afar. The ground on the island was littered with gray bird feces, but not a single seabird could be seen in the forest.

Furthermore, the only sound that he could hear came from the whistling of the wind through the branches of the sea fig trees, and the entire island was abnormally quiet.

Right at this moment, a cold voice rang out beside Han Li's ears.

"Wyrm 15, why aren't you entering the island?"

Han Li was slightly taken aback by this voice as it had come from the mask that he was wearing rather than from the island.

He didn't delay any further as he descended onto the island.

The soil on the island was very soft and loamy, and each step that Han Li took would leave a footprint beneath him. He traversed through the gaps in the dense forest to arrive at the center of the island, leaving a trail of footsteps in his wake.

At the center of an island was a massive sea fig tree that three people could link their arms around. All of the lateral roots hanging down from its branches had been cleared away to vacate a rather spacious area.

There were several figures in the area, and they were either standing or seated around the trunk of the tree.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the group, and his attention was immediately drawn to the red-robed man seated directly in front of the giant tree.

The man was wearing a crimson dragon mask that also had many strange runes engraved onto its surface, and the number "3" was engraved onto the glabella of the mask in strange characters.

This man was Wyrm 3.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly as he made this realization, but he didn't say anything.

Wyrm 3 only took a casual glance at Han Li before withdrawing his gaze, displaying no intention to speak with him.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to initiate any conversation, either, and he turned his gaze toward the others.

One of the figures gathered around the tree was slightly hunched over and was wearing a loose-fitting purple robe and a blue goat mask, upon which was engraved the number "9".

The figure was resting on their haunches, staring at something on the ground, not even bothering to cast a single glance in Han Li's direction.

Standing not far away from the purple-robed figure was a tall and broad man wearing a blue tiger mask, but he seemed to be more approachable and gave Han Li a slight nod.

Han Li didn't say anything as he cast his gaze toward the number "6" on the man's mask, and he returned the nod of acknowledgment.

To the left of the tree was an elegant woman in a mesh dress with an owl mask on her face. She was leaning against the trunk of the sea fig tree with her slender arms crossed in front of her chest, and as she turned to glance at Han Li, he caught a glimpse of the numbers "2" and "1" on her mask.

Behind her, on the other side of the sea fig tree, a head that was wearing a blue eagle mask that bore the numbers "2" and "5" poked out from behind the tree to take a glance at Han Li, then promptly ducked back behind the tree again.

There was also a thin figure hanging off a branch on the right side of the sea fig tree, and they were wearing a monkey mask with the number "8" engraved upon it.

Upon sensing Han Li's gaze, the thin figure also turned to look at Han Li with their yellow eyes through the holes on their mask.

Below the monkey-masked figure was a thin man wearing a blue robe and a bear mask. He was seated in an upright position, meditating with his eyes closed, and the numbers "1" and "3" were engraved onto the glabella of his mask.

Perhaps it was due to the rules of the Transient Guild or for some other reason, but no one was conversing with anyone else, and even Wyrm 3 wasn't saying anything to anyone.

Han Li quickly picked a spot to sit at, then closed his eyes and began to meditate.

Eight days passed by in the blink of an eye, and no one else turned up during this time, but neither did anyone leave or speak.

The atmosphere was a very strange one.

On the morning of the eighth day, right as the first ray of light from the rising sun shone down upon the island, Wyrm 3 suddenly raised his head slightly, then stood up from the ground as he declared in a rather rigid voice, "Time's up..."

Everyone quickly also stood up upon hearing this, and the thin monkey-masked man who had been seated on the tree branch this entire time immediately jumped down as well.

Right at this moment, a streak of light suddenly sped toward the island from afar, then plummeted out of the sky like an asteroid before crashing down onto the island.

The entire island shuddered violently, and all of the tree branches rustled incessantly.

The streak of light faded to reveal a burly figure wearing a boar mask.

As soon as he set foot on the island, he immediately rushed urgently toward the center of the island, snapping all of the branches and lateral roots in his path like a wrecking ball.

After arriving in the clearing, the man briefly inspected his surroundings, then yelled at the top of his lungs, "Which one of you is Wyrm 3?"

He then swept his gaze across everyone present without any inhibitions before his gaze finally settled on the red-robed man.

"So you're Wyrm 3. Hurry up and announce the mission, I still have things to do after this," the boar-masked man said in a loud voice.

"You're late, Wyrm 32," Wyrm 3 declared in a cold voice.

"Give it a rest, I'm only late by a few minutes. Hurry and announce the mission. I don't have any time to waste here," the boar-masked man said in an impatient voice with a dismissive wave of his hand.

All of a sudden, a sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart, and he reflexively took a step backward.

In the next instant, a layer of red light suddenly appeared over Wyrm 3's body, then transformed into a crimson inferno that enveloped him from head to toe. A scorching heatwave then erupted from his body, forcing everyone to rush back in retreat.

Immediately thereafter, he abruptly lunged forward with his one hand outstretched before him like a blade, aimed directly at the boar-masked man's chest.

In the face of Wyrm 3's abrupt attack, the boar-masked man reacted extremely quickly, taking a step back as he made a hand seal to conjure up a layer of white light over his body.

At the same time, a white octagonal shield appeared before him.

The shield was riddled with rhomboid patterns, and there was a layer of dazzling white light radiating from its surface, giving off bursts of law fluctuations.

Even though the boar-masked man was quite rushed in the defensive measures that he was adopting, Han Li noticed that the law fluctuations emanating from his shield were even more powerful than what Han Qiu had been able to muster up.

A dull thump rang out, and to everyone's surprise, there was no resounding clash. Instead, the outcome of the battle was decided after just that single clash.

To everyone's shock and horror, Wyrm 3's hand had already pierced through the octagonal shield and plunged straight into the boar-masked man's heart.

Plumes of white smoke were rising up from the hole on his chest, and the muscles around it had already been completely liquefied, dripping down from his body like molten lava.

"For openly defying the guild's orders and arriving late, Wyrm 32's membership status has been revoked," Wyrm 3 said in a cold voice as he slowly withdrew his hand.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the runes on the boar mask began to glow with dazzling light, following which the mask disintegrated into powder before dissipating into nothingness.

A face that was twisted in shock and agony was revealed beneath the mask, and it seemed that even up to the instant that the boar-masked man met his demise, he was still unable to believe that he had been unable to withstand even a single attack from his assailant.

Chapter 103: Master of Red Moon Island

The top of the boar-masked man's head suddenly sprang open, and a blue nascent soul with a horrified look on its face flew out before attempting to flee into the distance.

Wyrm 3 flicked a finger through the air without even taking a single glance at the nascent soul, releasing a ball of fire that instantly vanished into thin air.

Close to 10 kilometers away, a streak of fire caught up to the blue nascent soul in an instant.

A dull thump rang out, and Wyrm 32's nascent soul exploded into a burst of blue light before vanishing out of existence.

Everyone fell silent upon hearing this, but no one was able to see anyone else's expression due to the fact that they were all wearing masks.

Wyrm 3 swept his gaze over everyone, and there was no intimidation in his eyes. Instead, his eyes were completely aloof and apathetic, as if he were looking at a bunch of inanimate objects.

It was as if in his eyes, the people around him were no different from the rocks and trees on the island, or were simply tools at his disposal.

"The mission you'll be carrying out is to kill the master of Red Moon Island, Gongshu Hong," Wyrm 3 declared in a cold voice.

This announcement was immediately met with a surprised reaction, and several people in the group clearly had their reservations about this mission target.

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly beneath his cow mask. He had heard about Gongshu Hong from Luo Feng before, and this was certainly not going to be an easy target to assassinate.

According to Luo Feng, Gongshu Hong was a powerful Earthly Immortal with a mid-True Immortal Stage cultivation base. He cultivated the laws of blood, which were an extremely rare branch of the laws of water, and he was renowned all over the Black Wind Sea for his brutality and bloodlust.

Given how vicious and violent he was, he definitely had a great number of enemies, but not only was he extremely formidable, the power of laws that he cultivated was also extremely troublesome to deal with, so no one dared to go after him. Han Li certainly wasn't expecting such a fearsome character to be the target of their mission.

"Wyrm 3, with all due respect, Red Moon Island has always been a very mysterious place and very rarely interacts with the other islands.

“On top of that, for some reason, the island went into isolation several thousand years ago, and all outside cultivators are prohibited from setting foot on the island unless their presence on the island is considered to be necessary by the island master.

“It's said that all trespassers are executed without exception..." the goat-masked Wyrm 8 said in a rather hesitant manner.

"There's no need for you to worry about that. The guild has previously already sent people to infiltrate the island, and they've brought back a great deal of information. We would've waited until we managed to learn more about the island before releasing this mission, but half a month ago, the higher-ups in the guild passed down an order for Gongshu Hong to be killed as soon as possible," Wyrm 3 said as he took a glance at Wyrm 8.

"According to what I've heard, Gongshu Hong ranks near the top among all island masters in the entire Black Wind Sea, only below the masters of the central islands. On top of that, he has many Layman Immortals serving him, so he's not to be taken lightly," the tiger-masked Wyrm 16 said in a grim voice.

His sentiment was immediately supported by the owl-masked woman, who said, "Indeed. On top of that, as an Earthly Immortal, he'll be at the height of his powers on the island that he rules over. If we venture onto his island recklessly, we could..."

"What nonsense! Those so-called Earthly Immortals are just failed immortals who don't possess the aptitude to pursue any other paths of cultivation! Only in a pitiful place like your Black Wind Sea is someone like him considered to be a formidable target," Wyrm 3 scoffed with more than a hint of ridicule in his voice.

Han Li had been observing in silence this entire time, and he noticed that both Wyrm 8 and Wyrm 9 displayed very slight reactions to what they had just heard, seemingly taking objection to Wyrm 3's derogatory words.

However, neither of them expressed their displeasure beyond that.

"Let me make this clear. If there are any deserters or cowards who are constantly hanging back on this mission, you'll meet the same fate as Wyrm 32," Wyrm 3 warned in a cold voice.

Even though everyone was wearing masks, a few of them couldn't help but exchange a few glances, and through their non-verbal communication, it was clear that they were all praying for the best.

Wyrm 3 paid no heed to everyone's reactions as he swept a hand through the air, and a burst of red light instantly appeared in the sky.

A draconic roar rang out from within the light, and a dragon-shaped flying ark that was rough 200 to 300 feet in length emerged.

The entire was fiery red in color, and at the front of the ark was a figurehead carved in the form of a dragon's head. The entire ark was riddled with smooth golden spirit patterns, as well as engravings of fiery clouds, indicating that it was no ordinary treasure.

Wyrm 3 leaped up into the air before landing at the front of the spirit ark, following which his slightly rigid voice rang out again. "What are you all waiting for?"

"This is... an Acquired Immortal Treasure! As expected of an immortal of his caliber..." the goat-masked Wyrm 9 couldn't help but praise as he looked up at the fiery red spirit ark, then leaped onto it behind Wyrm 3.

Everyone else also rose up into the air, and a hint of envy appeared in the eyes of many of them upon hearing what Wyrm 9 had just said.

Most of the people gathered here were Layman Immortals, and not only did they not have a single immortal treasure to share between them, barely any of them had ever even seen one before.

Han Li was also rather taken aback, and he couldn't help but take a few extra glances at the spirit ark.

After everyone had jumped aboard, Wyrm 3 made a hand seal before casting a series of incantation seals into the spirit ark, and the entire ark instantly lit up with bright red light as scorching crimson flames appeared over its surface, resembling several soaring fiery dragons that carried the ark rapidly into the distance.

The speed at which the ark was moving was truly astonishing.

……

Several days later.

A streak of fiery red light sped across the sky above a turbulent blue sea, then suddenly stopped in mid-air, revealing a dragon-shaped flying ark inside.

Atop the ark stood several masked figures, and they were none other than the members of the Transient Guild who were traveling toward Red Moon Island.

At this moment, Han Li was standing on one side of the ark, casting his gaze toward a large island close to 100 kilometers away.

To call it an island was a bit of an injustice as it was countless times larger than Dark Veil Island and resembled a huge continent.

"Here's some information regarding Red Moon Island. Take a look for yourselves," Wyrm 3 said in an emotionless voice.

He then swept a hand through the air, releasing several white jade slips that flew toward Han Li and the others.

Han Li accepted one of the jade slips, then took a glance at everyone around him, upon which he saw several people pressing their jade slip against the glabella of their mask.

He did the same thing, and sure enough, once the jade slip was pressed against his mask, a series of images and text instantly appeared in his mind.

After inspecting the contents of the jade slip for a moment, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he discovered Red Moon Island was even larger than he had anticipated. It was truly like a continent.

"Wyrm 3, I'm assuming those six or seven locations annotated on the map in the jade slip must be the places where Gongshu Hong is most likely to appear. Which one should we go to first?" the goat-masked Wyrm 9 asked.

"In order to ascertain his location as soon as possible, we're going to split up into three groups and infiltrate the island from the east, the west, and the south. Each group will explore the annotated points closest to them first, then gradually advance toward the center of the island until we track him down," Wyrm 3 replied without any hesitation.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this. He had already anticipated this type of arrangement, and in reality, he wanted nothing more than to be split up. In fact, the ideal situation would be for him to go off on his own, but clearly, that wasn't going to be possible.

Sure enough, Wyrm 3 continued, "Wyrm 8, Wyrm 13, Wyrm 21, the three of you will form a group led by Wyrm 8, and you'll enter the island from the east to explore the annotated points on the eastern side."

The monkey-masked Wyrm 8 cupped his fist in a salute to accept the order.

The bear-masked man and the owl-faced woman also nodded in response before joining Wyrm 8 in silence.

Wyrm 3 then swept his gaze over the remaining guild members, and continued, "Wyrm 9, Wyrm 15, Wyrm 16, the three of you will form a group led by Wyrm 9, and you'll enter the island from the west."

"You can count on me, Wyrm 3," the goat-masked Wyrm 9 declared with a respectful salute.

Han Li and the tiger-masked man exchanged a glance with one another, then joined Wyrm 9.

Wyrm 3 didn't even bother to take a glance at Wyrm 9. Instead, he turned to the eagle-masked man as he instructed, "Wyrm 25, you can accompany me and enter the island from the south."

Wyrm 25 accepted the order in a slightly hoarse voice, then made his way over to Wyrm 3.

"Gongshu Hong is adept in the laws of blood, so he's extremely sensitive to auras. On top of that, there are surveillance restrictions set up all over the island. Under normal circumstances, we wouldn't have to worry as our masks can conceal our auras, but if we're too careless with the use of our spiritual sense, then there's a very good chance that we could be discovered.

“Hence, do not use your spiritual sense after entering the island unless it's absolutely necessary to do so," Wyrm 3 said in a stern voice.

"Yes," everyone replied in unison.

"One last thing: if any of you find Gongshu Hong before I do, do not engage him in battle and immediately notify me using your mask. Even though it's very unlikely that he'll be able to detect us when we're using our masks, as a safety precaution, make sure to also only use your masks when absolutely necessary," Wyrm 3 continued.

"We'll be sure to keep that in mind, Wyrm 3," Wyrm 9 immediately said in a respectful voice.

Han Li placed a hand on his mask, and he suddenly recalled how Wyrm 3 had transmitted his voice to him through the mask upon his arrival on Sea Fig Island. It seemed that this mask was indeed quite a mysterious treasure.

"Let's begin!" Wyrm 3 declared, then stowed the spirit ark away with a wave of his hand.

He then reached out to grab onto Wyrm 25 before speeding away to the eastern side of the island.

Wyrm 8 and his group also departed as streaks of light.

Wyrm 9 took a glance at Han Li and Wyrm 16, then departed toward the west, followed closely by Han Li and Wyrm 16. However, what was worthy of note was that they were significantly slower than the others.

Chapter 104: Pilgrimage

It didn't take long before Han Li's trio arrived at their designated entry point, which was a certain beach on the western coast of Red Moon Island.

To their surprise, the area was completely barren and devoid of human population. However, they then recalled that Red Moon Island had been isolated from the outside world for thousands of years, so this wasn't all that surprising.

As for the alert restrictions set up here, they were concealed in a clever fashion, but for a trio of immortals like them, they were naturally able to avoid the restrictions with ease.

Even so, they didn't dare to let down their guard and made sure to keep their auras concealed as they traveled toward the first target on the map, a place by the name of Heavenly Water City.

At the moment, there was a dense blanket of clouds in the sky, allowing the trio to travel even more discreetly.

While flying through the air, Han Li was inspecting the environment on the island, and he discovered that the terrain in the western part of the island was quite flat, with very few hills or mountains.

Most of the terrain here consisted of plains, and there was lush greenery stretching as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

Perhaps it was due to the properties of the soil here, but all of the trees on the island were of a crimson color.

The leaves on the trees rustled incessantly amid the sea breeze, presenting a sight that resembled a flickering sea of fire.

After a while, the three of them finally flew out of the forest, and a plain appeared up ahead. Several dozen kilometers away from the forest was a large city, and even from afar, they could see the words "Maple Sea City" emblazoned onto the plaque above the city gates.

All of a sudden, Wyrm 9 raised a hand and stopped cold in his tracks.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 immediately followed suit.

"Did you see something?" Wyrm 16 asked as he inspected his surroundings.

"This is the first city that we've encountered after entering the island, so why don't we take this opportunity to ascertain our location? After all, the map provided to us by Wyrm 3 isn't accurate, so let's make sure we haven't gone off track," Wyrm 9 said.

"That's a good idea," Wyrm 16 replied with a nod.

Han Li naturally had no objections to this, either. They had been flying for close to a day up to this point, so there was indeed a need to ascertain their location.

Thus, the three of them descended onto the ground below before making their way toward the city.

However, upon arriving at the city, the three of them were surprised to find that not only were the city gates tightly shut, there was no sound coming out of the city at all. This certainly wasn't a small city, yet it seemed to be completely deserted.

"Keep your guard up, this could be a trap set by the enemy!" Wyrm 9 cautioned through voice transmission.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 nodded in response, and the three of them approached the city in a stealthy manner. After verifying that there were no restrictions set up outside the city, they leaped onto the city wall.

Due to what they had been told by Wyrm 3, they refrained from releasing their spiritual sense to inspect the state of the city. However, after inspecting the city through other means, they didn't notice anything abnormal.

"Looks like it really is just an empty city. It seems I was overly cautious," Wyrm 9 mused.

"How strange. This city doesn't look very old, so it should've been inhabited not long ago. It doesn't look like it's been attacked, either, so why is there no one here?" Wyrm 16 asked in a puzzled voice.

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly in befuddlement.

Through the use of his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he had seen that many of the houses in the city were empty, and some of the shops also had their doors tightly shut. However, there were many signs indicating recent human activity, so it did indeed seem like the residents of the city had only recently left.

The wind blew through the empty streets, causing some of the open doors and windows to creek and clatter incessantly. An occasional stray cat or stray dog would pass through the area, but those were the only signs of life in the city.

"In any case, what happened here has nothing to do with us. We've already confirmed our location, so it's time to leave. We have to prioritize our mission above all else," Wyrm 9 said, clearly not wanting to investigate what had happened here.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 nodded in response. They had no interest in such trivial matters, either.

Thus, the three of them departed from the city and continued onward.

After leaving the city, the terrain up ahead only became flatter and flatter, and it didn't take long before a lush grassland appeared up ahead. There were many cows and sheep roaming and grazing freely over the grassland, but there was still not even a single person to be seen.

In fact, they didn't even discover any people in the small villages littered across the grassland.

At the end of the grassland was another city, and after encountering the deserted Maple Sea City and all of those empty villages, the three of them had no intentions of stopping at the city, but they still reflexively took a glance down at it.

As a result, they were once again surprised to find that this city was also deserted.

"Why is this city completely deserted as well?" Wyrm 16 asked in a puzzled voice.

Wyrm 9 contemplated the situation for a moment before speculating, "Perhaps something recently happened in this area, so everyone has been evacuated."

"If the next city is also deserted, then I feel like there's a need to inform the others of what we've seen," Han Li said.

"Let's wait and see. According to the map, there's another large city less than 1,000 kilometers up ahead," Wyrm 9 replied with a nod.

Sure enough, it didn't take long before another city emerged up ahead.

This place was known as Calm Rest City, and it was quite a large city that was several hundred kilometers in size.

To the surprise of Han Li's trio, everything was normal in this city. Long lines of people were entering and exiting the city gates, and all of the shops in the city were open, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold. Aside from mortals, there were also many low-grade cultivators here, presenting a stark contrast with the previous two deserted cities.

Wyrm 16 seemed to have relaxed a little upon seeing this, and he speculated in a joking voice, "There are quite a few people here. Could it be that everyone from the other two cities has come here?"

However, Han Li's brows were furrowed slightly in befuddlement. This city was not far away from the previous city, so why was the situation here so different?

"Those two previous deserted cities are very strange. There must be abnormal circumstances that led up to those two cities being deserted, so I think it's best to conduct a quick investigation. We have more than enough time on our hands at the moment, and we can also gather some information about the island from this city," Han Li suggested.

"Wyrm 15's right. It's better to be safe than sorry," Wyrm 16 chimed in in agreement.

"Alright, in that case, let's make a brief stop at this city, but make sure to keep your guard up at all times," Wyrm 9 said as he pointed at a plaza at the center of the city.

At the center of the plaza stood a crimson statue that was giving off faint crimson light, which encompassed an area with a radius of over 1,000 feet.

All of the people nearby, regardless of whether they were mortals or cultivators, regarded the statue with a great deal of reverence, bowing respectfully whenever they passed by. However, none of the cultivators in the city were very advanced in their cultivation base, with even the most powerful of them only at the Core Formation Stage.

Han Li had naturally also already noticed the statue, and it was a normal statue used by Earthly Immortals to collect the power of faith.

As an Earthly Immortal himself, it was nothing out of the ordinary to see that Gong Shuhong had set up statues like this on his island.

However, according to the information that the Transient Guild had collected, the cultivation art that Gong Shuhong was using was quite special, and it seemed to be able to allow him to conduct surveillance using these statues. As such, they were warned not to stir up any trouble in any of the island's cities to avoid alerting Gong Shuhong to their presence.

However, Han Li had always had his doubts about these claims.

Recently, he had read many scriptures about these statues, and according to everything that he had read, these ordinary statues were only special vessels for gathering the power of faith. They weren't Earthly Deity Avatars, so they didn't have any senses.

However, he naturally wasn't going to go against the instructions of the Transient Guild for no reason.

The three of them landed in a discreet location outside the city, then used the restrictions in their masks to alter their appearance, transforming into three completely unremarkable-looking merchants before entering the city with everyone else.

Even though their auras were concealed by their masks, they were still reining in their auras as much as possible.

Looking at the lively and bustling scene around him, Han Li couldn't help but think back to the time that he had spent traveling the Spirit Domain Realm with Liu Le'er.

At the time, he had still been in a mentally impaired state, but he was able to retain those memories.

In an environment as cruel as the cultivation world, it was very touching that a little girl like her truly cared for him and looked after him like her own brother, and in her, Han Li felt as if he could see a faint shadow of his little sister, the memory of whom had already become rather fuzzy in his mind.

Han Li couldn't help but wonder exactly where Liu Le'er had been taken.

All of a sudden, he was snapped out of his train of thought by the sound of Wyrm 16's voice.

"There's a restaurant up ahead. Why don't we go take a look there?"

Han Li immediately returned to his senses before casting his gaze forward to find a three-story restaurant that appeared to be thriving.

As soon as the trio entered the restaurant, they were immediately greeted by an energetic waiter.

"We would like some privacy, so get us a booth," Wyrm 16 instructed before the waiter had a chance to say anything.

"Sure thing! Please come with me," the waiter said as he led the trio into an elegant booth on the second floor.

"We'd like two flagons of warm wine and a few of your restaurant's best dishes, and make it snappy. Take this silver, you can keep the change."

After taking a seat, Wyrm 16 pulled out a silver ingot before tossing it at the waiter.

Both Han Li and Wyrm 9's attention were drawn to Wyrm 16 upon witnessing this interaction, thinking to themselves that he seemed to be a regular patron at restaurants like this.

The waiter gleefully accepted the silver ingot, then gave an affirmative response before quickly exiting the room.

Wyrm 16 was slightly embarrassed by the scrutiny directed his way from Han Li and Wyrm 9, and he said, "My apologies, fellow daoists. I've transcended beyond requiring food and drink for sustenance long ago, but I'm embarrassed to admit that I've never quite been able to get over my hankering for mortal food."

"There's no need to apologize, Fellow Daoist. Everyone has their individual preferences. Now that you mention it, I'm also beginning to miss the foods that I once enjoyed as a mortal, so this is a perfect opportunity to rekindle some of those past memories," Wyrm 9 chuckled.

The waiter quickly returned with a platter that was laden with all types of dishes and wine.

The food and drink served in the restaurant was quite appetizing, and both the wine and the dishes were giving off alluring aromas.

Wyrm 16 poured out cups of wine for everyone, then quickly downed two cups of wine in succession as a blissful look appeared on his face.

A faint smile also appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he also took a small sip of wine from his own cup.

"I'll leave you to enjoy your meal. Don't hesitate to call for me if you need anything." The waiter turned to depart as he spoke, but he was stopped by Wyrm 16.

"Hold on a second."

"Is there something else you need?" the waiter asked as he turned back around.

"The three of us are merchants who came from the south, and we passed by Maple Sea City and Inkface City on the way here, but both of those cities were completely deserted. Do you know why that's the case?" Wyrm 9 asked with a smile.

"All of the residents of those two cities were summoned to Red Moon City for the pilgrimage not long ago, so they're naturally deserted," the waiter replied with a smile.

Chapter 105: Linking Up

"Pilgrimage? What's that?" Wyrm 16 reflexively asked.

Wyrm 9's brows immediately furrowed slightly as he turned to Wyrm 16 with a displeased expression.

Wyrm 16 had also realized his mistake, and a sheepish look appeared on his face.

"The pilgrimage is..." The waiter was just about to reply when his expression suddenly changed drastically, and he yelled, "You don't know about the pilgrimage? You're outsiders..."

Two translucent threads of light shot into the waiter's head in a flash, and his voice immediately cut off as a dazed look appeared in his eyes.

Right before the waiter began yelling, Wyrm 9 had already conjured up a blue light barrier that encompassed the entire booth to prevent any sound from escaping.

"My apologies..." Wyrm 16 said with an embarrassed expression.

"It's fine. It's a good thing that Wyrm 15 was able to react so quickly," Wyrm 9 said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"Go on, tell us what this pilgrimage is," Han Li prompted.

He had cast a small enchantment onto the waiter. The enchantment was very weak as he wasn't able to use any spiritual sense, but it was more than enough on a mortal like the waiter.

"The pilgrimage is a tradition that has been around since ancient times. Once every 60 years, the residents of each city would be taken in batches by their respective city lords to Red Moon City, where they would be preached to by the holy lord. The year of the pilgrimage is also known as the holy year," the waiter replied in a robotic manner.

"If they're only going to see the holy lord, then why do they have to pack all of their belongings as if they're relocating?" Han Li asked.

"Because everyone wants to be chosen. The holy lord will bestow his blessings upon the fortunate chosen ones, granting them more fertile land," the waiter replied without any hesitation.

"Who are the chosen ones? And what happens to those who aren't chosen?" Han Li asked.

"The ones who are chosen are all the most devout followers of the holy lord. It is the highest honor one can receive. As for those who aren't chosen, they can only return to their original cities," the waiter said as a hint of longing appeared in his eyes.

Han Li's trio exchanged a glance with one another upon hearing this, and all of them could see their own surprise mirrored in one another's eyes.

That explained the deserted cities, and as for the holy lord that the waiter was speaking of, that was almost definitely Gongshu Hong.

"What else do you know about the holy lord?" Wyrm 9 asked.

"The holy lord bestows upon us fertile land and protects us for generation after generation..."

The waiter rattled off a long list of things that this supposed holy lord did, but none of this information was useful to Han Li's trio.

Han Li shook his head as he interrupted the waiter's pointless rambling and asked, "You all seem to be very hostile toward outsiders. Is this a part of the holy lord's teachings?"

"That's right! All outsiders are sinister devils who covet the fertile land of our Red Moon Island. If we discover any outsiders, we are to inform our city lords right away and have those outsiders killed," the waiter replied with a dazed expression, but a cold and forbidding tone had crept into his voice.

Wyrm 16 gave a cold harrumph upon hearing this, while a contemplative look appeared on Wyrm 9's face.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he asked a few more questions regarding the holy lord, but unfortunately, the waiter was but a mere mortal who knew very little, so Han Li was unable to dig up much more information.

Thus, he indicated for Wyrm 9 to withdraw the blue light barrier in the booth, then chanted an incantation as a faint gleam appeared in his eyes before vanishing in a flash.

The waiter abruptly shuddered as a hint of clarity returned to his eyes, and he looked around with a slightly dazed expression.

"You can go now. We'll call for you if we need anything," Han Li said in a calm manner.

He had just wiped away the waiter's memories of the last few minutes.

"Enjoy your meal." The waiter's head was still feeling a little fuzzy, and he flashed an apologetic smile before exiting the booth.

"So that's why those cities were deserted. It seems like we were overthinking things," Wyrm 16 said with a smile.

"That may be true, but we did manage to get some rather interesting information out of him, nonetheless. Seeing as all of the residents of those two cities have been summoned for the pilgrimage, doesn't that mean that Gongshu Hong should currently be accepting the pilgrimage in that so-called Red Moon City?" Wyrm 9 mused.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, and the information about Red Moon Island contained in the jade slips that Wyrm 3 had given them surfaced in his mind.

The map included in the jade slips was very basic, and there were very few cities marked out on them, but one of those cities was indeed one by the name of Red Moon City. However, it was quite some distance away from Heavenly Water City.

If these mortals were going to attend the pilgrimage, they most likely had to be taken to Red Moon City by high-grade cultivators through some special means. Otherwise, at the snail-like rate that mortals were capable of traveling at, there was no guarantee that they would be able to reach Red Moon City in this lifetime.

Wyrm 16's eyes suddenly lit up, clearly having also drawn the same conclusion, and he asked, "Should we communicate this information with the others?"

Han Li considered this notion for a moment before offering his opinion on the matter. "Given how we were able to obtain this piece of information so easily, I'm sure the scouts sent by the Transient Guild would've already been able to secure the same information.

“The list of locations that they proposed that Gongshu Hong could be at right now didn't include Red Moon City, and there had to have been a reason for that. Perhaps what the waiter just told us was nothing more than a circulating rumor."

Wyrm 9 nodded in agreement. "I think we should follow the original plan and travel to Heavenly Water City to link up with the members of the guild lurking in the city, then think about what to do next."

After arriving at a consensus, the three of them promptly departed from Calm Rest City.

After that, they passed through many more cities, towns, and villages, and around 20% to 30% of them were deserted.

Having already learned the reason why these places were deserted, the three of them made no further stops along the way.

Three days later, a majestic black city that was over 100 feet tall appeared on a set of vast plains that stretched for thousands of kilometers.

There were thousands of acres of lush fields outside of the city, and they were surrounded by several branches of a large river that flowed out to the sea, segregating the land into plots of farmland of different shapes and sizes.

The main branch of the river had been diverted by an artificial channel, which passed through a rice field before circling around the entire city to form a moat that was over 100 feet wide.

At the moment, it was early in the morning, and the drawbridge that led into the city hadn't been lowered yet. Countless mortals were gathered outside the city, carrying different wares in their hands, on their shoulders, or on carts, waiting for the city gates to open.

Among them were three completely unremarkable-looking figures in coarse linen clothes with conical hats on their heads. The trio looked no different from the average farmers here.

They were none other than Han Li's trio, who had arrived outside the city and adopted disguises for themselves.

The light of the rising sun illuminated the large characters that spelled out "Heavenly Water City" on the plaque above the city gates, and all of a strike, the loud strike of a bell rang out from within the city.

Immediately thereafter, the sound of moving mechanical parts rang out, and the heavy drawbridge was slowly lowered while tethered to a pair of thick black chains.

Everyone outside the city had already been waiting for quite some time, and they began to enter the city along the drawbridge.

Stationed on either side of the city gates were several Nascent Soul cultivators standing on guard duty, and they were led by a Deity Transformation cultivator. All of them wore dark blue robes with a crimson crescent moon embroidered on each of their chests.

Han Li was unable to use his spiritual sense to examine the city, but he knew that there had to be even more powerful cultivators inside.

With the observation that they had made through visiting the previous few cities, they had discovered that Red Moon Island was the same as the other islands in the Black Wind Sea in that cultivators lived among the mortals in the cities, and the mortals seemed to be accustomed to the existence of the cultivators as well.

However, it seemed that all of the cultivators at or above the Nascent Soul Stage on the island were wearing these blue robes emblazoned with crimson moons, making it appear as if they all belonged to a certain sect.

After entering through the city gates, a faint burst of light appeared above Han Li. He raised his head slightly to discover an octagonal array diagram engraved onto the brick above his head, with a round copper mirror embedded at the very center of the diagram.

There was a beam of faint red light that was shining down from the copper mirror, encompassing everyone who made passed by beneath it.

With just a single glance, Han Li was able to figure out the purpose of the array. It was most likely an array that was designed to pick out cultivators who were intentionally posing as mortals to prevent them from sneaking into the city.

Given Han Li's current level of expertise in arrays, this array wasn't very complex or advanced. Anyone above the Grand Ascension would be able to easily pass through under it without being detected after making some simple preparations.

However, given how powerful the auras of cultivators above the Grand Ascension Stage were, if they didn't possess any special treasures to conceal their auras, they would've most likely already been detected upon entering the island, so they wouldn't even have made it to this point.

Han Li and the others were all above the Grand Ascension Stage, and with the aura concealment effect of these masks, they had nothing to worry about.

Thus, the three of them followed the crowd in a relaxed manner as they slowly drew closer and closer to the city, and while passing under the array, the light in the copper mirror only flashed briefly before returning to normal, clearly passing them off as mortals.

After entering the city, the crowds of people began to diverge in two separate directions, and the sights and scenes in the city were gradually laid out before them.

The street that was directly facing them was lined with shops and merchants, and different flags used to attract customers were hanging off all of the shop buildings.

However, it was still quite early, so quite a few of the shops still weren't open for business, and there weren't too many people on the bluestone streets aside from those who had just entered the city.

The only shops that were open were ones that were serving breakfast to the early risers.

This city was larger than any other city that Han Li's trio had passed through on Red Moon Island, and the entire city was split up into four major areas by two main streets, one that ran from northeast to southwest, and the other from northwest to southeast.

Han Li's trio followed one of the main streets to the southern area of the city, then branched off onto a smaller path. After walking for over an hour, taking many turns in the process, they arrived in a secluded alley.

The alley was extremely quiet, and the few courtyards inside all had their doors tightly shut. There was no sound to be heard coming from any alleys, and not a single person could be seen, either.

The three of them made their way to an ordinary-looking estate at the deepest point in the alley, then drew to a halt.

"This is the place," Wyrm 9 said as he took a glance at the dark red doors of the estate.

This estate was a secret stronghold established by the members of the Transient Guild who had already infiltrated Red Moon Island, and Han Li's trio had arrived here to link up with them and obtain intelligence.

Wyrm 16 made his way over to the doors of the estate, then knocked on them using the door-knockers just like any ordinary mortal would, employing a sequence of two short knocks followed by a long knock.

A few dull thuds rang out, but there was no response from inside.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to use his spiritual sense to assess the situation when he remembered the warning that Wyrm 3 had issued to them.

Wyrm 16 and Wyrm 9 had naturally also realized that something seemed to be amiss, but they didn't use their spiritual sense, either, clearly harboring the same inhibitions as Han Li.

Wyrm 16 turned around to look at Han Li and Wyrm 9 with a suspicious expression, and Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly in response, but he didn't say anything.

As for Wyrm 9, he was also silent for a moment before gesturing for the two of them to prepare for battle.

Right as the three of them were preparing to break in by force, a string of four bell chimes suddenly rang out from inside in the agreed-upon three short and one long sequence.

The three of them faltered slightly as they turned their attention back to the doors, and Wyrm 16 hesitated momentarily before quickly knocking on the door three more times, this time with more force.

Moments later, the dark red doors swung open to create a gap that could allow a person to pass through, and the head of a middle-aged man poked out from within.

"Come in," the man said in a low voice after taking a glance at Han Li's trio.

Chapter 106: Crimson Space

Han Li took a glance at the middle-aged man to find that his face had clearly also been manifested from one of the Transient Guild's masks.

The faces conjured up by the masks looked no different from normal faces, but the wearers of the masks could sense a faint connection between the masks, and that connection was what the members of the Transient Guild used to communicate with one another.

Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16 had clearly also noticed this, and they stepped into the courtyard of the estate one after another.

Han Li hesitated momentarily before also following suit.

Once everyone had entered the courtyard, the middle-aged man took a quick glance outside before closing the doors again.

The courtyard was over 1,000 feet in size, and aside from a withered old tree, there was only a set of stone tables and stone stools inside, positioned at the foot of the tree.

The tree was growing on a patch of soil, but aside from that, the rest of the courtyard was paved with brand-new tiles that were spotlessly clean, without even a single fallen leaf on them.

Furthermore inside was a main room that was directly facing the doors of the estate, and on either side of the main room were several booths, all of which currently had their doors slightly ajar.

The middle-aged man led the way forward while turning back to Han Li's trio as he said, "I've heard that the higher-ups are sending more people here, and I've been waiting for quite some time. May I ask who it is that's leading this mission?"

Han Li had been constantly observing the middle-aged man ever since he entered the courtyard, and as soon as this question was raised, a cold light immediately flashed through his eyes as he threw a punch at the man from behind without any warning.

The man was quite alarmed by this abrupt turn of events, but he seemed to have already been prepared, and a burst of red light erupted from his back, forming a shimmering silver shield that appeared in the path of Han Li's fist.

A dull thump rang out, and the silver shield exploded violently, while the middle-aged man was sent flying through the air, crashing heavily onto the stone staircase in front of the main room. He immediately threw up several mouthfuls of blood in succession, and his aura became significantly diminished.

Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16 had clearly also detected that something was amiss, yet right as they were also about to spring into action, a faint buzzing sound rang out, and the surrounding space suddenly began to warp and twist.

Bursts of red light erupted into the heavens in an area with a radius of several thousand feet around the courtyard, and a massive crimson array projection appeared in the sky with countless crimson runes surging over its surface.

Before Han Li's trio had a chance to react, red light flashed at the center of the array projection, and they appeared in a crimson space along with the middle-aged man.

This space didn't seem like it belonged to the real world, and there appeared to be no end to it in sight in any direction.

Above everyone was a dense layer of crimson yin clouds, while the ground down below was bright red in color, as if it had been soaked by blood. There was even a nauseating, bloody odor wafting through the surrounding air.

Right as Han Li's trio was inspecting their surroundings with bewildered expressions, the entire crimson space suddenly shuddered violently, and hundreds of rifts of different sizes instantly opened up on the ground to release bursts of viscous crimson mist.

A series of indistinct figures then crawled out of the mist amid a chorus of ghostly howls.

Those indistinct figures were humanoid blood ghosts that looked as if they had just been skinned, and they were crawling out in hordes from the rifts on the ground.

As soon as these sinister blood ghosts emerged from the ground, they immediately let loose a string of hoarse cries as they pounced on Han Li's trio.

"Be on your guard, fellow daoists. Not only do we have to pay attention to those blood ghosts, the aura of this place is also not quite right," Wyrm 9 cautioned as he took a glance at the blood ghosts, then looked up at the crimson clouds in the sky.

Han Li had naturally also noticed that the bloody odor wafting throughout this place seemed to contain a strange type of belligerent energy that could enter directly into one's consciousness, invoking a sense of frustration and agitation.

However, given his immense spiritual sense, this level of disruption wasn't worthy of concern.

After issuing those cautionary words to Han Li and Wyrm 16, Wyrm 9 flipped a hand over to produce a piece of white jade with a golden string passing through it. He then placed the string around his own neck to wear the piece of jade like a pendant, and it released a burst of translucent white light that encompassed his entire body.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a palm through the air, and a torrent of blue waves erupted in front of him amid a flash of blue light, instantly sweeping up around a dozen of the blood ghosts that were closest to him, pulverizing them into clouds of blood mist upon contact.

Wyrm 16 also pulled out a purple talisman before pressing it to his own glabella, and the talisman abruptly vanished amid a flash of purple light. Immediately thereafter, he let loose a low roar, and a string of cracks and pops rang out from within his body as his arms and torso began to rapidly expand.

In this new enlarged form, he leaped high up into the air before crashing down onto the army of blood ghosts up ahead like a giant asteroid, instantly pulverizing seven or eight of them.

In order to avoid arousing suspicion, Han Li also pretended to take a pill, then took a step forward before sending the two blood ghosts closest to him flying back with his fists.

While the two blood ghosts were flying back, they crashed into around a dozen more oncoming blood ghosts, all of which exploded into blood mist amid a string of dull thumps.

The three of them quickly discovered that these blood ghosts were quite fearsome in appearance, but they weren't very difficult to deal with at all. In fact, none of them could take even a single hit.

However, the problem was that there seemed to be no end to them, and after one horde was struck down, more would immediately emerge from the rifts on the ground to take their place. No matter how many were killed, there was always more to come, and Han Li's trio was quickly surrounded by hundreds of blood ghosts in a watertight encirclement.

Meanwhile, the eyes of the middle-aged man who had just been injured by Han Li had turned slightly bloodshot, and a horrified look had appeared on his face as he frantically summoned all types of treasures. First, he released a set of array flags that he set up in the surrounding area, then summoned a mirror that hovered above his head while a suit of crimson armor appeared over his body amid a flash of red light.

One protective light barrier after another appeared around him to shield him from all directions, and none of the surrounding blood ghosts were able to get close to him. All they could do was frantically swipe their ghostly claws at the protective light barriers, of which there were around seven or eight.

However, the middle-aged man still didn't seem to feel safe, and he was holding a crimson longsword as his eyes darted around in an anxious and uneasy manner.

It was clear that even though his treasures were capable of keeping the hordes of blood ghosts at bay, they were unable to prevent the bloody odor in the air from contaminating his sanity.

Sure enough, before long, he threw his head back and let loose a guttural roar with completely bloodshot eyes, looking as if he had completely lost his mind as he slashed his sword wildly through the air.

Without his control, the power of the surrounding treasures waned significantly, and the outermost light barrier was quickly torn apart by the blood ghosts.

Han Li was in the midst of fighting off blood ghosts himself when a thought suddenly occurred to him upon seeing this, and he hurriedly communicated a message to Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16 through voice transmission. "The more of these blood ghosts we kill, the more concentrated the blood in the air will become."

"Indeed. We have to get out of this place as quickly as possible. Otherwise, if this goes on for much longer, we can't guarantee that we won't also lose our minds," Wyrm 9 replied.

"Fellow daoists, I may have a way to break open this space, but I'll need you to protect me while I make some preparations," Wyrm 16 said in an urgent voice after forcing back several of the blood ghosts in front of him.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said as he reached out with his hands like lightning, grabbing onto a pair of blood ghosts before hurling them in Wyrm 16's direction, sending them crashing into a horde of blood ghosts to his left.

On the other side, Wyrm 9 sent all of the blood ghosts around him flying, then leaped up into the air before landing on Wyrm 16's right, upon which he made a hand seal and began to chant an incantation.

A burst of low rumbling rang out, and a cloud of blue water vapor emerged in front of Wyrm 9, releasing bursts of rich water-attribute spiritual power.

Immediately thereafter, he thrust his palms forward forcefully, and a draconic roar rang out as a blue water dragon rushed out of the cloud of vapor, flying directly at the horde of blood ghosts approaching from Wyrm 16's left.

Water splashed in all directions as dozens of blood ghosts were knocked over by the water dragon in the blink of an eye, plunging their formation into complete chaos.

At the same time, Han Li had already appeared on Wyrm 16's right, and he was traversing through the army of blood ghosts while lashing out with his fists, sending one blood ghost flying after another. However, while he was doing this, he was also constantly inspecting his surroundings with blue light flashing within his eyes.

With Han Li and Wyrm 9 covering him from the left and the right, Wyrm 16 immediately sat down on the spot with his legs crossed, then summoned a sharp spike in the shape of a narrow triangular pyramid with a wave of his hand. The sharp tip of the spike was pointed directly upward at the heavens.

There were circles of tiny and complex runes engraved all over the surface of the spike, and judging from the spatial fluctuations that it was giving off, it seemed to be an Acquired Immortal Treasure that possessed a hint of power of laws.

Both Han Li and Wyrm 9 were very surprised to see this.

There were very few people in the entire Black Wind Sea who were in possession of immortal treasures, and they certainly weren't expecting a layman immortal like Wyrm 16 to have one at his disposal.

After summoning the spike, Wyrm 16 folded his hands in front of him as he chanted an incantation in an unhurried manner.

Moments later, his chanting drew to a halt, and he reached out to brush his hand over the spike before him, instantly opening up a gash that began to bleed profusely.

After being stained with his blood, the spike instantly began to glow bright with crimson light as if it had been heated extensively in a furnace, and the spatial fluctuations that it was giving off also became stronger and stronger.

Right at this moment, an agonized howl suddenly rang out from a certain point in the crimson space, and Han Li and Wyrm 9 immediately turned toward the direction that the sound had come from.

As it turned out, all of the protective barriers around the middle-aged man had already been torn apart, and he was completely inundated by the hordes of blood ghosts around him.

However, in the next instant, a burst of red light suddenly appeared among the blood ghosts, then rapidly erupted up into the air, revealing itself to be the middle-aged man's nascent soul. The nascent soul was wielding a miniature crimson sword, and it was rising up into the sky with a deranged expression.

However, before it was able to get very far away, a rift suddenly opened up in one of the crimson clouds in the sky, following which a dark purple bowl flew out from within.

The bowl circled around momentarily in the sky, then released a burst of incredibly powerful suction force that instantly drew in the deranged nascent soul.

As soon as the nascent soul entered the bowl, a burst of strange force instantly converged upon it, destroying it in the blink of an eye, reducing it into a burst of red light that vanished into the bowl in a flash.

A series of glowing black runes then appeared on the surface of the bowl, and they appeared to have been engraved onto the bowl's surface.

Chapter 107: Escape

Almost as soon as the nascent soul was devoured by the bowl, a purple-robed elderly man suddenly flew out of the crimson bowl, then immediately pointed a finger at the bowl from afar.

All of the runes on the surface of the bowl instantly began to glow with dazzling black radiance while intertwining to form countless tiny patterns. Immediately thereafter, a thick beam of black light shot out of the bowl, hurtling directly toward Wyrm 16 down below.

The beam of light was traveling incredibly quickly, and having been preoccupied with the blood ghosts, it was too late for Han Li and Wyrm 9 to step in.

Wyrm 16 was at a crucial juncture in the ability that he was preparing, so he was also unable to take evasive measures.

In this dire situation, he had no choice but to adjust the angle of the spike before him so that it was pointed up at the oncoming beam of black light instead of its original target.

The spike had already turned a bright crimson color, and a burst of light had only just appeared on its tip. However, before the burst of light was able to erupt out of the tip, it was struck by the beam of black light, which exploded violently on contact.

It was as if a scintillating crimson sun had suddenly risen in front of Wyrm 16, sending bright crimson light and incredibly powerful shockwaves sweeping in all directions, forcing all of the surrounding blood mist to recede by several thousand feet.

Countless blood ghosts were sent flying by the powerful shockwaves, while Han Li and Wyrm 9 forced their way through the shockwaves as they rushed toward Wyrm 16.

However, before they were able to reach him, the crimson light faded to present a disturbing sight.

Wyrm 16 had slumped to the ground with his eyes tightly shut, seemingly having fallen unconscious. Several metal-skewer-like pillars of black light had pierced through his limbs and his torso, pinning him firmly to the ground while releasing bursts of faint law fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, a string of rumbling thunderclaps rang out from high up in the sky, and Han Li and Wyrm 9 immediately stopped cold in their tracks before shooting back in retreat.

In the next instant, a series of millstone-sized balls of crimson lightningfire came crashing down from the heavens before exploding violently, completely inundating the spot where they had been standing just a moment ago in blinding lightning.

After steadying themselves, both Han Li and Wyrm 9 looked up in unison to find that the purple-robed elderly man was holding the dark purple bowl in his hand, while his face was concealed behind a layer of red light, and lightning was flashing wildly in the crimson clouds around him.

"I knew that those bastards would've definitely had more allies to come, but I didn't think that three True Immortals would arrive here at once. What an honor this is for me. If you don't want to completely lose your sanity, then surrender yourselves for capture right away!" the elderly man chuckled in a cold voice.

"If you don't want to die, then let us out right now!" Wyrm 9 countered in an unyielding voice.

"To think that you'd still be acting so cocky even when your deaths are imminent! Let me give you two a lesson in respect at the cost of your lives!" the purple-robed elderly man cackled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the bowl in his hand flew out of his grasp before circling around in the air, and a string of rumbling thunderclaps instantly rang out within the surrounding crimson clouds. Immediately thereafter, hundreds of balls of crimson lightningfire came crashing down from the heavens like a meteor shower.

A string of deafening booms rang out one after another, causing the entire space to tremble and quake violently.

With each ball of lightningfire that crashed down onto the ground, a massive crater would be left in its wake, and huge bursts of crimson fire and lightning would erupt in all directions.

Before long, the entire area within a radius of several kilometers had been completely filled by countless bursts of crimson flames, which resembled a garden of crimson lotus flowers in full bloom, radiating astonishingly scorching temperatures.

It was unclear whether this was intentional or not, but none of the balls of lightningfire had fallen upon Wyrm 16. Instead, he was only splattered with traces of crimson flames, and the burning pain instantly roused him from his unconscious state, causing him to howl with agony.

Blue light continued to flash within Han Li's eyes as he constantly sprang from one spot to another, traversing through the blood ghosts and the storm of lightningfire, but he was still unable to avoid being struck by the haphazardly flying bursts of crimson flames.

Even with his current physical body, the flames were still causing him slight burning pain, and what was even more disturbing was that the flames also seemed to be capable of setting his blood alight, causing a sense of violent mania to well up in his heart.

However, a burst of cool and refreshing energy instantly rose up from his dantian at his behest, then circulated throughout his head to eradicate the sense of manic violence in the blink of an eye.

Not far away from Han Li, Wyrm 9 had summoned a blue gourd treasure, and bursts of watery blue light were gushing out from within to form a rippling blue light barrier around him. The barrier allowed him to ward off the crimson flames, but he was struggling to deal with the simultaneous assault from both the falling balls of lightningfire and the converging blood ghosts.

It had only taken a few seconds for the nearby space to be virtually completely inundated by crimson flames, leaving the two of them with less and less space to maneuver and evade.

During this time, more and more blood ghosts continued to rush out of the rifts on the ground, and not only did they not seem to be negatively affected by the crimson flames at all, their speed and power seemed to have been enhanced in this environment as they charged toward Han Li and Wyrm 16 with no regard for their own safety.

Wyrm 9 had only just barely dodged several balls of lightningfire when he was instantly surrounded by a horde of blood ghosts.

A grim look flashed through his eyes as he bit through the tip of his own tongue, then opened his mouth to release a burst of blood essence that vanished into the blue gourd in his hand in a flash.

The gourd instantly began to glow with dazzling blue radiance, and countless blue runes emerged on its surface while the sound of a rushing river rang out from within.

Immediately thereafter, a torrent of blue water came gushing out of the gourd's opening, then transformed into a series of blue-armored water warriors that charged toward the surrounding blood ghosts with their ice spears held aloft.

After doing all of that, he turned to Han Li before communicating a message to him through voice transmission.

"We can't let things continue like this, Wyrm 15! I'll find a way to keep that man occupied, you go and save Wyrm 16 and assist him in breaking open this space!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a hint of red light appeared in his eyes, and he shot up directly toward the purple-robed elderly man as a streak of light.

However, Han Li offered no response to this, and he didn't even seem to have heard Wyrm 9 at all.

First, he threw several punches to send the blood ghosts around him flying back through the air, then dodged a few balls of lightningfire before suddenly changing directions and flying away in a certain direction at an incredible speed.

Wyrm 9 had only just reached the purple-robed elderly man when he saw this out of the corners of his eyes, and he immediately flew into a thunderous rage.

"Wyrm 15, where the hell are you going?"

Before he had a chance to do anything else, a beam of black light shot out of the bowl in the purple-robed elderly man's head, then came hurtling directly toward his head.

He hurriedly injected more power out of his blue gourd, which released several bursts of blue light that began swirling in front of him to form a massive blue vortex.

A dull thump rang out as the beam of black light fell directly upon the center of the vortex, resulting in an explosion of black light, while the blue vortex was also rapidly shrinking amid a burst of loud rumbling.

Right at this moment, several more beams of black light came shooting out of the bowl in the purple-robed elderly man's hand, and Wyrm 9 was forced to focus solely on defending himself as he forced the blue gourd to release more bursts of blue light. As a result, he was unable to go after Han Li.

At this point, the red light in his eyes was gradually growing brighter and brighter, while the piece of white jade hanging in front of his chest had turned rather dim and wasn't as glittering and translucent as before.

"Ha! Your companion has already abandoned you! But rest assured, there's no way he'll be able to break out of this space!" the purple-robed elderly man cackled without even taking a glance at Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li was already several thousand feet away, and he suddenly raised a fist before throwing an almighty punch through the air.

A resounding boom rang out, and the entire crimson space shuddered violently as a line of bright light appeared in front of Han Li's fist, then rapidly extended into a white rift that stretched for thousands of kilometers.

The sound of a shattering mirror then rang out as the entire crimson space crumbled away from the white rift, then disintegrated into countless fragments.

All of a sudden, everyone had returned to the sky above the secluded courtyard in Heavenly Water City. There were eight blue-robed cultivators laying on the alley outside the courtyard, and there were several array plates strewn on the ground next to them.

They were naturally the ones who had summoned and were controlling the crimson space, and what was quite surprising was that all of them were Body Integration cultivators. They seemed to have suffered some type of backlash from the destruction of the crimson space, and not only had they fallen unconscious, there was blood flowing out of all of their orifices, making them appear as if they were on the verge of death.

Inside the courtyard, Wyrm 16's entire body was charred black, and he was leaning against the withered old tree in a completely still manner.

The black skewers of light impaling his body had already disappeared, and his aura was rather unstable, but it seemed that he wasn't in any life-threatening danger.

All of a sudden, a burst of dazzling light erupted in the sky above the courtyard, and two figures emerged before shooting back in different directions.

One of those figures was Wyrm 9, and the red light in his eyes was gradually fading. As a result, clarity was restored in his mind, and an elated look appeared on his face.

In contrast, the purple-robed elderly man on the other side wore an extremely dark expression, and he turned to Han Li with intense resentment in his eyes.

Han Li appeared to be the weakest of the trio, so never did he think that Han Li would be able to identify the most fragile point in the array and destroy the entire array in a single strike.

The crimson space was far more stable than the average array, and even if an ordinary immortal could identify the fragile points within it, there was still no guarantee that they would be able to break the array open.

However, this wasn't the time to be pondering such matters. The purple-robed elderly man quickly thrust a palm against the bottom of the bowl in his hand, and waves of strange ripples that were visible to the naked eye rapidly spread through the area.

A string of dull thumps rang out from within the alley as the heads of all of the unconscious Body Integration cultivators exploded one after another.

Immediately thereafter, their nascent souls were drawn in by bursts of strange ripples, flying into the bowl as streaks of crimson light before being pulverized in the blink of an eye.

The only exception came in the form of one of the Body Integration cultivators, around whom a layer of white light had appeared. It seemed that he was carrying some type of treasure that was able to ward off the effects of those strange ripples, thereby preventing his head from exploding. The purple-robed elderly man faltered slightly upon seeing this, but he had no time to dwell on such trivial matters as he quickly lashed out.

The black runes on the surface of the bowl began to glow brightly once again, and two even thicker beams of light erupted out from within, hurtling directly toward Han Li and Wyrm 9.

The spiritual patterns on the surface of the blue gourd in Wyrm 9's hand flashed for an instant, and a thick pillar of water erupted out of the gourd's opening.

A resounding boom rang out as the black light and blue water exploded violently, sending water splashing down in all directions.

Wyrm 9 was sent flying back several hundred feet by the resulting shockwaves before finally managing to steady himself, while Han Li was also forced to take evasive measures against the beam of black light directed at him.

By the time both of them had steadied themselves, the purple-robed elderly man was already nowhere to be seen.

Chapter 108: Strange

Han Li remained on the spot for a moment before quickly arriving beside Wyrm 16, then helped him into an upright position before feeding him a pill.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist."

Wyrm 16's wounds were quite severe, and after giving Han Li a quick nod of gratitude, he immediately sat down with his legs crossed to digest the pill and recover from his injuries.

Meanwhile, following the disappearance of the purple-robed elderly man, Wyrm 9 suddenly flew down to the only surviving Body Integration cultivator in the alley next to the courtyard.

Before the Body Integration cultivator had a chance to say anything, Wyrm 9 reached out with one hand like lightning and grabbed onto the man's head with his fingers curled up into claws. Blue light flashed from the palms of his hand, and the Body Integration cultivator instantly fell unconscious.

In the next instant, a horrified red nascent soul was forcibly dragged out of the man's head through the use of some type of secret technique, and it was enveloped within a burst of blue light with a pair of heavy-lidded eyes, appearing to be in a very weak and lethargic state.

Wyrm 9 carried the nascent soul back into the courtyard, and he took a glance at the seated Wyrm 16 before turning his gaze toward Han Li.

"I didn't think that you would be such an expert in arrays, Fellow Daoist. I thought you were deserting the battle, but it seems that I was too eager to jump to conclusions. Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist," Wyrm 9 said.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. I'm no expert in arrays, I just so happened to have been able to find a fragile point within that space. It's all thanks to your efforts in keeping that layman immortal occupied that I had the opportunity to break open the array," Han Li replied with a smile.

Wyrm 9 didn't speak any further on this matter, and he turned to the nascent soul in his hand with a cold look in his eyes, then raised his other hand.

A plume of thick black threads shot out of his palm before piercing directly into the nascent soul's head.

The nascent soul shuddered as it let loose an agonized howl, but Wyrm 9 remained completely unmoved as more black threads shot out of his palm before surging into the nascent soul's head.

The nascent soul's voice became weaker and weaker, and the look on its face also became more wooden and dazed.

Wyrm 9's brows furrowed slightly as if he were displeased by something, and the number of black threads surging out of his palm abruptly increased drastically.

Right at this moment, a layer of translucent light suddenly appeared over the nascent soul's body, causing it to become semi-transparent.

An alarmed look immediately appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to say anything, the nascent soul exploded into countless specks of translucent light.

A dark look appeared on Wyrm 9's face upon seeing this.

"It looks like some type of restriction was placed upon his nascent soul, and that restriction is triggered when a soul search technique is used on him. Did you manage to find anything, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li asked as he heaved a faint sigh.

"I didn't manage to find anything useful. Given that he was only a Body Integration cultivator, he most likely wouldn't have known much anyway. However, I can confirm that the Transient Guild members who were previously here have already been killed by them," Wyrm 9 replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"What do we do now?" Wyrm 16 asked as he rose to his feet.

At this point, he had already recovered somewhat from his injuries.

"Let's conduct a thorough search of this city first. Our covers have already been blown, so we don't need to sneak around anymore," Wyrm 9 replied.

……

Meanwhile.

A dark red louchuan was speeding through a blanket of dark clouds in the sky tens of thousands of kilometers away from Heavenly Water City.

The louchuan had a total of two levels, each of which had several independent rooms. There were several wing designs engraved onto the louchuan, forming eight pairs of giant red wings that were flapping rapidly.

In one of the rooms on the top floor of the louchuan was the purple-robed elderly man who had fought against Han Li's trio not long ago, and he was seated on the ground with his legs crossed and a dark look on his face.

After a brief moment of silence, he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized jade plate, then tapped it a few times, upon which a burst of red light appeared on its surface, accompanied by a rather coarse voice.

"How did it go, Chou Wu?"

"I've already fought with the people sent by the Transient Guild," the purple-robed elderly man replied in an expressionless manner.

"I see. Then it's just as I expected," the voice in the jade plate replied in a smug manner.

"The overall power of the people they sent far exceeded what you predicted! There were two Layman Immortals and an Earthly Immortal! If I didn't have some tricks up my sleeve, I could've easily met my demise there! Even though I managed to escape, one of my subordinates still fell into their hands," the purple-robed elderly man grumbled in an incensed voice.

"Oh? Does that subordinate know anything?" The voice in the jade plate also faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"He's just a Body Integration cultivator, what could he possibly know?" the purple-robed elderly man scoffed in a disdainful voice.

"Good. So three True Immortals were sent to your side alone. Looks like the Transient Guild really is coming after us this time. If they decide to back down, then both sides will be spared a lot of trouble, but if they continue to present themselves as a pest, then the holy lord will teach them a good lesson. Thanks for your hard work, you can come back now," the voice in the jade plate instructed.

The purple-robed elderly man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, clearly quite displeased that the owner of the voice in the jade plate was issuing him orders, but he didn't say anything and put an end to the voice transmission.

After that, he made a hand seal, and the red light radiating from the louchuan brightened considerably as it accelerated even further.

……

In a certain stone hall in Heavenly Water City.

This was quite a large area, but it was rather empty inside. There were rows of stone pillars standing on either side of the hall, at the tops of which sat a series of unlit braziers.

At this moment, Han Li's trio was standing at the entrance of the hall, and their masks had already reverted back to their original forms.

Seeing as they no longer had any qualms about being discovered, they were able to release their spiritual sense without any inhibitions, allowing them to quickly complete an exhaustive search of the entire city. As a result, they discovered no cultivators above the Spatial Tempering Stage in the city, nor abnormal activity that was worthy of note. However, they did discover this stone hall in a secluded area in the southern part of the city.

At the center of the hall were three corpses placed together in an orderly fashion. All three corpses were completely shriveled up with their faces warped and distorted, as if they had seen something extremely terrifying right before they died. Furthermore, there were also several azure masks that were similar to the ones worn by Han Li's trio placed next to the bodies.

Judging from how shriveled up these bodies were, it looked as if they had had all of their blood sucked dry in an instant.

The fact that these bodies had been placed in this stone hall without any effort made to conceal them indicated that this was a clear act of provocation.

"These must be the guild members who infiltrated the island before us," Wyrm 9 remarked as he inspected the bodies and their masks.

"One of them was at the Grand Ascension Stage, while the other two were at the Body Integration Stage. It looks like they were killed in an instant, and not even their nascent souls were able to escape. I presume this was done by that Layman Immortal we fought earlier. However, thinking back, it seems like he was able to use some power of laws," Han Li said with a contemplative expression as his gaze roamed over the three bodies.

"Looks like Gongshu Hong was already prepared. He set up a meticulous trap, and we fell right into it," Wyrm 16 said in a resentful voice.

"Now's not the time to be dwelling on things like that. It looks like we won't be able to find any useful information in Heavenly Water City. Before we leave, we have to inform Wyrm 3 of the situation, then discuss how to proceed from here," Wyrm 9 said.

After that, he made a hand seal, and a layer of blue ripples emerged over his blue goat mask. The mask then began to flash erratically before abruptly lighting up.

Wyrm 9 immediately closed his eyes, and his lips began to quiver as he communicated a message through voice transmission.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Wyrm 16 stood silently off to the side.

A short while later, the light glowing from Wyrm 9's mask faded, and he opened his eyes.

"What did Wyrm 3 say?" Wyrm 16 immediately asked.

"He instructed us to travel to Dragon Lake City right away to meet up with him," Wyrm 9 replied.

"Have they been attacked as well?" Han Li asked.

"The city that Wyrm 3 and the other fellow daoist are traveling to is quite far away, so they still haven't gotten there yet. However, judging from the situation here, the guild members that they're supposed to meet up with are most likely already dead as well. Now that they're aware of the situation, it won't be that easy for the enemy to catch them off guard," Wyrm 9 replied.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't ask any further questions.

"There's no point in staying here any longer, so let's go." Wyrm 9 swept a hand through the air to release a burst of blue light that swept up the bodies and stowed them into a storage tool, then began to make his way outside.

The trio departed from the stone hall, then quickly left Heavenly Water City and arrived on a barren plain.

Wyrm 16 was just about to unleash a self-concealment secret technique when he was stopped by Wyrm 9.

"There's no need for that. Wyrm 3 says that seeing as the enemy is already aware of our presence on the island, there's no need to bother with concealing ourselves anymore. We can go straight to Dragon Lake City."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and blue waves appeared out of thin air in all directions, while a blue flying ark that was over 100 feet in length emerged up ahead. The flying ark was completely translucent, and it was extremely sleek in design with spiritual light radiating from its surface.

Wyrm 16 faltered slightly upon seeing the flying ark, following which a hint of envy appeared in his eyes.

"This entire boat is constructed from Blue Skycloud Crystal. It's not an immortal treasure, but it can't be too far away," Han Li praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. This is only a mere spirit treasure, it can't even begin to compare with an immortal treasure," Wyrm 9 chuckled.

The power that Han Li had displayed during the recently concluded battle had greatly impressed Wyrm 9, and he was unconsciously speaking in a more polite manner to Han Li as a result.

"This flying ark is decently fast and will suffice as a mode of transport. Wyrm 16, try to recover as quickly as possible. I'm sure there are going to be more hard battles to come," Wyrm 9 said as he leaped onto the front of the ark.

Wyrm 16 nodded in response, then also flew onto the ark with Han Li.

With a wave of his hand, Wyrm 9 released an incantation seal, and the blue light radiating from the flying ark brightened considerably as it shot through the air as a streak of blue light.

……

Dragon Lake City was a far larger city than Heavenly Water City. There was a lake in the city that took up over 1,000 acres in area, and it was connected to several large rivers in the city, which flowed all the way out of the city.

It was morning at the moment, and there were many people traversing through the city, presenting a lively and bustling sight.

By the time Han Li's trio arrived in the city, then traveled to a secluded estate in the western part of the city, everyone else had already arrived, but by the looks of it, Wyrm 8's trio had only just arrived as well.

Wyrm 9 provided Wyrm 3 with a detailed recount of events pertaining to the ambush they had suffered in Heavenly Water City, then released the bodies of the Transient Guild members who had previously infiltrated the island.

A cold look appeared in Wyrm 3's eyes at the sight of the shriveled-up bodies on the ground, and everyone else's expressions also changed slightly upon seeing this.

Chapter 109: Exploring Red Moon City

"They were already like this by the time we discovered them. We speculate that they were most likely killed by the same Layman Immortal that ambushed us," Wyrm 9 said as he withdrew his gaze from the bodies on the ground.

"After hearing about what happened to your group, Wyrm 8 and I also arrived at our destinations, and as expected, all of the guild members who infiltrated the island before have already disappeared," Wyrm 3 said in a grim voice.

"On the way here, we didn't discover anything abnormal aside from the deserted cities, where the residents supposedly traveled to the holy city for the pilgrimage. As for the pilgrimage itself, the results of our investigation are much the same as what Wyrm 9 and the others found; it's most likely just a way for Gongshu Hong to collect the power of faith," Wyrm 8 said after a brief moment of contemplation.

"Did you also hear that the so-called most devout followers out of the people attending the pilgrimage will be chosen, and that those chosen ones won't return to the cities that they once lived in?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"We did indeed hear about that as well. Apparently, they'll be taken to another city with more fertile land. Perhaps that's just a method that Gongshu Hong employs to increase the level of devotion that his followers feel toward him," Wyrm 8 replied in a nonchalant manner, then changed the subject as he continued, "On the way here, neither Wyrm 3 nor my group was ambushed by the enemy, so it seems that Gongshu Hong has already been wary of our Transient Guild for quite some time. In light of that, I believe it's necessary for us to reassess the accuracy of the information that the guild has previously received about Red Moon Island,"

"Indeed. Perhaps Gongshu Hong is already aware that we're on Red Moon Island, and he intentionally spread false information to lure us to the wrong places. However, it seems that he underestimated our overall power. Setting aside everything else for now, I think it's safe to conclude that Gongshu Hong definitely won't be at any of the six or seven places annotated on the map.

“Instead, there may actually be a chance that he's in Red Moon City right now, so we might as well go and take a look there. Perhaps we'll be able to find something," Wyrm 9 suggested.

"Speaking of that, Red Moon Island has a total of 28 provinces, and almost every one of them has a city by the name of Red Moon City," Wyrm 8 said with a shake of his head.

"Really?" Wyrm 9 was very much taken aback to hear this.

"There's a place by the name of Red Moon City marked on the map that we received, but as we were passing through a certain city, we discovered by chance that the Red Moon City that they were referring to was somewhere else entirely. Initially, we didn't really take it to heart, thinking that they had merely misspoken, but that wasn't the case.

“Even though we only passed through several provinces, we made sure to keep an eye out, and we discovered that each of the provinces that we passed through has a Red Moon City," Wyrm 8 said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing five jade slips that flew toward Han Li and the others.

Everyone caught the jade slips before injecting their spiritual sense into them.

There were many more annotated locations on the map in the jade slip than the previously obtained, and sure enough, aside from the originally marked-out Red Moon City, there was another Red Moon City annotated in each of the provinces that Wyrm 8's group had passed through.

Each province was extremely vast, so if the high-grade cultivators in those provinces intentionally kept this a secret, there was no way that any mortals or even low-grade cultivators would’ve been able to find out the existence of the other Red Moon Cities.

"The cities that we passed through on the way here only sold maps of certain areas, but there are no maps of the entire island being sold, and it seems that this was entirely by Gongshu Hong's design.

“His subordinates most likely have some type of special restriction placed upon them, making them unable to disclose this matter to anyone. I think it's even reasonable to speculate that the map that we originally obtained was intentionally leaked to us by Gongshu Hong," Wyrm 9 mused.

Everyone fell silent upon hearing this.

Given all of this new information that had come to light, Gongshu Hong's whereabouts had become a complete mystery, making it very difficult for them to proceed with the mission.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to Han Li, and he pressed the jade slip against his own forehead again as a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

"Seeing as we have no other leads, let's begin by investigating those Red Moon Cities. Mobilize everyone and check out those Red Moon Cities one by one," Wyrm 3 instructed.

Wyrm 9 faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Are you not going to come with us, Wyrm 3?"

"I'll act on my own. If you find out anything, then just convey the information to me through voice transmission," Wyrm 3 replied, following which a burst of red light emerged over his body, and flew up into the sky before flying toward a certain direction, making no attempt to conceal his aura.

"Looks like Wyrm 3 intends to openly search for Gongshu Hong. Let's follow his instructions. We're currently in the Wave Province, and we're not too far away from the Red Moon City in this province," Wyrm 8 said.

Thus, everyone immediately adopted different faces using their masks, then mingled into the crowd before leaving the city.

As they were passing by a certain street, Han Li suddenly said, "Please wait here for me for a moment, I have some errands that I need to run. My apologies for the inconvenience."

He then quickly made his way into the shop that sold all types of books before anyone had a chance to respond.

Everyone faltered slightly upon seeing this, but they all exchanged a quick glance with one another and didn't say anything.

It didn't take long before Han Li emerged from the shop with a few books in his hand, and they seemed to be books on the geographic environment of this island.

"Sorry to keep you all waiting," Han Li said as he stowed the books away in front of everyone.

The group quickly departed from Dragon Lake City, then made their way to a secluded place before rising up into the sky.

Wyrm 9 released that translucent blue flying ark once again as a mode of transport for himself, as well as Wyrm 16 and Han Li, attracting a great deal of attention from Wyrm 8 and the others.

Han Li stood on the spirit ark as he took a glance down at a river near Dragon Lake City, then sat down with his legs crossed and pulled out the books that he had just purchased before carefully reading through them.

Wyrm 16 was rather perplexed by Han Li's actions, but he paid Han Li no heed as he continued to recover from his injuries.

Han Li quickly read through the books that he had purchased, and after some contemplation, he pulled out the jade slip that Wyrm 8 had given to everyone earlier before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

At this point, the sky was gradually beginning to darken, and some stars had appeared up above.

The group of seven traveled for close to an entire day before stopping in front of a large city.

This city was none other than the Red Moon City of the Wave Province, and it was even larger than Dragon Lake City, with a huge river that was several thousand feet wide flowing through it.

The entire city was enshrouded under an enormous blue restriction that occasionally rippled with surges of translucent light, presenting a rather mysterious sight to behold. Through the blue light barrier, only a faint outline of the city could be made out.

However, there were openings in the restrictions corresponding with the locations of the four city gates situated in the north, south, east, and west, allowing people to enter and exit the city.

Blue-robed cultivators were situated at each of the four city gates, examining the people who wished to enter or exit the city.

"If I'm not mistaken, this should be the vastly renowned Thousand Light Illusory Ripple Restriction. The restriction's defensive properties aren't very remarkable, but it's extremely sensitive to spiritual sense," Wyrm 8 mused as he inspected the restriction.

"If this city is so heavily guarded, is there a chance that this is the Red Moon City that we're searching for?" Wyrm 21 speculated as an elated look appeared on his face.

Everyone else's eyes also lit up upon hearing this.

"Regardless of whether it is or not, let's go in and take a look first. Make sure to be on your guard at all times and rein in your spiritual sense as much as possible so you don't trigger any arrays or restrictions," Wyrm 8 instructed.

A hint of displeasure flashed through Wyrm 9's eyes upon hearing this, clearly discontent with taking orders from Wyrm 8, but he didn't say anything.

The seven of them descended upon a secluded spot outside the city, then made their way into the crowd of people who were entering the city.

There were Deity Transformation cultivators stationed at the city gate, but they were naturally unable to see through the disguises adopted by Han Li and the others, and the seven of them successfully entered the city.

The ground in the city was paved with large slabs of bluestone in a neat and orderly fashion, and the streets were lined with shops, presenting a thriving sight to behold.

The four city gates were connected by a pair of wide roads, which split up the entire city into four areas. At the center of the city was a massive plaza, at the center of which stood a huge statue.

At this moment, the city was absolutely packed with people, as were the massive plaza at the center of the city and all of the streets and roads. At the very least, the city had to have been holding several million people.

All of those people were currently reverently worshiping the statue at the center of the plaza, and the entire city was filled with a solemn atmosphere.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing, and he, along with everyone else, quickly realized what was happening.

This was most likely the so-called pilgrimage that they had been hearing about.

Blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes as he inspected his surroundings, following which his brows immediately furrowed slightly.

There was a massive number of people in the city, but most of them were mortals who possessed no magic power. There were some cultivators among them, but they were all low-grade cultivators ranging between the Qi Condensation Stage and the Core Formation Stage.

There were also some blue-robed cultivators in the city, but none of them possessed advanced cultivation bases, either. Just like the cultivators stationed at the city gates, these blue-robed cultivators were all at the Nascent Soul Stage or the Deity Transformation Stage, and there wasn't even a single Spatial Tempering cultivator among them.

It seemed like this wasn't the place that they were searching for.

At this point, everyone else had clearly also noticed this, and their expressions immediately darkened slightly.

"In any case, we should examine this city thoroughly. Perhaps we'll be able to find some leads," Wyrm 8 proposed.

Everyone else nodded in agreement, and after a brief discussion, they decided to split up.

The city was too massive, and Han Li and the others couldn't just use their spiritual sense to scour large areas at once. In any case, everyone was in the city, so even if there were any enemies lurking in ambush, they would've been within sufficiently close proximity to one another to provide reinforcements.

Thus, the decision was made, and everyone quickly split up.

Han Li made his way along a certain street, inspecting everything in the surrounding area with blue light flashing within his eyes.

His body had taken on a semi-tangible form, allowing him to blend into his environment.

All of the people on the street were worshiping the statue, so he would've stuck out like a sore thumb walking along the street on his own, and that was why he had decided to employ this concealment technique.

Moments later, Han Li appeared in front of a shop on the side of the street, and it was another bookshop.

At the moment, the entire city was observing the pilgrimage, so even though the shop was open, there weren't any customers inside, only a middle-aged manager looking after the shop.

Han Li flew into the shop, then re-emerged moments later.

After that, he made no further stops and began to carefully explore the city.

Due to how massive the city was, it took the seven of them close to half a day to examine the entire city, following which they gathered back together in a secluded area in the city.

Unfortunately, none of them were able to dig up any useful information.

It seemed that this city was completely unremarkable aside from its enormous size.

"Looks like this isn't the Red Moon City that we're looking for. In that case, we shouldn't waste any more time here..."

Right at this moment, Wyrm 25 suddenly spoke up to interrupt Wyrm 8. "Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 8, there's something rather strange underground here."

At this moment, Wyrm 25 was crouched down onto the ground, and a series of yellow ripples that were visible to the naked eye were emanating from his body before vanishing into the ground down below.

Chapter 110: Leads

"Did you manage to find something down there?" Wyrm 8 hurriedly asked as an elated look appeared in his eyes.

"I suggest all of you take a look at what's 1,000 feet under here," Wyrm 25 said as he stood up straight again.

Everyone immediately released their spiritual sense before directing it into the ground beneath their feet, following which their eyes quickly lit up.

There was a large underground cavity directly beneath them, and it had clearly been artificially constructed.

"It's a good thing that you have such great attention to detail. Otherwise, we would've missed this entirely," Wyrm 8 praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. I just so happen to be using a special cultivation art that gives me heightened sensitivity to what's underground," Wyrm 25 replied with a modest smile.

"Let's go and take a look down there." Wyrm 8 didn't say anything further and led the way down underground.

The other two members of his team immediately followed along, as did Wyrm 25.

Soon, Han Li's trio were the only ones left still on the surface.

Wyrm 9 was looking rather displeased, and he didn't immediately follow Wyrm 8 and the others underground.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 exchanged a glance before also choosing to remain on the spot.

Even though the seven of them were operating together, certain factions had been formed among them due to the teams assigned by Wyrm 3.

After a brief moment of silence, a burst of blue light appeared over Wyrm 9's body, and he also vanished into the ground down below.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 quickly followed suit, and a short while later, they arrived in that underground cavity.

The space within the underground cavity was quite large, standing at a radius of at least tens of thousands of feet.

The ground was very smooth and even, and it was entirely paved with bluestone slabs to form a circular underground plaza. It seemed that it had already been a very long time since anyone had visited this area.

Everyone couldn't help but exchange a few glances upon seeing this.

Han Li briefly inspected his surroundings, then took a whiff of the air in the underground cavity to find that it was very damp here. In addition to that, there was a faint bloody odor wafting through the air alongside an indistinct yin aura.

He crouched down before plunging his fingers into one of the bluestone slabs on the ground, then pulled it up to reveal the dark red earth down below, upon which he discovered that the dark red soil was tinged with a faint layer of black.

Han Li picked up a handful of soil, then tossed it away after a brief inspection.

"Did you discover something, Wyrm 15?" Wyrm 16 asked.

"No, I just feel like this place is rather strange. The faint odor of blood and the yin aura in here indicates that many people seem to have died here, and even the soil beneath these stone slabs has been tainted to become yin soil," Han Li mused with a contemplative expression.

"Perhaps this is a place that was specifically constructed to deal with enemies," Wyrm 16 speculated.

Han Li shook his head in response. Enemies of the island could've been killed anywhere, so why was it necessary to construct this massive underground chamber as an execution site?

He felt like there was something very suspicious about this, but he couldn't pinpoint exactly what was wrong here.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 8 and the others were also speculating about what this underground space could've been used for.

"There's a simple solution to this. If we want to know why there's an underground space here, all we need to do is capture someone and interrogate them," Wyrm 9 suddenly said, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a small yellow flag, which vanished into the ceiling of the underground cavity in a flash.

Somewhere on the edge of the plaza in Red Moon City, a blue-robed middle-aged cultivator at the Nascent Soul Stage was patrolling the city and maintaining order.

All of a sudden, a burst of yellow light flashed beneath his feet, and a large yellow hand shot out like lightning, closing itself around his legs before dragging him down into the ground.

At the same time, a series of yellow ripples emerged on the ground beneath his feet, transforming the hard stone material into a swamp-like consistency.

Thus, the middle-aged man vanished into the ground in the blink of an eye, and the yellow ripples on the ground also disappeared immediately thereafter.

Everyone was focused wholeheartedly on the pilgrimage, so no one noticed what had just happened.

Yellow light flashed on the ceiling above the underground plaza, and the middle-aged man tumbled down before falling onto the ground.

His expression immediately changed at the sight of Han Li's group, but his body was enshrouded in a layer of yellow light that prevented him from moving and making any sound.

Wyrm 9 grabbed onto the man's head, and countless black threads shot out of his palm before vanishing into the man's head.

The man's facial muscles twisted and spasmed painfully as blood began to seep out of his orifices, but Wyrm 9 paid that no heed as he continued to release more black threads out of his palm with a cold expression.

Moments later, the middle-aged man's body abruptly shuddered, and a dull thump rang out within his head, as if something had exploded in there.

Immediately thereafter, his aura completely faded, as did the light in his eyes.

A dark look appeared on Wyrm 9's face.

As was the case with the Body Integration cultivator that he had captured in Heavenly Water City, this man's soul had also had a restriction placed upon it, leading to automatic self-detonation as soon as certain memories were encroached upon through the use of soul search techniques.

"Even if there were no restrictions placed on the souls of these cultivators, a Nascent Soul cultivator wouldn't have known much anyway. There's not much point in continuing to stay here. I suggest we move on to the next Red Moon City right away," Wyrm 8 said with a hint of mockery in his eyes.

After that, he rose up into the air and vanished into the stone ceiling up above, followed immediately by the three people beside him.

Wyrm 9 gave a cold harrumph, then also departed from the underground cavity with Han Li and Wyrm 16.

A short while later, the group of seven departed from the city and traveled to the next Red Moon City.

……

Several days later, the seven of them arrived in front of another city that was enshrouded under an enormous blue restriction, and this one was right next to a massive lake.

To call it a lake wasn't entirely accurate. In reality, it was connected to the sea, making it technically an inland sea.

Outside the city was a series of connected docks with thousands of ships and boats entering and exiting, presenting a breathtaking spectacle to behold.

This was the Red Moon City of the Feng province, and it was also already the sixth Red Moon City that they had visited in the past few days.

Every single one of those cities had been the same as the Red Moon City in Lan. Aside from the residents of the cities observing the pilgrimage and the underground space that each city possessed, there was nothing abnormal or worthy of note.

The seven of them landed outside the city before sneaking their way inside.

Once again, this city had two main roads that connected the four city gates, with a massive circular plaza at the center of the city.

This city was also absolutely packed with people, and the plaza was laden with worshippers who had come to attend the pilgrimage from all over the province.

Han Li briefly inspected his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and a hint of dismay quickly appeared on his face.

Just like the previous few Red Moon Cities, there were no high-grade cultivators in this city at all. Once again, this was most likely a red herring and a complete waste of time.

Wyrm 8 was just about to say something when a faint breeze swept past him, and Wyrm 9 had already taken Han Li and Wyrm 16 deeper into the city.

A cold look flashed through Wyrm 8's eyes, but he didn't say anything as he led the three people accompanying him down another path.

Moments later, Han Li's trio arrived in a secluded corner.

Right as they were about to split up and go off on their own, Wyrm 9 suddenly said to Han Li and Wyrm 16, "There's an unofficial rule in the guild that those who make important contributions in missions will be given additional rewards, and these rewards are often extremely bountiful.

“Even though we don't have many leads at this point, make sure to constantly be on the lookout so the reward doesn't fall into the hands of Wyrm 8 and the others."

Han Li and Wyrm 16 faltered slightly upon hearing this, then cupped their fists in a salute toward Wyrm 9.

"Thank you for your guidance, Fellow Daoist."

Wyrm 9 nodded in response before departing in a certain direction, and Wyrm 16 also did the same after hurriedly bidding farewell to Han Li, seemingly very eager to claim this reward for himself.

Meanwhile, Han Li made his way down another street, and his gaze was constantly roaming over the shops on either side of the street as if he were searching for something.

At this point, the pilgrimage seemed to be about to draw to a conclusion soon, and many people had begun walking through the city, so he didn't have to employ a concealment technique.

A short while later, Han Li made his way into a shop on the side of the street, and this was yet another bookshop.

The shop was quite large, with a total of four levels. There were three rooms on the first floor, each of which was around 40 to 50 feet wide, and they were packed with bookshelves.

Due to the ongoing pilgrimage, business was quite slow, and there weren’t many customers in the shop.

"What can I help you with?" A portly middle-aged man with a well-maintained mustache immediately approached Han Li with a warm smile, and it seemed like he was the shopkeeper of the bookshop.

"Do you have any old maps or books on geography? The older, the better," Han Li replied as he glanced at the bookshelves in the shop.

A peculiar look flashed through the shopkeeper's eyes, but the expression only lingered for an instant before he replied in a calm manner, "We do have maps here, but none of them are very old."

Even though the change in the shopkeeper's expression was only present for a split-second, it naturally didn't escape Han Li's attention.

Intrigued by this development, a layer of translucent light appeared in his eyes, and the shopkeeper's eyes instantly took on a dazed look at the sight of Han Li's eyes.

"Bring me the oldest maps and geography books that you have here," Han Li instructed.

"Yes," the shopkeeper replied in a wooden manner, then turned and made his way deeper into the shop.

Han Li followed along behind the shopkeeper, and a short while later, he emerged from the shop with a book that had a brown cover.

The pages of the book seemed to have been made of some type of beast hide, and it appeared to be an extremely old book.

As Han Li flipped through the pages of the book, a hint of excitement appeared in his eyes.

Close to half a day later, the group of seven met back up again, and all of them were looking rather frustrated.

They hadn't discovered anything in this city, and the underground space here was also completely empty, so no leads had been gathered.

"Where the hell is he? Are we really just going to have to keep searching for him indefinitely on this island?" Wyrm 21 grumbled.

"Don't get disheartened. Gongshu Hong may have gone into hiding, but this is his stronghold. There are only less than 30 Red Moon Cities in total. If we search through them one by one, we'll be sure to find some leads. Next, we'll go to the Red Moon City in the Zang province," Wyrm 8 said before turning to depart.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly spoke up. "Please wait a moment, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 8, I may have found some leads pertaining to Gongshu Hong 's whereabouts."

Everyone immediately turned to him upon hearing this, and an elated look appeared in Wyrm 9's eyes as he hurriedly asked, "What have you found?"

Han Li extended a finger forward, and a screen of light that was depicting an image appeared in front of him.

"Please take a look, everyone," Han Li said.

Everyone turned to the light screen to find that there was a map of the island displayed on it. It was very similar to the map of the island that Wyrm 8 had previously presented to everyone, except this one was a bit more detailed.

"Isn't this the map that Fellow Daoist Wyrm 8 has already distributed to everyone? We've already seen it," Wyrm 25 scoffed with a hint of disdain in his voice.

Everyone else was also rather perplexed.

However, Wyrm 8 and Wyrm 9 seemed to be quite intrigued by what they were seeing.

Chapter 111: Divine Selection

"It looks like you two have noticed the difference. The previous map didn't appear to have any issues, but none of the major bodies of water on the island were presented on that map, and that's because those bodies of water aren't marked out on the maps being publicly sold. In contrast, I've marked out all of the major bodies of water that we've passed by on the way here on this updated map," Han Li explained with a smile.

Everyone turned back to give the map a closer look upon hearing this.

Sure enough, just as Han Li proclaimed, the previous map provided by Wyrm 8 was quite detailed, but there were very few bodies of water marked out on it, and even the ones that were marked out were only small rivers and lakes.

Everyone's attention had been drawn to the cities prior to this, so no one had noticed this.

"During these past few days, I made sure to gather some information on the island's geographic environment from all of the cities that we visited. In particular, I tracked down all of the old maps that I could, and I was finally able to find some information related to these major bodies of water," Han Li said.

He then extended a finger forward once again, and a series of large rivers appeared on certain parts of the map depicted on the light screen.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this.

"Due to the short timeframe, this is all of the information that I was able to gather on the major bodies of water. Now that it's all laid out in front of you, I'm sure you've also noticed that all of the Red Moon Cities that we've passed through and some other large cities have all been situated next to large bodies of water. This is something that we've personally seen these past few days, so we can verify this to be true," Han Li explained.

Everyone thought back to the cities that they had visited during the past few days, and sure enough, they had all been in close proximity to a large river or lake, as was the case with the Red Moon City that they were currently in.

"Surely that doesn't mean anything though. There are many advantages to building cities near large bodies of water, and that's certainly not something that's unique to the Red Moon Cities on this island," Wyrm 13 countered.

"That's true, but through an enchantment that I cast on the shopkeeper of a bookshop in this city, I found out from him that all images depicting the major bodies of water on the island are strictly prohibited on all books being sold on the island, and this order was issued by Gongshu Hong himself. It's clear that he's trying to hide something," Han Li said.

Wyrm 13 had no counterargument to this.

"I don't know why Gongshu Hong is doing this, but looking at all of the major bodies of water that have already been marked out on the map, they converge at this point," Han Li continued as he pointed at a city on the map.

That city was none other than the Red Moon City of the Kun province.

"This is all just speculation. Can you be certain that that's where Gongshu Hong is?" Wyrm 25 asked in a skeptical voice.

"Of course I can't be certain, but wouldn't it be much better to take a look there first instead of continuing on a completely aimless search? At the very least, we'll have slightly better chances there," Han Li replied.

Wyrm 25 opened his mouth as if he wanted to rebuke Han Li, but he was unable to find the words to do so.

"That makes a lot of sense to me! If you hadn't discovered, we would've still been completely in the dark," Wyrm 9 said in an elated voice.

After joining forces with all of the other guild members, he had always felt outmatched by Wyrm 8, and he was very pleased to have finally scored a victory of sorts over Wyrm 8 and his group.

"I fully agree with Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15's proposal. If we really go and search through all of the Red Moon Cities one by one, Gongshu Hong would've most likely already been tipped off long before we get to him, and he'll go into hiding somewhere else where we can't find him. We really do have to thank Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15 for making this discovery" Wyrm 16 said.

"You're far too kind, fellow daoists. I only happened to stumble upon this discovery by chance," Han Li said with a modest smile.

After a moment of contemplation, Wyrm 8 declared, "Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15's theory is very sound. Let's go to the Kun province."

……

One night, several days later.

Two streaks of light flashed through the night sky above a vast plain, then descended onto the outskirts of a forest down below.

The two streaks of light faded to reveal a pair of flying arks, and Han Li's group flew down in their animal masks.

"Up ahead is the Red Moon City of the Kun province. It looks like there's a pilgrimage going on in that city as well," Wyrm 8 said as he pointed up ahead.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the direction that Wyrm 8 was pointing in, and he saw a massive, brightly lit city standing in the night close to 10 kilometers away.

The city was illuminated by crimson lights that had also stained the clouds in the night sky up above the same color, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

This city was also enshrouded under a blue light barrier, but under the influence of the crimson lights, the blue light barrier was leaning toward a shade of dark red.

"This is an enormous city. It looks like there really is a chance that this is where Gongshu Hong is hiding," Wyrm 9 mused as he inspected the city before him.

"Let's not delay any further. Just like in the past, let's all refrain from using our spiritual sense as much as possible after entering the city," Wyrm 8 said.

Wyrm 9 naturally chose to ignore those orders, while everyone else nodded silently in response.

Moments later, everyone had adopted disguises using their masks and donned black cloaks that allowed them to blend into the night.

After that, they approached Red Moon City in silence.

At this moment, the city's four gates were wide open, and the main roads leading to the plaza at the center of the city were lined with red lanterns that illuminated the entire city to be as bright as day.

There were thousands of people making their way along the official roads outside the city gates, and they were rushing quickly toward the city. They had all traveled to Red Moon City to attend the pilgrimage, but all of them were a little late due to one reason or another.

Han Li and the others split up into two groups, then joined the crowd to enter the city through the gates.

Han Li, Wyrm 9, and Wyrm 16 entered the city through the southern gate, then followed the flow of the crowd toward the center of the city.

The atmosphere in the city was quite solemn, and everyone was very quiet as they traveled toward the center of the city in silence with their arms crossed over their chests.

Only after getting close to the center of the city could one hear the sound of some type of strange chanting, and Han Li's trio felt as if they were hearing the sound of constantly crashing waves, reverberating in a special rhythm.

At this moment, there were already millions of people packed onto the giant plaza at the center of the city and the nearby main roads. As a result, Han Li's trio was unable to progress any further upon reaching only halfway up the southern main road.

Thus, they were forced to squeeze through the crowd toward the plaza at the center of the city like a trio of slipper eels, much to the chagrin of many of the people around them.

However, due to the fact that the majority of the people here were mortals, and they were all busy chanting prayers, no altercation ensued from their actions. Thus, they were able to slowly squeeze their way onto the plaza, and even though they still weren't at the center of the plaza, they weren't all that far away.

Han Li was quite a tall man, so all he had to do was raise his head slightly to see all the way to the center of the plaza, where a huge statue that was over 1,000 feet tall was situated.

It was unclear whether it was due to the material of the statue or the lanterns around it, but the entire statue was of a crimson color, presenting a rather unnerving sight to behold.

Hovering in the air in front of the statue's chest were seven blue-robed figures, each of whom had the image of a crimson crescent moon embroidered onto the chest of their robes.

Under the illumination of the lanterns and with the statue behind them serving as a backdrop, these figures were made to appear like deities, and they were all giving off a peculiar aura.

However, none of them were actually all that remarkable when it came to their cultivation base. The white-haired elderly man at the center of the group was a late-Grand Ascension cultivator, but aside from him, everyone else was only at the Body Integration Stage.

However, for all of the people down below, the most powerful of whom were only Core Formation cultivators, they were no different from lofty deities.

Just like all of the millions of worshippers gathered down below, these seven people were also chanting the same prayers with extremely reverent expressions.

While Han Li was sizing up the seven blue-robed cultivators, Wyrm 16's voice suddenly rang out in his mind. "Should we take them down?"

He turned to find that Wyrm 9 was also looking back at him with a rather hesitant expression.

Right at this moment, the moon reached its highest point in the night sky, and the sound of prayers in the surrounding area gradually subsided.

The white-haired elderly man in the sky slowly turned around, sweeping his gaze across the plaza like a ruler looking down upon his people.

"It is only thanks to the infinite benevolence of the holy lord that we are all able to stand here today. Those among you who are most devout to the holy lord will be chosen for higher honors. The divine selection is about to begin, it's time to dedicate your prayers to the holy lord and pray for selection."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a wave of thunderous cheers instantly rang out from the crowd, but the cheering quickly subsided, and everyone looked up with hopeful expressions with their hands clasped tightly in front of them in prayer.

In order to blend in, Han Li's trio did the same thing.

Right at this moment, the plaza suddenly shuddered slightly as if some type of ancient array had been activated, and a very peculiar aura rose up in the surrounding area.

Han Li lowered his head slightly as he peered through the gaps in the crowd to inspect the ground with blue light flashing in his eyes.

As a result, he discovered that a series of complex patterns that were invisible to the naked eye had suddenly lit up, and they were intertwined with one another as they extended in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, hundreds of pillars of crimson light suddenly rose up into the heavens from all over the plaza, encompassing one Red Moon City resident after another.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the pillars of crimson light, and he was rather taken aback by what he saw.

Not only were the people encompassed within the pillars of light not panicked in the slightest, they were nothing short of ecstatic, and some of them were even weeping uncontrollably from joy.

If there were any friends or family next to them, then all of those loved ones would also be overjoyed, and even those who were unfamiliar with the ones encompassed within the pillars of light were looking at them with admiration and envy in their eyes.

Han Li turned to Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16 with a perplexed expression to find that they were just as puzzled as he was.

After all, nothing like this had ever happened in any of the previous Red Moon Cities that they had visited.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to Han Li, and he transmitted his voice to Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16, raising the question: "Could it be that these are the people chosen by the so-called holy lord?"

After a brief moment of contemplation, Wyrm 9 replied, "That's probably it. If we follow these people, perhaps we'll be able to find out more information about Gongshu Hong. The only problem is that we don't know where these people are going to be taken."

Han Li smiled as he replied, "There's an easy solution to that problem. There are people of all demographics being teleported away, so it seems like the selection process is completely random, but that's actually not the case."

Chapter 112: Clues

After hearing what Han Li had to say, Wyrm 16 immediately paid closer attention to the people being teleported away, and he quickly exclaimed, "These people seem to all be either low-grade cultivators or in possession of spiritual roots!"

"That's right! Are you suggesting that we also pose as low-grade cultivators so we can be teleported away with them?" Wyrm 9 asked.

"That's right. Given our powers, I'm sure we'll be able to pass as low-grade cultivators with no issues at all," Han Li replied.

"The place where we're going to be teleported to may have something to do with Gongshu Hong. Should we inform Wyrm 8 and the others?" Wyrm 16 asked in a slightly hesitant voice.

"We're only infiltrating their ranks for now. Let's wait until we actually make a discovery before we contact them," Wyrm 9 replied in a cold voice.

After that, he raised a hand and gently tapped a finger against his own forehead, upon which a burst of invisible fluctuations instantly began to emanate from his body.

His manifested face didn't change at all, but his aura was rapidly changing, adjusting itself to the mid-Foundation Establishment Stage in the blink of an eye.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 also immediately followed suit, adjusting their own auras to the Foundation Establishment Stage as well.

After that, they waited patiently for the same pillars of red light to emerge from beneath their feet.

However, a few minutes passed by, and during that time, more and more pillars of red light continued to rise up around them, but they weren't given the same treatment.

"Why haven't we been teleported away? Could it be that you're incorrect in your assessment, and this divine selection really is just a random process?" Wyrm 9 asked with a skeptical expression.

Han Li contemplated the situation for a moment before replying, "Be patient and keep waiting. If we haven't been teleported away even after the divine selection process has ended, then we'll just have to release our spiritual sense over a small area to investigate."

Wyrm 9 didn't say anything further upon hearing this, but he began to inspect his surroundings.

Right at this moment, a burst of red light suddenly rose up beneath his feet to encompass him, and everyone around him instantly turned their attention toward him.

Before he had a chance to do anything, the light faded, and he had also vanished from the spot.

Words of praise and envy instantly rang out from the people around him.

However, before long, two more bursts of red light emerged nearby, teleporting two more people away in a flash.

These two people were naturally none other than Han Li and Wyrm 16.

Han Li felt the entire world spin around him, and he couldn't help but sway unsteadily on the spot before reappearing somewhere else entirely.

He quickly swept his gaze over his surroundings to find that he was still surrounded by countless people, and Wyrm 16 was standing not far away from him with a perplexed look on his face, while Wyrm 9 was nowhere to be seen for now.

At the moment, they were situated in a vast underground palace that was so packed with people that it was impossible to see the walls of the palace. The only things that were visible were the ceiling up above the thick stone pillars standing nearby.

There were a series of large braziers hanging down from each of the stone pillars, and it was unclear what was being burned inside them, but they weren't releasing any smoke, and there were only crimson flames visible inside.

At the same time, bursts of red light were appearing incessantly in the surrounding area as one mortal and low-grade cultivator after another was teleported into the underground palace.

In contrast with the solemn atmosphere on the plaza, it was much rowdier here. All of the people who had been teleported into this place seemed to be unable to contain their excitement, and they were eagerly looking around while standing on the tips of their toes.

Aside from several Foundation Establishment and Qi Condensation cultivators, all of the people around Han Li were mortals, so being teleported here all of a sudden felt like a divine miracle to them, and they all began to chant their prayers in a reverent manner.

The combined voices of their prayers were reverberating throughout the entire underground palace, causing it to buzz incessantly.

For some reason, Han Li was struck by an oppressive sensation as he listened to these prayers.

However, this feeling only lingered for a short while before fading away, but there was a persistent bloody odor in the murky air that refused to dissipate.

His brows furrowed slightly as he looked down to find that all of the bluestone slabs that the ground was paved with had been stained a shade of red so dark that it was beginning to resemble black. It seemed like the type of color that could've only arisen from being regularly soaked in blood.

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but think of the yin soil that he had discovered under the stone slabs beneath the Red Moon City of Lan, and his brows furrowed even more tightly at the thought.

At this moment, Wyrm 16 squeezed through the crowd with some difficulty, arriving behind him before asking in a low voice, "Have you found anything?"

"I think I may have found some clues, but I can't be sure for now. Let's track down Fellow Daoist Wyrm 9 first," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

After that, he transmitted his voice to Wyrm 9, asking for his location.

Through their communication, he was informed that Wyrm 9 had been teleported to a location rather far away from them, near the center of the underground palace.

Thus, the two of them were forced to squeeze their way through the noisy crowd, drawing a great deal of ire and discontent along the way.

The closer they drew to the center of the underground palace, the more pronounced the bloody odor in the air became, and the darker the shade of red of the stone slabs beneath their feet.

By the time they arrived at the center of the underground palace, the color of the ground had almost turned a shade of dark purple.

Han Li looked up to find a statue that was over 30 feet tall up ahead, and it depicted none other than Gongshu Hong.

Near the statue was a stone platform that was around 100 feet in size, and it was only protruding slightly above the ground. The platform was completely empty with the exception of a short yet extremely muscular man.

The man was wearing a purple robe, and there was also a crimson moon design embroidered onto his chest.

His eyes were half-closed, and his aura was restrained, but Han Li could sense that he was a Layman Immortal.

Han Li and Wyrm 16 made their way over to the edge of the platform, following which the former's gaze lingered on the Layman Immortal for a moment before he turned to look beyond the statue.

Someone also squeezed their way out of their crowd in that direction, and it was none other than Wyrm 9.

He had naturally also spotted Han Li and Wyrm 16, yet right as he was about to make his way over to them, the Layman Immortal suddenly raised his head before briefly inspecting his surroundings.

Moments later, the man withdrew his gaze before looking directly up ahead as he began to speak. "Everyone..."

As soon as his voice rang out, all of the commotion in the area instantly ceased, and the entire underground palace became extremely quiet as everyone directed their attention toward him.

The atmosphere in the palace had become rather solemn, and Wyrm 9 also stopped what he was doing as he cast his gaze toward the Layman Immortal as well.

"The divine selection ceremony has already concluded. All of you have been chosen by the holy lord as his most devout followers, an honor unmatched by any," the man declared.

Everyone immediately erupted into ecstatic cheers upon hearing this.

Han Li swept his gaze across his surroundings to find that there was no longer any more red light appearing in the area, indicating that no more people were being teleported into the palace.

The Layman Immortal raised his hands in a quieting gesture, and the cheering gradually subsided, with the underground palace quickly falling silent again.

After that, he continued, "Out of the infinite kindness of his heart, the holy lord has decided to select those of you who possess the best cultivation aptitude to bestow cultivation arts upon and serve by his side. All you need to do is pray with sincerity and wait for the arrival of the holy lord."

Everyone in the palace immediately closed their eyes and clasped their hands before themselves in prayer upon hearing this.

An elated look appeared on Wyrm 16's face as he transmitted his voice to Han Li and Wyrm 9: "It sounds like Gongshu Hong will be coming here. Should we inform Wyrm 3 right away?"

Han Li cast his gaze toward Wyrm 9 upon hearing this, only to find a hesitant look on the latter's face.

Right at this moment, the statue at the center of the underground palace suddenly began to tremble, and two bursts of crimson light appeared in its eyes.

Han Li's trio immediately turned their attention toward the statue.

"We welcome the arrival of our holy lord," the Layman Immortal said in a reverent voice as he turned around and extended a bow toward the statue.

Everyone immediately followed suit, extending respectful bows of their own as they greeted in unison, "We welcome the arrival of our holy lord."

Han Li had also bent over slightly, but his gaze remained on the statue and the Layman Immortal.

The man was making a string of hand seals, and his lips were quivering incessantly as if he were chanting something.

All of a sudden, the crimson light within the statue's eyes flashed, and two pillars of red light were projected directly forward.

As the statue slowly revolved on the spot, the two pillars of red light swept through the crowd.

As the red light swept over Han Li, he could clearly sense a burst of spiritual sense lingering on him for a moment before turning elsewhere.

What was rather strange to him was that the spiritual sense was coming from the purple-robed man rather than the statue.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 9's voice rang out in his mind.

"What is he trying to do? There's no holy lord descending here, it's just him releasing his spiritual sense!"

"It looks like this is only a ceremony held in the name of that so-called holy lord. Gongshu Hong most likely isn't going to be coming here," Han Li replied after a brief moment of contemplation.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the pillars of red light that were combing through the crowd suddenly drew to a halt, lingering on a pair of young men.

The two were ecstatic, and they hurriedly moved toward the center of the underground palace under the instructions of the Layman Immortal, attracting much admiration and envy from those that they passed by along the way.

Han Li took a brief glance at the two men to find that even though they were only at a Foundation Establishment Stage, but their spiritual roots and bone structures were both quite good.

After that, the two pillars of light continued to sift through the crowd, landing on a thin young man and an elegant young woman moments later.

Han Li examined them to find that even though they weren't cultivators, both of them had exceptional cultivation aptitude.

As the pillars of red light continued to move through the crowd, one person after another was selected, and all of them were instructed to move toward the platform that the Layman Immortal was on.

Before long, over 200 people had already gathered there.

Ignoring their cultivation bases, Han Li could see that these people were the cream of the crop among the tens of thousands of people gathered in the underground palace when it came to cultivation aptitude.

With that in mind, he was suddenly struck by a sense of realization. Many past observations were strung together in this instant to form a cohesive theory, and he hurriedly transmitted his voice to Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16 to communicate this theory.

"I'm afraid we may be in some trouble, fellow daoists. This is not a place where people gather to see this so-called holy lord. Instead, it's most likely a sacrificial site."

"What?" Wyrm 9 was very alarmed to hear this.

"Did you find some leads, Wyrm 15? What led you to this conclusion?" Wyrm 16 asked as he turned to Han Li with a perplexed expression.

Chapter 113: Trap

"Just like in all of the underground palaces in the other Red Moon Cities, there's a lingering bloody odor in the air here, and the earth has already turned into yin soil. It's clear that this is a place where living beings are regularly slaughtered. Among the people brought to this place, all of them are either cultivators or mortals who possess spiritual roots. They're most likely going to be used as sacrifices here," Han Li explained with a grim expression.

"Now that you mention it, Gongshu Hong does cultivate in the laws of blood. Could it be that he regularly requires a large number of sacrifices to support his cultivation?" Wyrm 16 speculated with tightly furrowed brows.

"If that's the case, then why don't they begin the sacrifice right away? Why did they put the sacrificial subjects through a selection process first?" Wyrm 9 asked in a skeptical manner.

"My guess is that those who possess the most exceptional cultivation aptitude are selected so that they can be developed into those high-grade cultivators wearing the crimson robes, and they'll be the ones who directly serve Gongshu Hong.

“In order to prevent these people from revealing the true nature of the pilgrimage, they've most likely had some type of restriction placed on their souls. As for the rest... The true sacrifice will most likely begin after the selection process is complete," Han Li replied.

"Looking at the current situation, we should still have enough time to take that man down and get out of here," Wyrm 9 said as he took a glance at the Layman Immortal.

However, right as his voice trailed off, a loud buzzing sound immediately rang out from the surrounding space.

At the same time, a series of intertwining crimson patterns appeared on the walls of the underground palace, and they quickly began to spread like a system of cobwebs, instantly covering the entirety of the walls.

These crimson patterns flashed momentarily before blooming like flowers, revealing countless eyes that were glowing with faint crimson light. The eyes were constantly squirming as if they were living creatures, presenting an extremely unsettling and harrowing sight to behold.

Everyone was quickly illuminated a crimson color by the light being released by the eyes, and the bloody odor permeating through the air instantly became countless times more pungent.

Horrified looks began to appear on the faces of many of the people in the underground space upon seeing this.

Wyrm 9 was just about to say something when another burst of buzzing rang out, and the crimson eyes abruptly brightened considerably, releasing beams of crimson light that were as concentrated and densely packed as rain, encompassing the entire underground space, making it impossible to take evasive measures.

Every single beam of crimson light was giving off bursts of unidentifiable law fluctuations, and Han Li's trio was very alarmed by this development.

They didn't know what this crimson light was, but it clearly wasn't going to be something beneficial to them.

Han Li immediately summoned his True Extreme Membrane, and at the same time, he swept a hand through the air to release a round yellow mirror and an azure jade pendant, which instantly transformed into a pair of haloes, one yellow and one azure, both of which settled around him.

He had obtained these treasures from Tuhar, the Grand Ascension cultivator of the Cold Crystal Race that he had slain, and he was carrying them precisely in case of situations like this.

Wyrm 9 also reacted extremely quickly, making a hand seal as a series of blue ripples appeared around him, forming a series of layers that shielded his body from all directions.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 16 summoned a large azure umbrella, which revolved in the air above him before releasing countless dazzling threads of azure light, which draped down to form a ball of azure light that encompassed his entire body.

"What's going on? The selection process still isn't finished yet..."

A hint of befuddlement appeared in the Layman Immortal's eyes at the sight of the crimson eyes that had appeared around him, but before he had a chance to ponder the situation any further, countless beams of crimson light shot forth through the air.

He seemed to be quite fearful of these beams of crimson light, and he immediately opened his mouth to release a crimson flag, which instantly transformed into a crimson light barrier that enveloped his entire body.

The beams of crimson light were traveling extremely quickly, landing on everyone in the underground space in the blink of an eye.

The light barriers released by the treasures summoned by Han Li's trio posed no obstacle at all as the beams of crimson light passed through with ease before vanishing into their bodies.

Han Li's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately inspected his own internal condition with his spiritual sense.

However, the crimson light had vanished without a trace after entering his body, much to his shock and concern.

Right at this moment, a strange vibration began to ring out beside Han Li's ears.

For some reason, his heart was suddenly beginning to thump violently in an uncontrollable manner, and his heart rate was rapidly climbing.

At the same time, his blood circulation also sped up by severalfold, causing his entire body to become scorching hot, and the magic power in his dantian was also becoming unstable due to his violently beating heart.

Alarmed looks appeared on the faces of Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16, and they were clearly also experiencing the same thing as Han Li.

"What's going on?"

"What is this terrible feeling?"

"I can't take this..."

"Argh!"

A string of blood-curdling howls intermingled with dull thumps rang out from all directions, and Han Li's trio looked around to find that all of the mortals and low-grade cultivators who had been struck by the beams of crimson light were trembling incessantly, while their skin had also turned bright red.

Immediately thereafter, their bodies swelled before exploding into clouds of viscous blood mist.

Within the span of just a few seconds, hundreds of thousands of people in the surrounding area had exploded into blood mist, forming a suffocating cloud that permeated throughout the entire underground space.

As the crimson eyes on the walls blinked, the blood mist in the underground space rapidly converged to form a series of blood clouds. In the absence of all of the people who had had their bodies blown up, the underground space had become completely empty.

As a result, there were no longer any obstacles around to obstruct the view of Han Li's trio, and they discovered that there were four more people in the underground space with them.

They were none other than Wyrm 8 and his group, and they had somehow managed to infiltrate this place as well.

Wyrm 9 and Wyrm 16 were both quite pleased to see this.

Despite their differences, it was always good news to be reunited with allies in perilous situations. With the powers of seven True Immortals combined, surely they would be able to find a way out.

Han Li quickly swept his gaze over the blood clouds in the sky, and his heart immediately sank slightly. Bright azure light radiated from his body as he drew upon all of his magic power and unleashed several secret techniques in a row to try and quell the unrest in his body, but no matter what he did, his condition refused to improve, and his heart rate was only becoming faster and faster.

A burst of indescribable force was accumulating within his body before surging toward his heart, while another type of power was filling his body, causing it to rapidly expand.

A strange crimson color had appeared on his skin, but it was extremely faint.

Upon noticing this crimson sheen on his own skin, Han Li was immediately reminded of what had happened to those mortals and low-grade cultivators before their bodies exploded.

The same crimson color had also appeared on the skin of all of the other six Transient Guild members, but what was quite surprising to them was that there was an agonized look on the face of the purple-robed man on the raised platform, indicating that he also seemed to be in the same situation as them.

However, they naturally had no spare capacity to pay any heed to him.

At this point, the nature of the situation was already obvious.

They had thought that they had successfully snuck into the underground palace without being noticed, but in reality, they had already been detected by Gongshu Hong, who took advantage of their plan to trap them in this underground space. In order to avoid rousing their suspicions, it seemed that he was even prepared to sacrifice this Layman Immortal subordinate of his.

The crimson eyes on the walls were still blinking incessantly, releasing one beam of crimson light after another, and everyone was doing their best to take evasive measures, but they were still constantly being struck by the beams of light.

With each beam of crimson light that struck its target, a burst of strange power of laws would make its way into the target's body, further accelerating their heart rate.

Within the span of just a few seconds, everyone felt as if their hearts were about to leap out of their chests, and it was an extremely agonizing and panic-inducing feeling.

Among the seven of them, Han Li was the only one who was still holding up relatively well. Having already attained a True Extreme Body, his physical constitution was far superior to that of the average immortal, and that applied to his heart as well.

Even though his heart rate was also constantly accelerating, it was still bearable to him for now.

Wyrm 9 had a dark look on his face, and at this point, he was no longer making any attempt to conceal his magic power. He began to chant an incantation, and countless blue runes flew out of his body before intertwining to form a thin protective barrier.

The barrier was quite thin, but it was giving off bursts of powerful laws of water fluctuations.

The beams of crimson light were still able to pass through the blue protective barrier, but they were clearly whittled down significantly during the process.

It looks like the power of laws can only be stopped by the power of laws... Han Li thought to himself upon seeing this.

Han Li and Wyrm 9 were still in decent condition for now, but the same didn't apply to Wyrm 16.

Even though he was also pulling out all the stops, his body was still swelling steadily, and his skin had turned as red as blood, the same shade as the blood that was gushing uncontrollably out of his orifices.

"We have to find a way to get out of here!" Wyrm 9 yelled as he rose up into the air as a streak of blue light.

Wyrm 16 immediately followed along.

Han Li was the least affected by the crimson light out of everyone present, but it naturally didn't benefit him in any way to remain in this place, so he followed along as well.

Wyrm 8 and the others also quickly rose up into the air upon seeing this.

During his ascent, Wyrm 9 swept an arm forcefully through the air to release a blue flying dagger, which transformed into a giant blue blade that was over 100 feet in length in the blink of an eye. The blade was giving off sounds of howling wind and rumbling thunder as it crashed viciously into the stone ceiling of the underground space.

However, as soon as the blue blade made contact with the ceiling, a vast expanse of crimson light suddenly emerged from the ceiling without any warning, forming a crimson light barrier with countless runes surging incessantly over its surface.

A resounding clang rang out as if the giant blue blade had struck a metal wall, and the crimson light barrier remained completely unscathed, not even wavering in the slightest from the force of the impact.

Wyrm 9's expression changed drastically upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a black spike that was enveloped in black light shot out of Wyrm 16's body, and there was an urgent look in his eyes as he released a mouthful of blood essence, which vanished into the black spike in a flash.

The black spike immediately began to glow brightly while revolving rapidly, and countless tiny runes appeared on its surface alongside arcs of black lightning amid a string of rumbling thunderclaps.

The space in the wake of the black lightning trembled violently, and there were even some black spatial rifts that had appeared in the air.

Chapter 114: One Life for Another

"Go!"

Wyrm 16 thrust a finger through the air, and a resounding boom rang out from the black spike as it shot forth as a bolt of black lightning before striking the crimson light barrier up above with devastating force.

Almost at the exact same moment, circles of runes appeared on the surface of Wyrm 9's blue blade at his behest, and the light radiating from the blade became blindingly bright. Meanwhile, the fist projections unleashed by Han Li also fell upon the crimson light barrier.

A string of loud rumbling rang out, and the light on the surface of the crimson light barrier flashed wildly as it caved in significantly, but it still showed no signs of breaking.

Right at this moment, the crimson patterns on the surrounding walls suddenly began to release dazzling crimson light, while a strange glugging sound rang out.

The vast blood cloud in the air suddenly began to churn and tumble violently, following which long plumes of blood mist extended out from within it before flying in all directions, then seeped into the crimson patterns on the walls.

In the blink of an eye, the vast blood cloud vanished without a trace, leaving the underground space even emptier and more cavernous than before.

The crimson patterns on the walls abruptly became around twice as thick as they originally were, and those unsettling crimson eyes also bulged as if they had been opened up wide, presenting an even more terrifying sight to behold.

At the same time, the crimson light barrier shielding the ceiling of the underground space also became far thicker and denser, much to the alarm and dismay of Han Li and the others, and the parts of the light barrier that were caving in from the combined attacks from Han Li's trio were also radiating dazzling crimson light.

The black spike and the blue blade were repelled, and Han Li was also forced to stumble back by a burst of immense repulsive force as a stunned look appeared on his face.

Before they had a chance to do anything else, the surrounding crimson eyes began to glow even brighter, and the entire underground space was instantly enshrouded by dazzling crimson light, transforming the entire space into a crimson world.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, and he could clearly sense a burst of even more potent power of laws surging incessantly into his body through the crimson light, causing his heartbeat to accelerate even further.

Even with his incredible physical constitution, he was beginning to struggle.

In response to this sudden turn of events, Han Li immediately activated his Big Dipper Origin Arts, and seven specks of starlight appeared on his chest and abdomen, while a layer of starlight appeared over his entire body.

At the same time, all of his muscles, bones, and tendons were significantly bolstered, while a layer of starlight had also surfaced over his heart, and his heart rate finally began to slow a little.

In contrast, Wyrm 9's condition was worsening by the second, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which a burst of black light flew out of his body, then rapidly expanded to transform into a black-robed elderly man whose entire body was encompassed within a layer of dazzling blue light.

Countless blue runes were dancing within the blue light, giving off potent bursts of power of laws.

Immediately thereafter, Wyrm 9 made another hand seal before sweeping a hand through the air, and all of the blue light radiating from the black-robed elderly man's body instantly surged toward him.

As a result, the protective barrier formed by the power of laws around Wyrm 9 instantly brightened by around twofold, and it was able to ward off the oncoming beams of crimson light again.

Unfortunately for Wyrm 16, he didn't possess a body as powerful as Han Li's, nor did he possess any power of laws with which he could protect his body, and his face had become deathly pale under the relentless assault of the crimson light.

Bursts of power of laws that were constantly becoming more and more potent surged into his body in a frenzy before being converted into a form of strange power that struck viciously at his heart.

His heartbeat continued to accelerate rapidly until a dull thump suddenly rang out within his chest. Blood came gushing uncontrollably out of his mouth along with many organ fragments, and he fell heavily onto the ground with a dull thump, while the black spike also clattered onto the ground, having become completely dull and devoid of luster.

A desperate look appeared on Wyrm 16's face as he reached out in an attempt to grab onto something, but his body suddenly swelled up like a balloon before exploding violently into a cloud of blood mist that gave off incredible spiritual power fluctuations.

Both his body and his nascent soul had exploded in unison under the effects of the power of laws of blood.

The cloud of blood mist that his body had exploded into then immediately split up into several dozen bursts, as if it were being manipulated by someone, before vanishing into the surrounding walls and being absorbed, just like the blood cloud from before.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the blood mist formed by Wyrm 16's body was absorbed, the power of laws that were surging throughout this entire space became significantly more potent once again.

Han Li could hear the thumping of his heart ring out beside his ears once again, but he didn't panic as he took a deep breath before closing his eyes.

As a Profound Immortal, he was extremely knowledgeable about the human body, and the heart was the basis of the body, so he naturally had a very thorough understanding of the organ.

The sound of his heartbeat wasn't constantly getting louder and faster. Instead, there was some type of rhythm to it.

In the instant that Wyrm 16's body exploded, Han Li had grasped onto something.

Following Wyrm 16's demise, blood began to gush out of Wyrm 9's mouth and nose, and his face was becoming paler and paler.

He had clearly already realized that the increase in the potency of the power of laws surging through this space could be directly attributed to Wyrm 16's death.

At this point, he had already withdrawn all of the power of faith and power of laws in his Earthly Deity Avatar, but still wasn't enough to ward off the power of laws contained within the crimson light.

He could sense that his heartbeat had already accelerated to the limits of his body's physical tolerance.

I can't die here!

Wyrm 9 was roaring furiously in his heart, but he was unable to make even a single sound. The protective barrier around him gradually began to dim, and a despairing look appeared in his eyes.

All of a sudden, a fist punched through the protective barrier around him, seemingly out of nowhere, before striking him on the back.

The fist released a burst of force that penetrated into his body before acting upon his heart.

The force exerted was nothing short of ingenious, containing a certain tempo that immediately disrupted the frequency of his heartbeat. As a result, most of the destructive power that was crashing its way through his body instantly dissipated.

He opened his mouth and involuntarily threw up a mouthful of blood, but his complexion had already improved significantly, and he turned around to discover Han Li standing behind him, in the process of slowly withdrawing his fist.

He couldn't understand why Han Li was able to counteract the effects of the power of laws with just a single punch, but he still gave Han Li a grateful nod.

All of a sudden, the crimson eyes on the walls began to slowly close for some reason, and the crimson light filling the entire underground space also quickly faded.

However, the crimson patterns on the walls still remained, and the crimson light barrier protecting the ceiling was also still in place.

Despite that, both Han Li and Wyrm 9's heart rates had returned to normal, and they each heaved a long sigh of relief in the wake of that grueling ordeal.

In the distance, a figure descended out of the air, and it was none other than Wyrm 8. However, his entire body was drenched in blood, and he appeared to be in terrible condition, having clearly suffered greatly throughout that ordeal. However, the fact that he was able to survive to this point at all clearly indicated that the power of laws that he possessed was also quite special.

Aside from the three of them, there were no other survivors in this vast underground space, and there was a nauseating odor of blood and gore permeating through the air.

Han Li and Wyrm 9 had been too busy fending for themselves to keep tabs on the situation around them, so they failed to notice what had become of Wyrm 8 and his group.

Clearly, Wyrm 8 and the others had also done everything they could to break out of this space, but to no avail, and everyone else aside from Wyrm 8 had perished, which meant that four immortals had just fallen in that brief span of time.

Furthermore, the purple-robed man on the raised platform at the center of the crimson space had also disappeared, leaving only a large crimson flag that was glowing with faint spiritual light standing in his place.

Han Li wasn't pleased at all to see the demise of the purple-robed man. Instead, his brows furrowed slightly as a grim look appeared on his face.

There was a very good chance that Gongshu Hong was the one who had set this trap, and the fact that he was willing to sacrifice one of the Layman Immortals serving under him just to draw Han Li and the others to this place was a clear indication of just how determined he was to kill them.

As these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, he took some pills to aid in his recovery.

He wasn't naive enough to think that Gongshu Hong would leave them alone after that failed attempt to wipe out their entire group.

After taking a few pills himself, Wyrm 9 had also recovered somewhat, and he hurriedly cupped his fist toward Han Li in a grateful salute. "Thank you for saving my life, Wyrm 15. Words cannot express my gratitude."

After that, he beckoned toward the black-robed elderly man standing beside him, who rapidly shrank down before vanishing into his body as a streak of black light.

Han Li had already noticed the Earthly Deity Avatar that Wyrm 9 had released, but his expression remained unchanged as he replied in an indifferent voice, "There's no need to thank me, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 9. We're all in this together, so it's only right that I help out where I can."

Not only did he recognize Wyrm 9's avatar, he had even fought against it on a previous occasion. It was none other than the avatar of Patriarch Lu Kun that had accompanied Han Qiu to Dark Veil Island.

It was quite a coincidence that not only was Lu Kun also a low-level member of the Transient Guild, he was here on the same mission as Han Li.

At this point, Wyrm 8 had also flown over to them, and he landed beside Han Li and Wyrm 9 as a wry smile appeared on his face. "Looks like we've been one step behind Gongshu Hong this entire time."

"What a demented man he must be to sacrifice so many cultivators and mortals just for the sake of his own cultivation," Wyrm 9 spat through gritted teeth.

"Now's not the time to be discussing such matters. We should focus on finding a way out of here first," Han Li said as he inspected his surroundings.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of sinister cackling suddenly rang out.

"I didn't think that the three of you would be able to survive. The Transient Guild truly has no lack of formidable cultivators among its ranks!"

Immediately thereafter, the raised platform at the center of the underground space collapsed violently amid a burst of loud rumbling to reveal a massive hole.

A crimson cloud emerged from the hole, then dissipated to reveal three figures, one of which was none other than the purple-robed elderly man who had ambushed Han Li's trio back in Heavenly Water City.

The other two were also wearing purple robes with crimson moon symbols embroidered upon them, and one of them was a muscular middle-aged man with a thick beard on his face, while the other was a hideous young woman in a black dress, with a complexion that was as black as a kettle and a flat and virtually featureless face.

Judging from their auras, all three of them were True Immortals, with the middle-aged man giving off the most powerful aura of the three, and he seemed to be the leader of the trio.

The man cast a sinister gaze toward Han Li's trio with a cold smile on his face.

Chapter 115: Battling Chou Wu Again

"That brat was the one who somehow managed to break open my Bloodlight Space back in Heavenly Water City. I thought he had managed to do that purely out of dumb luck, but it seems like he's got some special tricks up his sleeve," the purple-robed elderly man said as he pointed at Han Li while his eyes narrowed slightly.

"Sounds like you've taken an interest in him, Chou Wu. In that case, I'll leave him to you, and we'll take care of the other two," the hideous woman in black said in a coarse and grating voice.

"That suits me just fine," Chou Wu chuckled in response.

While the three purple-robed cultivators were speaking with one another, Han Li's trio was also sizing them up with grim expressions.

These three were all Layman Immortals at the early-True Immortal Stage, so overall, they were inferior in power to Han Li's trio, but aside from Han Li, both Lu Kun and Wyrm 8 had suffered severe injuries. If a battle were to break out here, it was most likely going to be quite a grueling affair.

"Those three must be Gong Shuhong's other three Layman Immortal subordinates," Wyrm 8 said to Han Li and Lu Kun through voice transmission.

"This is a very strange place. I'm afraid there may be more nasty surprises to come if we linger here for too long," Han Li replied as he quickly swept his gaze over the crimson patterns on the surrounding walls, which had dimmed slightly at this point.

"We have to end this battle as quickly as possible. Now's not the time to be holding back," Wyrm 9 said.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the trio of purple-robed cultivators were already charging at them.

All of a sudden, spatial fluctuations erupted in front of Han Li's trio, and hundreds of crimson blades of light appeared before hurtling directly toward them.

Han Li took a half-step backward, then pulled back his fist before unleashing a powerful punch.

A burst of tremendous force instantly surged through the air, accompanied by a string of sounds akin to rain falling on a banana leaf.

All of the oncoming crimson blades of light instantly stalled, then exploded into countless specks of crimson light.

Before the light had even faded, Chou Wu's trio had already split up and were flying toward the opponents they had chosen for themselves.

A grim look appeared on Wyrm 8's face at the sight of the burly middle-aged man that was approaching him, and he had no time to address his injuries as he quickly made a hand seal.

A burst of light erupted all around him, following which a streak of dazzling azure light flew out of his body, then rapidly expanded to form a thin white-robed man beside him.

The white-robed man was quite similar to Wyrm 8 in appearance, but the skin all over his entire body was green, and he was basked in a layer of azure light. It was none other than Wyrm 8's Earthly Deity Avatar.

As soon as the avatar appeared, it immediately positioned itself in front of Wyrm 8, then opened its mouth and inhaled sharply.

Ferocious gusts of wind were instantly swept up in all directions, swirling violently to form a trumpet-shaped white vortex that surged into its mouth, causing its belly to expand rapidly.

It then opened its mouth to release an azure wave of energy that was visible to the naked eye, and the energy wave quickly transformed into an azure wind dragon that was over 100 feet tall.

A cold sneer appeared on the burly man's face upon seeing this, and he didn't even bother to make any preparations before throwing a punch directly forward.

At the same time, a sinister-looking white bone gauntlet had appeared over his fist, and spiritual light flashed over its surface as an enormous fist projection was unleashed, hurtling directly toward the azure wind dragon.

A resounding boom rang out as the azure wind dragon and the giant fist projection exploded in unison, sending countless azure blades of wind erupting in all directions.

A string of loud clangs rang out incessantly as the blades of wind sliced a series of extremely deep gashes into the ground, the walls, and the surrounding stone pillars as if they were made from tofu.

Following that initial clash, a layer of faint crimson light appeared over the burly man's body, and he rushed straight into the blades of wind as he continued to close in on Wyrm 8.

The blades of wind struck the crimson light on his body one after another in rapid succession, but they were unable to inflict any damage.

Wyrm 8 gritted his teeth as he leaped up into the air with his Earthly Deity Avatar to meet his opponent.

Meanwhile, after a fierce clash against Lu Kun, the hideous woman in black drifted backward with her entire body enveloped within a cloud of dense black mist.

However, before she had even descended onto the ground, her brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and a lotus flower formed by black mist emerged in the air beneath her feet amid a flash of black light.

She tread lightly onto the black lotus flower before springing up again and descending elsewhere.

On the spot where she was originally going to land, the blood that had accumulated over the ground suddenly churned and rippled, and a black figure wielding a blue longsword emerged in a flash, revealing itself to be Lu Kun's Earthly Deity Avatar.

Lu Kun's expression darkened slightly at the sight of his failed sneak attack, and he called out to his Earthly Deity Avatar to attack the woman together.

Not far away from them, Chou Wu was watching Han Li with a cold gaze, and he said in a cold voice, "I knew you had some tricks up your sleeve, but I didn't think that you were also a Profound Immortal. The blood puppet that I'm currently refining just so happens to be missing a vessel, so your True Extreme Body will be perfect for the role."

Han Li offered no response to this aside from raising his fists slightly in provocation.

The purple-robed elderly man's eyelids twitched slightly upon seeing this, and a hint of cold killing intent surfaced in his eyes.

All of a sudden, he flipped a hand over, and a dark purple bowl appeared over his palm amid a flash of black light. Red light was flashing and rippling incessantly within the bowl, as if it were filled with fresh blood.

As Chou Wu began to chant an incantation, the red light within the bowl brightened considerably, and it was originally only rippling slightly, but in the blink of an eye, it had begun to churn like boiling water while swirling violently within the bowl.

If one were to look closely, they would be able to see a series of anguished ghostly faces within the red light, and they were all frantically trying to clamber their way out of the bowl as if they were trying to escape.

A burst of dazzling radiance erupted from the bowl at Chou Wu's behest, and a huge volume of blood came gushing out, forming an enormous wave of blood that encompassed a huge area as it swept directly toward Han Li.

A nauseating odor instantly wafted through the air, while ghastly howls reverberated incessantly throughout the underground space. It was as if the entire area had suddenly been plunged into the underworld, and all of the cultivators and mortals who had just perished here had returned with a vengeance to vent their resentment and killing intent to their hearts' content.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he sensed the intense yin aura within the wave of blood.

With a flick of his wrist, the round yellow mirror came flying out, and a burst of yellow light was released from its surface, forming a ring-shaped light barrier all around Han Li.

As soon as the light barrier appeared, the wave of blood immediately came crashing down heavily upon it.

The yellow light barrier shuddered in an unsteady manner, but quickly stabilized itself again.

However, in the next instant, a burst of loud sizzling rang out as large plumes of smoke rose up from the surface of the light barrier, looking as if it were about to be melted away by the wave of blood. At the same time, the yellow mirror that was hanging in mid-air also began to tremble uncontrollably.

All of a sudden, a loud crack rang out as the round mirror was shattered before falling onto the ground, having completely lost its luster.

Without the yellow light barrier standing in its way, the wave of blood surged forward and inundated Han Li in an instant.

From Han Li's perspective, he felt as if he had been plunged into an extremely viscous sea of blood, and his movements were greatly restricted as a result.

His True Extreme Membrane was still glowing faintly even as it was soaked by the blood around him, but he could clearly sense that the membrane was constantly being contaminated by some type of corrosive power.

A series of ghastly figures were swimming incessantly through the sea of blood around him, and regardless of their age or gender, all of them seemed to be out for Han Li's blood as they rushed at him in all directions with their faces twisted in fury and bloodlust.

In response, Han Li thrust his arms through the air, instantly releasing countless fist projections that destroyed the 100 or so figures closest to him. At the same time, a layer of golden scales appeared over his body, and he grew noticeably in height as he prepared to leap out of the sea of blood.

"You're not getting away!" Chou Wu sneered as crimson light began to glow from his hand, and he thrust his palm against the bowl ahead of him.

Countless runes instantly began to sweep out of the bowl before vanishing into the sea of blood around Han Li.

The blood around Han Li instantly began to churn while rapidly revolving in a certain direction, and the temperature of the blood was also rapidly rising, as if it were being boiled over an open flame.

Before long, the temperature of the blood was already comparable to that of molten lava.

Within the scorching vortex of blood, Han Li's body began to sway unsteadily, and the layer of golden scales over his skin was beginning to take on a bright red hue. Furthermore, the sea of blood around him was tearing at him from all directions, preventing him from escaping.

A cold look appeared on his face as he made a hand seal, and a clear cry instantly rang out as the Essence Fire Raven flew out of his body, then transformed into a layer of silver flames to envelop him from all directions.

With this layer of flames around him, all of the scorching blood was kept at bay.

In fact, in the face of the astonishing heat being released by the silver flames, the blood around Han Li was quickly evaporating.

It didn't take long before a vacuum was formed around him, and the sea of blood was unable to restrict his movements any longer.

"I don't have time to waste with you here!" Han Li said in a cold voice as he sprang directly upward, and all of the blood above him instantly parted in the face of the protective barrier formed by the Essence Fire Raven.

After springing out of the churning vortex of blood, Han Li immediately threw a vicious punch directly at Chou Wu.

Chou Wu was greatly alarmed by this abrupt turn of events, and he hurriedly made a hand seal, upon which the bowl in front of him instantly swelled to several times its original size.

At the same time, the runes on the surface of the bowl began to glow brightly, and it released a series of black haloes as it positioned itself directly in the path of Han Li's fist.

A deafening boom rang out as Han Li's fist instantly shattered the black light radiating from the bowl. At the same time, several cracks instantly appeared on the bowl's surface, and it quickly reverted back to its original size.

Chou Wu shuddered violently as he gave a muffled groan, and blood began to trickle down from the corners of his lips.

He withdrew the bowl as he stroked the cracks on its surface with trembling fingers, and his eyes were full of shock as he murmured, "Impossible..."

Before he had a chance to do anything else, a sharp screech rang out, and a silver fire raven came flying rapidly at him like a speeding arrow, leaving a trail of silver flames in its wake.

Chapter 116: Forcing the Enemy Into Retreat

In the instant that the silver fire raven appeared, a hint of fear immediately appeared on Chou Wu's face, but at this point, it was too late to turn back. Thus, he gritted his teeth as a determined look appeared on his face, then abruptly opened his mouth to release three mouthfuls of blood essence onto the bowl in his hand in succession.

As soon as the blood essence came into contact with the bowl, it was completely absorbed without even a single drop left over. The bowl then began to buzz loudly as bright crimson light erupted from its surface alongside circles of runes, and a wyrm that was formed by blood flew out from within.

As soon as the wyrm appeared, it immediately opened its cavernous mouth to release a torrent of blood, which swept toward the silver fire raven as an enormous wave.

The wave of blood was extremely viscous, and it was giving off a nauseating odor.

The silver fire raven wasn't fazed in the slightest by the oncoming wave of blood, and it flapped its wings vigorously to release countless fist-sized silver fireballs that flew directly toward the wave of blood.

All of the silver fireballs exploded into silver flames upon contact with the wave of blood, evaporating the majority of the wave in the blink of an eye as plumes of white smoke rose up into the air.

The wave of blood was instantly punched full of holes, with the largest one being a hole that was 200 to 300 feet in size at the center of the wave.

The silver fire raven flew directly through the hole as a streak of silver light, then hurtled directly toward the blood wyrm and Chou Wu beyond it.

Chou Wu gritted his teeth as a fierce look appeared in his eyes, and he made a rapid series of hand seals, upon which bright crimson light radiated from the blood wyrm's body. At the same time, countless translucent runes appeared within the crimson light as the blood wyrm flew toward the silver fire raven with ferocious might.

Blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes as he inspected the blood wyrm, and his expression suddenly changed slightly as he hurriedly made a hand seal to try and summon the fire raven back to him.

However, right at this moment, all of the runes on the surface of the blood wyrm's body brightened considerably before exploding violently into an enormous cloud of extremely dense blood mist that swallowed up the silver fire raven in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, a clear cry rang out as a silver fireball shot out of the blood mist, then transformed back into a silver fire raven that flew rapidly back toward Han Li.

However, the fire raven was looking a little dim compared with before, and there were many patches of blood clinging to its body, clearly indicating that it had been affected rather heavily by the blood wyrm's self-detonation.

A layer of silver flames appeared over the fire raven's body at Han Li's behest, and the blood clinging to its body instantly evaporated, following which it flew back up his sleeve and vanished out of sight.

The blood wyrm released by Chou Wu's bowl treasure was imbued with a hint of power of laws, making it very potent in its ability to erode spiritual nature. Thankfully, Han Li had made a quick decision to summon the fire raven back to himself. Otherwise, its spiritual nature would've been significantly diminished.

At this moment, Chou Wu's face was rather pale, clearly indicating that the abilities that he had just unleashed had been quite taxing. A hint of resentment appeared in his eyes at the completely unscathed Han Li, and he suddenly grabbed onto his own robes before tearing them apart.

A long and narrow gash then abruptly appeared on his exposed belly, and the skin and flesh there shrank back on either side to reveal a gaping black hole.

Radiant black light began to glow from the surface of the dark purple bowl, and it flew into the gaping hole in a flash as if it had been summoned.

At the same time, the cloud of blood mist left behind by the detonated blood wyrm and what remained of the wave of blood swept back rapidly before also vanishing into Chou Wu's body through the gaping hole.

As a result, his height increased rapidly, and the pupils in his eyes disappeared, replaced by a pair of crimson rubies.

At this point, his robes had already been torn to shreds, and a layer of translucent crimson scales had appeared over his skin, transforming him into a crimson giant that was 70 to 80 feet tall, with a glittering sheen emanating from his entire body.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and instead of retreating, he charged directly toward the crimson giant.

Chou Wu cackled with glee upon seeing this as he raised a palm before swinging it down upon Han Li's head, causing the space in its wake to tremble and quiver.

Han Li made no attempt to take evasive measures as he lunged forward, raising his right fist to directly oppose the giant's enormous palm.

A resounding boom rang out, and Han Li felt as if a mountain were falling upon him, forcing him back down onto the ground, and in the blink of an eye, close to half of his body had been embedded deep into the ground.

However, after withstanding that punch from Han Li, the crimson giant shuddered violently before stumbling back several steps in an unsteady manner, and only after that was it able to steady itself.

Right at this moment, Han Li abruptly sprang up from the ground, reaching the ceiling of the underground palace in a flash, then propelled himself down from the ceiling with both feet, sending himself plummeting toward the crimson giant like a shooting star.

The crimson giant let loose a thunderous roar, and bright crimson light erupted from its body as it threw a vicious punch at Han Li.

At the same time, seven specks of blue light appeared on Han Li's chest and abdomen, and a layer of hazy starlight also appeared over his outstretched fist as it crashed into the crimson giant's fist.

A string of resounding booms rang out incessantly as if a mountain were collapsing, and the crimson light on the surface of the giant's fist quickly faded, following which the fist itself crumbled away into crystalline chunks of different sizes that fell down onto the ground.

In contrast, Han Li's fist resembled an unstoppable blade as it crashed through the crimson giant's arm, then blew right through the left side of its chest, shattering close to half of its entire body into pieces.

What remained of the crimson giant's body shuddered violently, and the light in its ruby eyes dimmed significantly. Immediately thereafter, its entire body completely crumbled away into a pile of crimson crystals.

Inside a crystal where the giant's dantian was located, Han Li spotted a miniature golden figure, and it was none other than Chou Wu's nascent soul.

It seemed that the nascent soul had been temporarily sealed within the crystal due to the secret technique that Chou Wu had just unleashed, rendering it unable to escape.

Right as Han Li reached out to grab the crystal, the nascent soul suddenly self-detonated with a loud thump, exploding into a cloud of blood mist that vanished without a trace into the blood on the ground below.

It had only taken less than 20 seconds for Han Li to put an end to Chou Wu's life, much to the astonishment of the four immortals who were still locked in a fierce battle not far away.

However, the four of them were displaying completely contrasting reactions, with Wyrm 8 and Wyrm 9 elated by this development, while the two Layman Immortals were completely horrified.

A decisive look appeared in the eyes of the woman in black, and she immediately extricated herself from her battle against Lu Kun before descending onto the raised platform at the center of the underground palace in a flash.

Almost at the exact same moment, the burly middle-aged man also escaped from Wyrm 8 and his Earthly Deity Avatar, then landed right next to his female companion.

In the next instant, their bodies blurred before transforming into a pair of crimson clouds that vanished into the large hole on the raised platform.

The two of them had fled the scene without any hesitation.

Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun exchanged a glance upon seeing this, then withdrew their respective Earthly Deity Avatars before making their way over to Han Li.

Even though the battle had only been a very brief one, the two of them had been severely injured to begin with, and those injuries had only worsened.

"I feel like a fool now for failing to realize after all this time that you possessed the ability to kill a Layman Immortal with ease, Fellow Daoist," Lu Kun said as he turned to Han Li with a complex look in his eyes.

"If you hadn't slain that man so quickly and forced his two companions into retreat, the two of us would've most likely struggled immensely in a drawn-out battle. I'll be sure to inform Wyrm 3 of what you've done here," Wyrm 8 said.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15's feats should be acknowledged and reported. However, at the moment, we should focus on finding a way to get out of here," Lu Kun said as he looked around with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"Earlier, Wyrm 16 used that immortal treasure to try and break through the restriction here, but not only did that not work, it caused that strange crimson light barrier to retaliate viciously, so it looks like brute force is not the way to go. We'll have to think of some other way," Han Li said with a contemplative expression.

"If you ask me, those two have most likely only temporarily retreated. I'm sure Gongshu Hong won't allow them to leave us alone for very long," Wyrm 8 said with a concerned expression.

"Wyrm 15, you were able to break through that crimson space back in Heavenly Water City, and I'm sure that wasn't just down to dumb luck. Can you see if you can find any vulnerable points in this space? In the meantime, I'll try and get into contact with Wyrm 3 to inform him of the situation here," Lu Kun said after a brief moment of contemplation.

"I'll give it a try," Han Li replied with a nod.

With that, Lu Kun closed his eyes, and the goat mask reappeared on his face before blue ripples began to surge over its surface.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 8 began to gather the storage treasures of all of the immortals who had met their demise in the underground palace.

Han Li merely took a glance at him, but refrained from saying anything, and blue light emerged within his eyes as he began to carefully inspect his surroundings.

There was a thick layer of blood caked onto the ground, and the remains of all of the people who had perished here were soaked within the blood. Blood had also splattered all over the surrounding walls and stone pillars, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Similarly, the statue in the underground palace was also drenched in blood, and it was looking particularly sinister and disturbing, like an evil deity who reveled in slaughter and bloodshed.

However, even after a thorough inspection, Han Li was unable to find any vulnerable points on the surrounding walls or the statue.

Moments later, Lu Kun also opened his eyes as he shook his head and said in a grim voice, "There's no response from Wyrm 3."

"This underground palace is rather strange. The restriction in here seems to be imbued with a type of laws of blood, and it's nurtured by all of the blood from the sacrifices performed in here, forming a completely independent space. It's not going to be easy to find a way out of here," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

While they were speaking with one another, Wyrm 8 also made his way over to them. "The storage tools left behind by our fellow daoists of the Transient Guild and those two Layman Immortals are all here. Let's split the contents. There are most likely still going to be more perilous moments to come on this mission, so it's best to be as prepared as possible."

At this moment, he was holding several storage bags in one hand, and two storage bracelets in the other.

After tallying the spoils, the three of them discovered that the six Layman Immortals were quite affluent, regardless of whether it was in terms of pills, materials, or treasures, and Han Li's trio all received bountiful returns.

Given everything that Han Li had displayed earlier, the only immortal treasure in the possession of the six deceased Layman Immortals, the black spike owned by Wyrm 16, naturally fell into his hands.

Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun were both very eager to take the treasure for themselves, but neither of them wanted to see the treasure fall into the other's hands, so in the end, both of them decided to do Han Li a favor and split the treasure to him.

Han Li was naturally aware of this, and after accepting the treasure, he made some concessions in the distribution of the six Layman Immortals' other possessions, a gesture that was much appreciated by the other two.

Chapter 117: Landing in Trouble Again

After quickly splitting the spoils, Han Li's trio split up once again to try and find a way out.

There was simply no way that they could feel safe until they left this strange underground space.

At the moment, Han Li was situated over 1,000 feet away from the statue, carefully inspecting his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun had also begun investigating the area after taking a short while to recover from their injuries.

As time passed, the three of them employed several methods to try and find a way out, but all to no avail. Han Li was still able to maintain his composure, but Lu Kun and Wyrm 8 were beginning to let their agitation get the better of them.

Right at this moment, the entire space suddenly shuddered before swaying violently, much to the alarm of Han Li's trio.

Before the three of them had a chance to do anything, the ground beneath their feet suddenly completely shattered with a resounding boom.

A viscous cloud of blood surged up from the shattered ground, then swelled rapidly to inundate the trio like lightning before descending back down, pulling Han Li's trio along with it.

The entire world was spinning in front of Han Li's eyes, but the surrounding cloud of blood was holding them tightly in its clutches.

By the time the world fell still around them again, they found themselves situated in a massive, unfamiliar space.

This was an underground cavern that was countless times larger than the underground palace from before, but the majority of its area was taken up by an enormous underground lake. The water in the lake was of the same color as blood, and it seemed to be very viscous, with bubbles rising up incessantly on its surface before popping one after another.

With each bubble that popped open, a burst of crimson mist would emerge, and the entire underground cavern was completely filled with this faint crimson mist.

At the center of the crimson lake was a flat island that was protruding out of the water. The island was several dozen kilometers in size, resembling a massive plaza.

At this moment, Han Li, Wyrm 8, and Lu Kun were standing on this plaza.

At the center of the plaza stood a huge palace, which was entirely enshrouded within a dense crimson cloud, through which only the indistinct outlines of the palace could be seen.

Aside from Han Li's trio, the entire underground cavern was completely empty, and it was eerily quiet, with only the sound of the popping bubbles on the surface of the lake punctuating the silence.

The two Layman Immortals who had fled earlier didn't seem to be in here, either.

After inspecting his surroundings, Han Li was just about to release his spiritual sense for a closer examination when he suddenly discovered that he was unable to release his spiritual sense out of his body due to a type of peculiar power imbued within the crimson mist in the air.

Judging from their grim expressions, Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun had clearly also noticed this, and the former immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release his Earthly Deity Avatar.

Lu Kun was just about to say something when Han Li suddenly yelled, "Look out down below!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the ground beneath their feet suddenly split open, and several massive crimson bone claws reached out to grab at their legs.

The three of them immediately flew up into the air to avoid the grabbing bone claws.

The ground down below continued to crumble away as one massive figure after another emerged. These were all crimson skeletons that were several times as tall as the average adult human, and in the blink of an eye, several hundred of them had emerged from the ground.

Every single one of those skeletons was giving off a powerful aura comparable to that of a Body Integration cultivator.

The skeletons let loose a string of low roars, then sprang up into the air, pouncing at Han Li's trio.

At the same time, the crimson lake around the island began to tumble and churn, following which a series of crimson monsters leaped out from within.

These monsters had female human upper bodies with heads of long, crimson hair and a pair of large bat wings on each of their backs, but they possessed serpentine lower bodies.

The auras being released by these winged naga monsters weren't inferior in the slightest compared with the giant skeletons, and as soon as they flew out of the crimson lake, they immediately sped directly toward Han Li's trio as well.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's trio found themselves surrounded by close to 1,000 skeletons and naga creatures, a development that was quite alarming to say the least.

Wyrm 8 gave a cold harrumph, and the Earthly Deity Avatar beside him began to glow with dazzling azure light at his behest, resembling an azure sun that was hanging in the sky above the crimson lake.

The Earthly Deity Avatar swept its hands through the air, and the azure light around it flew out of its body, then split up into four massive azure wind dragons that flew away in all directions.

A dozen or so of the oncoming skeletons and naga monsters were sent flying by the wind dragons, and the majority of the monsters who were directly struck instantly had their bodies destroyed.

The rest of them appeared to have sustained injuries as well, but the surrounding crimson mist seemed to have a mind of its own as it instantly surged into their bodies, healing their injuries at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye. Within the span of just a few seconds, all of them were fully healed.

Wyrm 8's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

The four wind dragons didn't appear to be very remarkable, but every single one of them had been formed by his power of laws, making each of their attacks far more formidable than even what a Grand Ascension cultivator could withstand. However, these skeletons and naga monsters were displaying extremely impressive physical resistance and self-regenerative abilities.

In contrast, Lu Kun was refraining from using his Earthly Deity Avatar, seemingly trying to conserve his power of faith. Instead, he swept a hand through the air to release eight flying daggers, which swelled rapidly to form eight giant blue blades that began to circle around in the air.

Seven or eight indistinct blade projections appeared around each of the giant blue blades, and with eight of these blades in total, dozens of blade projections were manifested before sweeping rapidly through the air in all directions amid a burst of rumbling that resembled the sound of violently crashing waves.

In the blink of an eye, the entire space within a radius of over 1,000 feet was filled with glacial blue light, and around a dozen skeletons and naga monsters were instantly struck before exploding on the spot.

In contrast with Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun, Han Li's attacks were far more mundane, and he was only throwing punches at the surrounding area.

With each punch that he threw, the surrounding space would shudder violently, and all enemies who attempted to attack him were destroyed with a single punch with no exceptions.

After just a few seconds, hundreds of skeletons and naga monsters had already been slain by the trio.

However, more and more of the creatures were emerging from the ground and the crimson lake with no end in sight, so the number of monsters that Han Li's trio was being attacked by wasn't decreasing at all.

"Fellow Daoists, we don't know where Wyrm 3 is at the moment, and there's a very good chance that Gongshu Hong is in that palace. His location is completely unknown to us, while we're exposed out in the open, so the situation is very detrimental to us," Han Li said to his two companions through voice transmission while inspecting the surrounding area with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

"Could it be that you've found a way out?" Lu Kun asked as a hopeful look appeared on his face, and Wyrm Eight directed his gaze toward Han Li as well.

This underground cavern didn't appear to be all that remarkable, but both of them could clearly sense that the entire cavern was enshrouded within a burst of immense power of laws, so getting out of this place definitely wasn't going to be an easy feat.

"I've found several conspicuous points in the cavern, but it's going to take some time for me to exploit those points, and these skeletons and naga monsters are quite annoying to deal with," Han Li replied.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Wyrm 8 said, "Leave these small fry to me. I have a way to keep them occupied for some time while you and Wyrm 9 focus on finding a way out."

"Alright, then I'll be counting on you."

Han Li threw several punches in rapid succession as he spoke, and seven or eight fist projections erupted forth before exploding violently amid a string of earth-shattering booms.

A burst of terrifying power swept through the area, tearing a hole in the encirclement formed by the surrounding skeletons and naga monsters.

At the same time, bright azure light erupted from Han Li's entire body as he flew through the hole in the encirclement, then sped toward a certain spot on the ceiling of the underground cavern.

The surrounding skeletons and naga monsters faltered momentarily, following which all of them roared in unison, and the majority of them abandoned Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun to go after Han Li.

Wyrm 8 harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and he flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession. Azure radiance that was even more dazzling than before erupted from his Earthly Deity Avatar, and the azure light spread through the air in circles, instantly encompassing the majority of the space within the underground cavern.

All of a sudden, a burst of peculiar buzzing rang out in the air, and all of the world's origin qi in the area encompassed within the azure light began to tremble. At the same time, a series of thin azure threads appeared out of thin air to ensnare the skeletons and naga monsters, thereby significantly hampering their speed.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued onward without pause, reaching his destination in the blink of an eye before throwing a powerful punch.

Right at this moment, two humanoid figures emerged from the ceiling of the underground cavern, and they were none other than the burly man and the woman in black who had fled earlier.

As soon as he appeared, the burly man immediately threw a punch at Han Li.

The menacing bone gauntlet on his fist suddenly began to glow brightly, and a massive fist projection that resembled a malicious ghost shot forth through the air.

At the same time, black light flashed within the hand of the woman in black, and a thick black mace appeared in her grasp. As soon as the mace was swung through the air, countless black mace projections were released, forming a black mountain that came crashing down upon Han Li.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and the fearsome fist projection exploded violently, as did the mountain of black mace projections.

The burly man and the woman in black were astonished to see this, and their bodies were jolted violently before being sent flying back through the air like a pair of cannonballs and crashing heavily into the ceiling of the cavern, causing the entire cavern to tremble and quiver.

Having witnessed Han Li's battle against Chou Wu, they were already aware that Han Li possessed incredible physical strength, but only after a direct clash did they come to realize that he was far stronger than they had anticipated.

Han Li also shuddered slightly, and he was forced to take two backward steps before managing to steady himself.

"Let me lend you a hand, Wyrm 15!"

A burst of blue light shot forth from behind Han Li, and from within the burst of light emerged Lu Kun and his Earthly Deity Avatar.

At the same time, Lu Kun opened his mouth to release a burst of blue light, which vanished into the body of his Earthly Deity Avatar, which instantly began to glow brightly with blue radiance as it also opened its mouth to release two balls of watery blue light.

Encompassed within the balls of light were countless shimmering blue runes, which were giving off powerful water law fluctuations.

The two balls of blue light flashed momentarily before abruptly sprouting a head and four limbs each to form a pair of watery blue figures, which sped through the air at an incredible speed toward the burly man and the woman in black.

This seemed like quite a complex sequence, but in reality, everything had taken place in the blink of an eye.

The burly man and the woman in black had only just steadied themselves when they were confronted by the pair of watery blue figures, and the burly man's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this as he flung his gauntlet through the air. Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which transformed into a cloud of blood mist that seeped into the gauntlet in the blink of an eye.

The gauntlet instantly took on a crimson hue, and it blurred momentarily before transforming into a sinister crimson ghostly head the size of a pavilion.

The ghostly head opened its eyes, and bright crimson light was radiating from its pupils. It then opened its cavernous mouth, and a wave of crimson flames erupted forth from within before sweeping toward the oncoming blue figure.

Chapter 118: Bait

At the same time, the woman in black hurriedly made a hand seal with one hand in response to the blue figure that was hurtling toward her.

The black mace in her hand began to glow with black radiance, and a series of winding crimson patterns appeared on its surface, following which a burst of crimson flames swept forth from the mace.

As the mace was swung through the air toward the oncoming blue figure, a string of explosions rang out incessantly in the air, immediately following which the mountain of giant mace projections appeared once again, except this time, every single mace projection was enshrouded within a cloak of crimson flames.

The space in the wake of the mountain of mace projections was visibly warping and rippling, as if it were boiling from the intense heat of the flames.

The two blue figures crashed into the crimson flames and the mace projections at virtually the exact same moment, but they were able to pass through those obstacles amid a flash of blue light, and they were completely unaffected.

However, upon closer inspection, one would discover that both of the watery blue figures had become slightly diminished in stature, but at the same time, their speed abruptly increased drastically as they reached the burly man and the woman in black in the blink of an eye.

The burly man and the woman in black were extremely alarmed by this unexpected development, but before they had a chance to do anything, the pair of watery figures suddenly began to glow with scintillating radiance.

Immediately thereafter, both of them exploded silently, transforming into a vast expanse of glacial energy that swept toward the burly man and the woman in black from all directions.

A string of loud crackling rang out as a layer of crystalline blue ice appeared on their bodies, and the ice was rapidly spreading. In what seemed like no more than the blink of an eye, the two of them were encapsulated within two massive blocks of blue ice, both of which were several dozen feet tall.

This was clearly no ordinary ice, as evidenced by the fact that the two of them were completely immobilized within it, and their expressions of shock and horror had been frozen onto their faces. However, in the next instant, crimson light flashed from both of their bodies, and the series of cracks began to appear over the surface of the two blocks of ice.

Meanwhile, Lu Kun's complexion had paled slightly, while the blue light radiating from the body of his Earthly Deity Avatar had dimmed significantly, and it was clear that this had been quite a taxing attack for him to unleash.

Right as the burly man and the woman in black were about to break out of the blocks of ice, Han Li suddenly appeared behind them in a wraith-like manner. A layer of golden scales emerged on both of his fists, and they were thrust through the air like a pair of mighty wyrms, crashing into the bodies of his two opponents with devastating force.

The two blocks of ice exploded violently, as did the bodies of the burly man and the woman in black within them.

Their nascent souls flew out of the shattered blocks of ice, and each of them was encompassed within a faint layer of crimson light. In the blink of an eye, both of them appeared in front of the gates of the palace on the island down below, as if by instantaneous teleportation, and their movements were completely unaffected by all of the azure threads in the surrounding area.

Han Li wanted to intercept the pair of nascent souls, but it was already too late.

Right as the two nascent souls were about to fly into the palace, the crimson cloud that the palace was enveloped in suddenly began to surge and churn violently. Immediately thereafter, a pair of massive hands formed by crimson mist extended out from within. The pair of hands spread their fingers open, and crimson light flashed over their palms, upon which the two nascent souls were instantly immobilized and drawn into their grasp.

"Please spare us, merciful holy lord!" the pair of nascent souls desperately implored as horrified looks appeared on their faces.

A cold harrumph suddenly rang out from within the palace at the center of the island, and the voice was extremely unpleasant on the ears, much like the sound of metal grating on metal.

The expressions on the faces of Han Li's trio changed slightly upon hearing this, and a hint of alarm appeared in the eyes of Wyrm 8, who was still situated on the island. He immediately withdrew his hand seal, then rose up into the sky with his Earthly Deity Avatar to join Han Li and Lu Kun.

As a result, all of the azure threads in the air faded away. However, instead of swarming Han Li's trio, all of the crimson skeletons and naga monsters melted away into streaks of viscous crimson light, which then flew into the crimson cloud from all directions before vanishing out of sight.

Immediately thereafter, a tall and imposing figure slowly emerged from within the palace. The figure's entire body was enshrouded in a layer of crimson light, so only the faint outlines of their facial features were visible.

Behind the figure were two huge balls of crimson flames that were crackling incessantly.

What was rather strange about these two balls of fire was that the outermost layer of both of them consisted of crimson flame, but one of them contained a purple center, while the center of the other one was white.

A pair of faces could be seen within the purple and white flames, and those faces belonged to none other than Chou Wu and the man in the purple robe from before.

"Please spare us, almighty holy lord! Our physical bodies may have been destroyed, but we can just find new bodies, and we'll be able to continue to serve you!"

The nascent souls of the burly man and the woman in black began to desperately plead for their lives once again.

"Thank you for your hard work over all these years. I'll take care of things from here."

Gongshu Hong remained completely unmoved by their desperate pleas, and he merely raised a hand into the air, upon which the pair of giant crimson hands closed their fingers. Two blood-curdling howls instantly rang out, following which two peculiar balls of crimson fire flew out of the pair of giant hands.

The outermost layers of the fireballs were both crimson in color, yet they contained an azure core and a black core, respectively.

The twisted features of the burly man could be seen within the azure flame, while the face of the woman in black emerged within the black flame, presenting a peculiar and unsettling sight to behold.

The two balls of crimson flames quickly descended in front of Gongshu Hong, and the purple, white, azure, and black flames within them were slowly revolving on the spot while suspended in mid-air.

Han Li's trio was looking on at the harrowing scene unfolding before their eyes, and they couldn't help but exchange an astonished glance with one another.

"I'm very pleased with those four sacrifices from before. Now that I've taken your nascent souls as well, my Origin Restoration Blood Flames will be able to advance even further. Once that happens, I'll no longer be bound to this island," Gongshu Hong mused as he turned his attention to Han Li's trio.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately made a hand seal, and the four flames of different colors revolving through the air around him instantly vanished into the layer of crimson light over his body at his behest. Immediately thereafter, his aura began to elevate incessantly.

"It seems like he's very close to reaching the late-True Immortal Stage. This is going to be a difficult fight," Han Li said in a grim voice as a layer of translucent light appeared over his body.

"At this point, our backs are against the wall, so we have no choice but to fight."

Lu Kun flipped a hand over as he spoke, and a purple jade vial appeared in his hand. He tipped a thumb-sized purple pill out of the vial, then swallowed it without any hesitation.

At the same time, his Earthly Deity Avatar raised a hand, and a vast expanse of watery light surged forth to form a series of protective light barriers that enveloped his entire body.

At the same time, Wyrm 8 was also busy at work, releasing several glowing treasures in succession to protect himself.

"It's your turn now!"

The surging crimson light around Gongshu Hong gradually subsided, and he raised his head to the heavens before exhaling deeply, then slowly raised his arms, and two piercing balls of crimson light surfaced over the palms of his hands.

However, right as he was about to spring into action, something unexpected happened.

A burst of spatial fluctuations erupted behind him, and a hand that was enveloped in flames appeared out of thin air before plunging into his body from behind, piercing through his chest and emerging out the front.

Han Li's trio was elated to see this.

They could tell from the aura emanating from the hand that it belonged to none other than Wyrm 3, who had been missing for quite some time.

The crimson light on the surface of Gongshu Hong's body shuddered before exploding and flying away in different directions as seven or eight streaks of crimson light.

These streaks of crimson light then converged over 1,000 feet away to form Gongshu Hong's body again, except the crimson light on the surface of his body had grown a little dimmer.

A flash of fire erupted behind the fiery hand arm that had just emerged out of thin air, and Wyrm 3 appeared with his entire body enshrouded in orange flames.

As soon as he emerged, he immediately hurtled toward Gongshu Hong as a streak of dazzling fire.

The flames around Wyrm 3's body expanded drastically mid-flight, transforming into a thick and vibrant fiery wyrm that opened its cavernous mouth, threatening to devour Gongshu Hong whole.

A burst of violent law fluctuations erupted out of the fiery wyrm's body, evaporating all of the crimson mist in the surrounding area.

Gongshu Hong harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and he brought his palms together before releasing a crimson fiery python, which sprang out of the crimson light enveloping his body before pouncing toward the fiery wyrm.

A resounding boom rang out as the two fiery creatures clashed before exploding violently into balls of dazzling flames.

Wyrm 3 took advantage of this opportunity to rise up above Gongshu Hong, and a huge crimson sword had appeared in his hand. There was a dragon engraved onto the surface of the sword, and it was giving off immense spiritual pressure, indicating that it was a Profound Heavenly Treasure.

With a swing of his arm, the giant crimson sword came crashing down with tremendous force.

Around a dozen streaks of fiery swordlight surged through the air before converging to one spot, forming a giant sword projection that was over 1,000 feet in length before descending toward Gongshu Hong.

Crimson light flashed from Gongshu Hong's hands, conjuring up a pair of crimson claws that were swept through the air.

10 crimson crescent-shaped claw projections were released, crashing into the giant sword projection amid an earth-shattering boom.

The sword projection and the claw projections exploded in unison, heralding the commencement of the fierce battle between Wyrm 3 and Gongshu Hong.

Lights of all types of different colors were clashing and weaving intertwining incessantly, while a string of loud booms rang out in rapid succession, causing the nearby space and the entire underground cavern to tremble and quake violently.

"I feel like Wyrm 3 was planning from the very beginning to have us charge ahead and act as bait to lure out Gongshu Hong," Lu Kun remarked with a wry smile.

"That's how things are in the Transient Guild. If you want to obtain what others cannot, then you have to be prepared to pay the ultimate price at any time," Wyrm 8 said, and there was also a hint of dejection in his voice.

"There's no point in talking about things like this right, fellow daoists. We have to help Wyrm 3 strike down Gongshu Hong if we want to survive this ordeal," Han Li said.

Lu Kun and Wyrm 8 nodded in agreement.

Having arrived at a consensus, the trio and the pair of Earthly Deity Avatars immediately entered the fray, charging toward Wyrm 3 and Gongshu Hong.

"Mere ants like yourselves should know your place!"

Gongshu Hong didn't even spare them a glance. Instead, he merely swept a hand casually in their direction.

A gust of fierce wind that was tinged with a bloody odor immediately swept toward Han Li's trio, and the crimson cloud up above abruptly began to release a vast expanse of crimson mist, which instantly encompassed the entire area overhead, inundating the trio and the pair of Earthly Deity Avatars.

The intense bloody odor was making Han Li's head spin, but a burst of cool and refreshing energy then immediately flashed through his brain, allowing him to shrug off the debilitating effects of the blood mist.

Blue light flashed within his eyes, and he was just about to retreat out of the cloud of blood mist when he heard an agonized howl ring out from nearby.

He hurriedly turned in that direction to discover that Lu Kun's Earthly Deity Avatar was in the process of crashing down toward the ground, and it was being rapidly pursued by a completely nude humanoid crimson creature.

The creature's bodily structure was no different to that of the average person, but its face was a complete blur, with no facial features visible aside from a pair of eyes that were giving off bright red light.

Chapter 119: Red Moon

Han Li immediately flew out of the cloud of blood mist upon seeing this, then rapidly descended toward the ground. Right as the tip of his foot was about to make contact with the ground, a cold gleam suddenly flashed through his eyes, and he raised an arm before throwing a punch toward a certain spot in the cloud of blood mist up above.

A crimson figure shot out of the blood mist in a flash, and it curled its fingers into a set of claws as it grabbed at the top of Han Li's head. Five powerful claw projections were unleashed from its fingertips, and the claw projections clashed directly with Han Li's fist projection.

A resounding boom rang out, and the projections from both sides disintegrated upon contact. Immediately thereafter, the crimson humanoid creature's arm exploded violently, and it was blown back by a burst of tremendous force, concealing it within the blood mist again.

Meanwhile, Han Li's body swayed slightly, and right as he steadied himself, a string of piercing howls suddenly rang out within the nearby cloud of blood mist.

Countless azure blades of wind erupted in all directions from the point where the sound was coming from, tearing a large section of the cloud of blood mist to shreds to open up a clear area, revealing Wyrm 8 locked in a fierce battle against another one of those crimson creatures. At this point, his Earthly Deity Avatar was already riddled with wounds, and it seemed that he was struggling immensely against his opponent.

Lu Kun's Earthly Deity Avatar had plummeted to the ground earlier, but it had since risen up to join forces with Lu Kun, and the pair were battling another crimson creature.

Right at this moment, the blood mist in the air churned slightly, and the crimson creature that had been sent flying by Han Li flew out once again, having already completely regenerated a new arm.

As soon as it emerged, it immediately sped toward Han Li as a crimson shadow once again.

Instead of retreating in the face of this oncoming assailant, Han Li charged forward to meet it once again, throwing several punches in succession to send it flying back through the air again while also leaving its body in tatters.

However, a series of crimson threads quickly shot out of the wounds on the creature's body, and those crimson threads tugged on one another to seal its wounds shut, following which it made another full recovery thanks to the surrounding blood mist.

No more than a few seconds had passed, and the crimson creature had made a full recovery once again before charging toward Han Li a third time.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

This crimson creature was rather similar to the water giant that Lu Kun had summoned in the past. In particular, this was the perfect environment for it to thrive in, so it was virtually unkillable by ordinary brute force attacks.

If things were to continue like this, even if he could hold his own for now, Lu Kun and Wyrm 8 most likely weren't going to last very long at all, particularly considering they were already carrying severe injuries.

Meanwhile, the roars of a tiger were ringing out incessantly up above.

As it turned, there were six giant tigers formed by blood mist prowling around Gongshu Hong, and they were locked in a fierce battle against Wyrm 3.

Perhaps it was because he was having to simultaneously control the three humanoid crimson creatures, but at this moment, the crimson light around Gongshu Hong's body appeared to be slightly dim. In the face of the attacks from Wyrm 3's giant crimson sword, the tigers were firmly on the back foot, and at this rate, it seemed that it would only be a matter of time before Gongshu Hong was defeated.

"You're no match for me without your avatar! Die!"

A cold sneer appeared on Wyrm 3's face, and his aura suddenly swelled by severalfold, becoming rather violent and unstable.

At the same time, his entire body began to rapidly swell in size amid a burst of crimson light, and a series of crimson scales emerged all over his skin. A pair of thick dragon horns also sprouted out of his forehead, and his teeth had been replaced by a mouthful of sharp fangs. In the blink of an eye, he had taken on a half-human, half-wyrm form, and in particular, his arms had become incredibly thick and strong.

At the same time, crimson runes surged out of his huge sword in frenzy, and they were swirling around incessantly, causing all of the world's origin qi in the entire underground cavern to fluctuate in a wild and unstable manner. Countless specks of light appeared out of thin air, then gushed into the sword like the tide, following which the sword was swung viciously in Gongshu Hong's direction.

A resounding boom rang out, and a crescent-shaped sword projection that was close to 1,000 feet in length swept through the air. The surface of the sword projection was radiating bright red light, and from this red light was emanating a hint of extremely violent power of fire laws. As it passed through the air, all it left in its wake was a thin fiery red line, which caused the surrounding space to shimmer and warp.

Gongshu Hong hurriedly shot back in retreat upon seeing this, and at the same time, he raised both hands up into the air in unison to release a pair of crimson claws. The claws instantly swelled to several hundred feet in size, radiating dazzling light as they crossed over one another and positioned themselves in front of him.

At the same time, the six blood mist tigers before him also pounced forward, releasing a viscous pillar of crimson light out of each of their mouths to oppose the oncoming fiery red line.

The red thread sliced through the pair of claws with ease, then clashed with the pillars of crimson light.

A string of dull thumps rang out in rapid succession, and the pillars of light all exploded into huge clouds of blood mist, while the six blood mist tigers were also eradicated.

In the next instant, the fiery red thread abruptly blurred before appearing directly in front of Gongshu Hong, as if by instantaneous teleportation.

At the same time, a layer of translucent crimson light appeared over Gongshu Hong's body before transforming into a suit of glittering and translucent armor.

However, the suit of armor was no match for the fiery thread, which tore through the armor with ease before slicing into Gongshu Hong's body.

Dazzling crimson flames erupted violently, releasing vast law fluctuations that instantly inundated Gongshu Hong. At the same time, the entire space in a radius of several thousand feet around him began to warp violently, as if it were about to be incinerated.

After unleashing that attack, Wyrm 3's aura also diminished by as much as 50% to 60%.

All of a sudden, a blurry crimson shadow shot out of the scorching flames, then appeared several thousand feet away.

The crimson light then faded to reveal a thin and tall middle-aged who appeared to be around 40 years of age. He had a head of lifeless straw-like hair, a set of gaunt and sunken facial features, and he was so emaciated that he was virtually nothing more than a sack of skin and bones, but his eyes were glowing with a crimson gleam.

His aura was in a state of disarray, and his left arm had been severed at the shoulder, but strangely enough, not a single drop of blood was flowing out of the wound.

"I see you used a substitution technique," Wyrm 3 chuckled coldly upon seeing this, and a burst of fearsome law fluctuations began to emanate from his giant crimson sword once again before he slashed it in Gongshu Hong's direction.

Yet another vast sword projection was released, and as soon as the law fluctuations arose, the sword projection transformed into a thin fiery red thread once again, hurtling toward Gongshu Hong at an incredible speed.

However, this time, Gongshu Hong didn't try to take evasive measures, nor did he try to defend himself against the attack. Instead, a peculiar grin appeared on his face.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from the lake down below, and an incredibly thick pillar of crimson light erupted out of the lake, instantly appearing between Gongshu Hong and the fiery thread.

The fiery thread struck the pillar of crimson light amid a burst of violent rumbling, and the pillar of light trembled as if it were about to instantly crumble.

However, bursts of crimson light then erupted out of the crimson lake down below before injecting themselves into the pillar of light in a frenzy, allowing it to remain stable and firm in the face of the fiery thread.

The fiery thread quickly began to dim, and a few seconds later, it vanished into nothingness amid a dull thump.

Wyrm 3's pupils contracted slightly in incredulity upon seeing this.

"It's about time..." Gongshu Hong chuckled to himself, then raised his right arm as he began to chant a complex incantation.

Another thick pillar of blood rose up from the crimson lake down below in a revolving corkscrew fashion, and it transformed into a viscous churning cloud of blood before injecting itself into Gongshu Hong's body.

As a result, his aura began to rapidly recover, and a series of red threads emerged from the wound on his left shoulder before intertwining with one another, forming a brand new arm in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, an even more astonishing scene ensued as the crimson lake down below began to churn and tumble violently, releasing one thick pillar of crimson light after another.

There were close to 100 pillars of light in total, and they were connected by more beams of crimson light to form an enormous array.

The entire underground cavern was instantly basked in dazzling crimson radiance, and the smell of blood in the air became 10 times more pronounced, while a burst of peculiar law fluctuations swept through the area.

Han Li was in the process of battling the humanoid crimson creature when his heart began to thump violently once again. All of the blood in his body began to churn before flooding back into his heart, instantly slowing his movements.

However, he only swayed slightly for a moment before steadying himself, but a hint of alarm flashed through his eyes.

Meanwhile, Lu Kun and Wyrm 8 were also affected by this burst of blood law fluctuations, which had caught them completely off guard. Thankfully, both of them were able to react very quickly, and with the assistance of their Earthly Deity Avatars, no opportunity arose for their opponents to exploit.

However, at this point, the light radiating from their bodies had become quite dim, and it was clear that the power of faith that they had accumulated up to this point was quickly running out. At the same time, both of them were quite far away from their respective islands, so there was no way for them to replenish their powers of faith.

In the air above, Wyrm 3 was just about to pounce at his opponent when an unnatural flush abruptly appeared on his face, and it was clear that the power of laws of blood had had a significant effect on him as well.

However, all it took was a quick hand seal and a deep breath for his complexion to return to normal, but even so, he was also quite alarmed by this turn of events.

Right as all of this was unfolding in the underground cavern, the entirety of the Kun province's Red Moon City began to rumble violently, as if an earthquake were taking place.

All of the rivers running throughout the city had also turned bright red, as if there were blood flowing through them.

The city's residents and those who were attending the pilgrimage were all panicked and bewildered by this disturbing sight, and none of them had any idea what was happening.

Before they had a chance to do anything, bursts of loud rumbling began to ring out incessantly.

All of a sudden, close to 100 pillars of crimson light rose up around Red Moon City, forming an enormous crimson light barrier that encompassed the entire city, enveloping it in a bloody and oppressive aura.

"What's going on?"

Not only were the ordinary civilians in the city at a complete loss, even the mid and high-grade blue-robed cultivators were completely bewildered and unsure of what to do.

Countless eye-shaped diagrams of different sizes appeared on the crimson light barrier in a flash, and all of them began to blink.

Countless beams of crimson light then shot out of the eyes before raining down upon the city.

Every single person that came into contact with the beams of crimson light instantly turned bright red, and their bodies swelled rapidly in size before exploding before they even had a chance to cry out.

In what seemed like no more than the blink of an eye, the lively and bustling city was already completely devoid of life. Blood began to flow over the ground in the city, only to quickly vanish into the ground as if it had been sucked away.

Meanwhile, the exact same thing was happening in all of the Red Moon Cities in all of the provinces on the entire island. Every single one of those cities had been enshrouded under an enormous crimson light barrier, which instantly robbed all of the living beings in the city of their life force, transforming them into fresh blood that seeped into the ground.

If one were to look down at Red Moon Island from high up in the sky, they would discover that all of the main rivers on the entire island had turned as red as blood.

The bodies of water formed a complex network, but ultimately, all of them were flowing toward the center, converging to the Kun province's Red Moon City.

At this moment, Red Moon Island resembled a blood moon hanging over the dark sea.

Chapter 120: Battling the Island Master

Inside the underground cavern.

Around a dozen dark caves had opened up on the surrounding rugged mountain faces, and blood was gushing out of the caves incessantly like a series of waterfalls. All of the blood was converging into the crimson lake down below, causing the blood inside to churn and froth incessantly.

In the air above, the giant array formed by the pillars of crimson light was buzzing loudly, and countless balls of crimson fire were springing up all over the array. Hints of power of laws were emanating from the balls of scorching flames, causing the nearby world's origin qi to boil and surge.

At the same time, the power of laws filling this entire space instantly became several times more pronounced.

An unnatural flush immediately appeared on the faces of both Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun, and both of them threw up a mouth of blood in unison. Immediately thereafter, they shuddered before falling back, and their auras were also rapidly diminishing.

Almost at the exact same moment, two bursts of crimson light shot forth in pursuit of the two of them in a flash, and they were none other than the two crimson humanoid creatures from before.

Wyrm 8 was greatly alarmed by this turn of events, and he opened his mouth to release a gust of fierce azure wind, which transformed into a crescent-shaped blade of wind that flashed through the air, leaving behind a thick white mark that was releasing powerful spatial fluctuations.

The crimson creature was unable to evade the attack, and it was split into two down the middle by the blade of wind.

However, that didn't slow it down in the slightest, and the two halves of its body transformed into two streaks of crimson light that reached Wyrm 8 in a flash before passing through his body. The streaks of light that came together to reform the body of the crimson creature, and held in one of its hands was none other than Wyrm 8's nascent soul.

The crimson creature cackled in a sinister manner as it opened its mouth before devouring the nascent soul whole.

At the same time, Lu Kun was still plummeting out of the sky, and for some reason, the magic power within his body had become stagnant and unwieldy, causing his heart to immediately sink.

The crimson creature was coming closer and closer, and he was completely powerless to evade it. All of a sudden, he gritted his teeth and made a decision. The head of his nearby Earthly Deity Avatar abruptly separated from its body, immediately following which its body exploded violently amid a flash of dazzling blue light.

Bursts of watery blue mist revolved through the air like a series of vortexes, releasing tremendous suction force that slowed down the crimson creature significantly.

Meanwhile, the head of the Earthly Deity Avatar flew toward Lu Kun as a streak of blue light, and it crashed into his body to accelerate his fall, sending him plummeting into the crimson lake down below, vanishing without a trace.

While Wyrm 8 and Lu Kun were both struggling against the effects of power of laws in the area, another fierce battle was taking place not far away, and the two combatants involved were none other than Han Li and the third crimson creature.

Han Li's face was slightly flushed, but his movements didn't seem to have been affected at all, and a barely detectable hint of surprise flashed through Gongshu Hong's eyes upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a sharp screech rang out, following which a streak of swordlight that resembled a translucent fiery red thread swept through the air, giving off terrifying law fluctuations that caused the nearby space to tremble and buzz.

A cold sneer appeared on Gongshu Hong's face as he swept a sleeve through the air, and bursts of crimson light erupted out of the surrounding pillars of light. At the same time, balls of crimson flames rose up from the lake of blood down below, and the crimson light fused with the crimson flames to instantly form around a dozen layers of thick light barriers to protect him from the oncoming attack.

The fiery red swordlight struck the first crimson light barrier, tearing through it with ease.

One light barrier was torn apart after another, but the fiery swordlight was also constantly becoming dimmer and diminishing in size.

Finally, after slicing through the ninth light barrier, it fizzled out into nothingness after flashing a few times.

In the distance, Wyrm 3 raised his giant sword above his head once again, and a burst of scorching law of fire aura swept forth from his body to keep out the surrounding crimson light.

However, before he had a chance to swing his sword, an unexpected turn of events suddenly arose.

All of the surrounding pillars of crimson light suddenly flashed in unison, then formed a massive crimson cage in the blink of an eye, trapping Wyrm 3 inside.

Wyrm 3 remained calm and composed as the flames around him reared up, and the massive sword in his grasp transformed into a blooming fiery lotus flower, releasing several sword projections in all directions. Each sword projection was around a foot in length, and all of them struck the surrounding crimson cage.

The cage flashed erratically as one crimson pillar was severed after another, only to be instantly mended by the viscous blood gushing out of the pillars.

A hint of derision flashed through Gongshu Hong's eyes, and he began to chant an incantation while making a string of hand seals.

The lake of blood down below surged and churned, following which more giant crimson pillars rose from the depths. The surfaces of the pillars were burning with scorching crimson flames, and the flames wrapped around the enormous crimson cage like a mass of tentacles.

The water level in the lake was rapidly falling, and even though there was more blood constantly pouring in from all directions, it still wasn't long before the lake had virtually run completely dry.

Enshrouded within a thick layer of crimson flames, the giant cage began to slowly revolve as if it had transformed into a cauldron.

Inside the fiery cauldron, Wyrm 3 sat down with his legs crossed, and his face had become slightly flushed once again, while his blood was boiling within his veins.

The surrounding crimson flames were releasing an inexplicable type of heat that enveloped his entire body, seeping into his flesh and blood as if it were trying to refine him like a pill.

All of a sudden, he let loose a low cry as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and a series of fireballs swept forth from his body, revolving around him to form a fiery space that was several dozen feet in size.

Wyrm 3's flushed complexion instantly improved slightly, but it seemed that this still wasn't enough to completely ward off the effects of the laws of blood.

"I have all the time in the world! Let's see how long you can last!" Gongshu Hong chuckled coldly outside the fiery cauldron while continuing to make a string of hand seals, but his attention had turned to Han Li.

Somehow, Han Li was able to remain largely unaffected by the power of blood laws permeating throughout the entire area, and he was able to hold his own against the crimson creature.

Gongshu Hong's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and the other two crimson creatures instantly sped toward Han Li as a pair of crimson shadows at his behest. At the same time, the crimson creature that was battling Han Li sprang back in retreat.

Han Li also flew back in retreat upon seeing this, and he took a quick glance at Gongshu Hong, then turned to face forward again, not letting his guard down for even a moment.

To his surprise, he wasn't attacked by the other two crimson creatures. Instead, they crashed into the retreating crimson creature, following which a stunning scene unfolded.

The bodies of the three crimson creatures dissolved into blood, then fused together to form a crimson male figure that was identical in appearance to Gongshu Hong with the exception of its skin coloration.

Dazzling crimson light erupted from its body, then proliferated outward alongside an immense aura.

So this is Gongshu Hong's Earthly Deity Avatar!

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Gongshu Hong's Earthly Deity Avatar let loose a wild screech, and crimson light flashed over its body a huge volume of blood gushed forth, then instantly intertwined to form a ball of blood roughly the size of a water vat. The ball of blood was giving off a rank odor as it sped toward Han Li as fast as lightning.

Han Li raised an arm, and a layer of shimmering golden scales appeared over his fist before clashing with the ball of blood amid a resounding thump, causing the surrounding space to shudder and ripple violently.

The ball of blood revolved on the spot momentarily before abruptly exploding into a vast expanse of blood mist, sending a burst of tremendous power of laws sweeping through the area.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly in alarm, and he immediately attempted to fly back in retreat, but it was already too late.

The cloud of blood mist churned violently, transforming into around a dozen crimson chains that instantly wound themselves around Han Li's torso and limbs, chaining him to the spot.

Han Li's entire body was already covered in golden scales, and he clenched his fists tightly as he tried to struggle free from his restraints, but the more violently he struggled, the tighter the crimson chains became. The chains were grinding audibly against his golden scales, and Gongshu Hong's Earthly Deity Avatar cackled in a sinister manner as he made a hand seal with both hands.

Half of all of the blood that was flowing out of the surrounding caves instantly split off to sweep toward Han Li at the avatar's behest, forming a giant vortex with a diameter of close to 1,000 feet to inundate his entire body.

However, in the next instant, a thunderous roar rang out from within the vortex, and a pair of incredibly thick golden arms reached out from within before grabbing viciously onto either side of the vortex.

A resounding thump rang out as the crimson vortex was forcibly torn apart, reduced to countless chaotic streams of blood that flowed away in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, a golden figure that was several hundred feet tall sprang out from within. It was none other than Han Li in his Giant Mountain Ape form, and there were still a few sections on his arms and torso that were drenched with blood.

As soon as he appeared, he immediately raised an arm, then made a grabbing motion with his hand. A ball of silver flames emerged on his palm, then rapidly elongated to form a huge silver spear that was over 100 feet in length.

Gongshu Hong's Earthly Deity Avatar faltered slightly upon seeing this, then beckoned with both hands to draw a vast expanse of crimson flames up from the lake of blood, forming a fiery crimson wheel around him that was over 100 feet in diameter.

A sharp screech rang out as the giant silver spear flew out of the golden ape's hand, and it was burning with scorching silver flames as it hurtled toward Gongshu Hong's Earthly Deity Avatar with unstoppable might.

Almost at the exact same moment, the crimson wheel of fire also began to revolve, then flew through the air like a scintillating crimson sun.

A resounding boom rang out as the fiery crimson wheel instantly exploded into a vast expanse of crimson flames, interspersed with wisps of silver flames.

The flames spread through the air in all directions in an extremely violent wave of scorching heat, causing the entire underground cavern to tremble and quake, while the blood in the crimson lake down below churned and surged.

The giant silver spear wasn't slowed down in the slightest. Instead, it was sped up even further by the shockwaves from the explosion, hurtling toward Gongshu Hong's Earthly Deity Avatar before piercing straight through his chest in a flash.

After summoning his Earthly Deity Avatar to deal with Han Li, Gongshu Hong had turned his full attention back to the crimson cauldron, attempting to incinerate Wyrm 3 as quickly as possible, and all of a sudden, his entire body shuddered as he threw up a mouthful of blood.

"No..." he roared as he lowered his gaze, just in time to see the giant silver spear protruding out of his Earthly Deity Avatar's chest transforming into a burst of dazzling silver flames that engulfed the avatar's entire body.

Chapter 121: Recommendation

Right as Gongshu Hong's aura was wavering in an unstable manner following the destruction of his Earthly Deity Avatar, a thunderous roar rang out from down below, and a burst of powerful soundwaves swept through the air with devastating power.

This was none other than the Vajra Roar that Han Li had just unleashed in his Giant Mountain Ape form.

The space in the wake of the white soundwaves blurred and warped violently, as if the entire space were about to collapse.

The crimson cauldron hovering in the air shuddered violently in the face of the destructive soundwaves, and it began to sway unsteadily, while the law fluctuations that it was releasing were also cast into disarray.

Right at this moment, a resounding draconic roar suddenly rang out from within the cauldron, immediately following which a burst of red light exploded above the cauldron, forming a huge cloud of blood mist.

Immediately thereafter, a fiery dragon that was over 100 feet in length rose up into the heavens from the blood mist, then twisted around in the sky before swooping down toward Gongshu Hong.

"How dare you destroy my Earthly Deity Avatar and ruin my cultivation foundation! I'm going to bring all of you down with me!" Gongshu Hong roared in a fit of blind fury, and a deranged look appeared on his face.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the crimson light around him brightened drastically while his body rapidly swelled up like a balloon, releasing a terrifying destructive aura.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately reverted back to his human form before stowing his Essence Fire Raven away with a wave of his hand.

The fiery dragon that Wyrm 3 had transformed into also changed directions and skirted around Gongshu Hong upon seeing this.

Scintillating radiance erupted from the scales on the fiery dragon's body alongside a vast expanse of crimson flames, which instantly encompassed the entire island on the lake of blood before forming a series of fiery red lotus flowers that bloomed in rapid succession.

A burst of scorching law fluctuations instantly permeated through the air, and it was as if a standalone realm had been opened up within the underground cavern.

This is a spirit domain!

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon sensing the change taking place around him.

Right at this moment, a burst of incandescent light that was as bright as the sun erupted within the underground cavern. At this point, Gongshu Hong's body had already swelled to several dozen times its original size, and melted away like snow and ice within the blinding radiance.

A series of violent explosions erupted incessantly, and the island at the center of the lake of blood was completely shattered before being instantly devoured by the eruption of light, then reduced to nothingness.

Devastating shockwaves erupted in all directions, shattering the entire underground cavern and causing it to collapse, resulting in huge volumes of the lake's water gushing in in a frenzy.

Above the cavern, the completely barren and lifeless Red Moon City also crumbled away into an enormous set of ruins.

However, there was an area in the cavern that was encompassed within a layer of green light, and it was completely unharmed.

Eight huge pieces of rhomboid turtle shells were hovering above that area, and they were connected together to form an ovular dark green light barrier that was completely unmoved by the shockwaves resulting from the explosions.

Within the light barrier, Han Li had activated his Xuanwu bloodline, and his entire body was encased in a suit of dark green armor as he calmly inspected his surroundings.

The scorching aura that filled the entire space wasn't displaying any sign of fading away, and all of the fiery red lotus flowers littered throughout the area were releasing bursts of strange aura fluctuations to combat the violent energy.

Not far away from Han Li, Wyrm 3 had already reverted back to his human form, and he was seated on a giant fiery lotus flower with his entire body enveloped within a layer of reddish-golden light. His robes were flapping audibly as he made a rapid series of hand seals, supporting his spirit domain with all his might.

Only after a few minutes had passed did the tremors in the cavern gradually subside. At this point, most of the fiery red lotus flowers had already dissipated, and Wyrm 3's spirit domain also slowly crumbled away.

As the final few lotus flowers faded out of existence, Wyrm 3 descended out of the sky with a weary expression.

Han Li also withdrew the turtle shells around him upon seeing this, and he cupped his fist in a salute toward Wyrm 3. "Congratulations on successfully killing Gongshu Hong, Wyrm 3."

"You played a pivotal role in our successful completion of the mission as well, Wyrm 15," Wyrm 3 said as he turned to Han Li.

At this point, the cold apathy that was normally seen in his eyes had completely faded, replaced by undisguised approval and appreciation.

"You're far too kind, Wyrm 3. I only made the slightest of contributions. I certainly wouldn't dare to consider my meager contributions anywhere near significant," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"There's no need to talk yourself down. In the Transient Guild, power is valued above all else. Those with insufficient power who covet benefits beyond what they deserve can't blame anyone else even if they were to meet their demise, do you understand what I'm saying?" Wyrm 3 asked in a meaningful voice.

"I do, and I will be sure to remember your teachings," Han Li replied in a respectful manner.

"Very good. I can put in a recommendation for you to be promoted to a higher-level member of the guild. Would you like that?" Wyrm 3 asked.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "May I ask what comes with being a higher-level member of the guild? If it requires taking on even more difficult missions, then I wouldn't dare to agree without giving it some careful consideration first."

"Setting aside everything else, if you're successfully promoted, you'll gain the ability to release normal missions and earn the right to exchange resources with other members of the same level," Wyrm 3 explained in an indifferent voice.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "In that case, I'll have to trouble you to put in a recommendation for me."

"I have the right to submit recommendations, but the guild will send out an envoy to examine your abilities to determine whether you deserve a promotion or not. When that time comes, you'll have to complete another trial mission, but I'm sure that won't be any problem for you given your powers," Wyrm 3 said.

Han Li didn't offer up any further words of gratitude, merely extending a slight bow instead.

"Alright, now that the mission is complete, I have to remain on the island for a while longer to wrap things up. Red Moon Island has a long history, so I'm sure it's laden with many precious resources. You can go explore the island on your own, but make sure you don't stay for too long," Wyrm 3 continued.

Han Li nodded in response before taking his leave, flying away into the distance as a streak of light.

Around 15 minutes later, a streak of azure light burrowed its way out of the ground near Red Moon City, then faded to reveal Han Li.

He stood in mid-air, and he couldn't help but heave a faint sigh as he looked down at the ruins of the city down below.

Seven people had accompanied Wyrm 3 into the city, yet he was the only one that remained, and that was sufficient testament to just how perilous the Transient Guild's missions were.

Gongshu Hong had sacrificed countless lives as a blood sacrifice to enhance his own powers, even going as far as to sacrifice four of the Layman Immortals who had been following him for countless years, reflecting just how cruel and ruthless he was, but similarly, Wyrm 3 was just as cruel and uncaring toward others when it came to achieving his objectives.

However, he was correct in that risk and reward always came hand in hand in the pursuit of cultivation. There were never any easy paths to take in cultivation, and that was something that should've been apparent to all cultivators from the moment they chose to pursue this path.

With that in mind, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of the slight hint of sympathy that he felt toward his fallen comrades.

After taking a brief moment to ascertain the direction he wanted to go in, he sped away into the distance as a streak of azure light, choosing not to linger on the island to search for any of the supposed resources there.

Earlier, he had already stowed away Wyrm 8's storage tool in secret, and in addition to everything that he had obtained before that, this had already been quite a bountiful trip.

The main resources of the island were definitely in Gongshu Hong's possession, which meant that they belonged to Wyrm 3 now. While it was true that there had to be other resources elsewhere on the island, those were far too insignificant for him to bother going out of his way to find.

Two months later, a streak of azure light appeared near Dark Veil Island, then faded to reveal Han Li.

A faint smile appeared on his face at the sight of the small island.

He had just endured quite a perilous trip, but thankfully, he had returned safely and achieved the objectives that he had set out to achieve.

Luo Feng quickly flew out of the island as a streak of light to meet him.

"Senior Liu!" he greeted with an elated expression.

He was the only one who had been informed by Han Li of this trip, and during this time, he had been waiting day and night in constant fear that some terrible fate would befall Han Li. Now that Han Li had returned safe and sound, he was immediately overcome by a sense of immense relief.

"Did anything happen during the time I've been away?" Han Li asked.

"Nothing out of the ordinary has happened during your absence," Luo Feng hurriedly replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then flew back toward his courtyard, while Luo Feng trailed along behind him and reported to him some of the news that had recently arisen during the past couple of months.

One of those pieces of news was that the island that Lu Kun presided over had suddenly gone into isolation without any explanation.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything.

Lu Kun had fallen into the lake in the underground cavern with the head of his Earthly Deity Avatar and never reappeared again, so it was unclear whether he was dead or alive.

However, given the situation at the time, even if he hadn't perished, he would've most likely at least suffered severe injuries.

With that in mind, Han Li dismissed Luo Feng, then returned to his courtyard and fell onto his bed before promptly falling asleep.

Only on the next day did he get out of bed, feeling fully revitalized, then flipped a hand over to produce a cluster of objects, consisting of several storage tools and spirit treasures, as well as Wyrm 8's broken Earthly Deity Avatar.

First, he examined Wyrm 8's broken avatar to find that most of the materials used to refine it were identical to that of Luo Meng's Earthly Deity Avatar, with the main difference being the copious amounts of precious wind-attribute materials used in Wyrm 8's avatar.

Even though these materials couldn't be recycled and reused, Han Li would still be able to learn a great deal from examining them and therefore be better prepared for when he refined his own avatar.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed the avatar away, then began to examine the spirit treasures.

Following his examination, he discovered that Wyrm 16's black metal spike seemed to be a low-grade immortal treasure, but aside from that, none of the other treasures were remarkable in any way. However, for some reason, even though the black metal spike appeared to be completely fine on the outside, it seemed to have sustained rather severe internal damage, and the power of laws imbued within it was slowly seeping out.

At this rate, all of the power of laws within it would be gone in just a few centuries.

It was no wonder that Wyrm 16 wasn't able to utilize the treasure to any great effect.

Thus, his interest in the collection of treasures immediately faded, and he only briefly examined the remaining treasures before stowing them away.

He had no need for any of those treasures in his current state.

Finally, Han Li picked up those storage tools before injecting his spiritual sense into them.

A long while later, he opened his eyes, and a hint of elation appeared on his face.

As expected, the collections of these True Immortals didn't disappoint. The storage tools contained many precious materials, far exceeding what could be found on Dark Veil Island.

In fact, there were many items that even he didn't recognize, but they were definitely all extremely precious.

With these things in his possession, he wouldn't have to worry about cultivation resources in the near future.

He took a deep breath before splitting these things up into different categories and stowing them away, then flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip.

This was an Earthly Immortal cultivation art by the name of the Profound Astral Wind Arts, and it seemed to be perfect for his needs. However, he still had to follow the set procedure, becoming an Ancestral God first before he could become an Earthly Immortal. Hence, the cultivation art wasn't very useful to him at this current stage, but it was still a good resource to study and examine.

Chapter 122: Trial

Over a month passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, Han Li was seated in his secret chamber in a completely still manner with his legs crossed and his eyes closed.

All of a sudden, his eyelids fluttered slightly, and he opened his eyes before rising to his feet. In the next instant, he appeared in the air above the courtyard that he was staying in, having already put on his azure cow mask.

After a brief hesitation, he flew through the air in a certain direction as a streak of azure light.

Close to half a day later, a streak of azure light shot forth through the air above a nameless island countless kilometers away from Dark Veil Island. The streak of azure light circled around in the air a few times upon reaching the island, then faded to reveal Han Li in his cow mask, hovering in the air beside a small hill.

As soon as he appeared above the island, a burst of spatial ripples that were visible to the naked eye emerged not far away, and a gray figure stepped out of thin air.

The figure was wearing a red mask, and their entire body was enveloped in a layer of gray light that concealed their aura. Even though they were standing right in front of Han Li, they somehow felt extremely distant in Han Li's eyes, and he couldn't get a clear look at them no matter how hard he tried.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this.

In the instant that the masked figure had appeared, Han Li had been struck by the feeling that they were most likely even more powerful than Wyrm 3.

The gray figure sized up Han Li for a moment, then declared, "Wyrm 15, Wyrm 3 has recommended that we consider elevating you to an azure member of the guild. Your past contributions are nowhere near enough for you to be considered for a promotion, but seeing as Wyrm 3 was willing to use his one-time recommendation on you, there's nothing for me to say. However, you must complete a trial mission in order to secure the promotion."

Their voice was rather indistinct, and it was impossible to discern their gender and age range.

"I understand," Han Li replied with a nod.

"This is the list of the missions for you to select from," the gray figure said as he flipped a hand over to summon a crimson badge.

With a tap of his finger, the strange patterns on the badge lit up, and countless tiny runes emerged before intertwining with one another to form a crimson screen of light that was several dozen feet in size.

Lines of small text appeared on the light screen, describing the available missions for Han Li to choose from.

Han Li didn't waste any time with words as he immediately directed his gaze to the light screen and began to carefully read through its contents.

The missions were extremely diverse, involving tasks like overseeing a dangerous area for 10,000 years, slaying a powerful being that was ruling over a certain extremely distant region, and gathering various types of rare treasures.

The one thing that all of these missions had in common was that they all appeared to be very difficult, with many of them no less difficult than killing the lord of Red Moon Island.

Han Li's mind was racing as he read through these missions.

Given his current powers, there were some missions that were possible for him to complete, but all of those missions were going to take a very long time, and time was the one thing that he had the shortest supply of.

He didn't even want to wait for 10 years or 100 years, let alone thousands or tens of thousands of years.

The True Immortal Realm that he was situated in was rife with peril, and there were clearly some powers that he was unaware of trying to hunt him down. Otherwise, he wouldn't have lost 300 years' worth of memories and ended up in the Spirit Domain Realm.

He continued to inspect the list of missions while these thoughts were running through his mind, and all of a sudden, his gaze settled on a particular mission.

"Revive the seed of an unknown spirit medicine within 100 years."

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of this mission.

He didn't know what spirit medicine this seed belonged to, but given that he possessed the Heaven Controlling Vial, this was surely not going to be a difficult mission for him to complete.

With that in mind, he pointed at the mission on the light screen, making sure to remain composed as he asked, "Would you be able to elaborate on the mission concerning the revival of the spirit medicine seed?"

The light glowing from the gray figure's body flashed slightly, and they seemed to have been rather taken by this request. "Oh? Are you interested in that mission?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Is there a problem with this mission?"

"No, that's not it. This mission was released by an elder of our guild. He came across this spirit medicine seed by chance, but he hasn't been able to identify what spirit medicine it belongs to. On top of that, the seed is completely devoid of vitality. By his estimation, it would have to require wood-attribute power of laws of a certain level to have a chance at reviving the seed," the gray figure explained.

"I'll take this mission," Han Li replied with a nod.

The gray figure took a glance at Han Li, and they didn't ask any questions. Instead, they simply stowed the crimson badge away, then produced what appeared to be a white array plate before handing it to Han Li as they said, "This is an object transference plate, and someone will send the seed to you through this plate in a few days. If you can revive the seed, then send it back using this plate, and you'll have completed your trial mission."

Han Li accepted the plate from the gray figure, and a hint of intrigue flashed through his eyes. He had never seen anything of this nature outside of the Immortal Realm.

After Han Li selected his mission, the gray figure didn't stay any longer, raising their arm to release a burst of gray light, which flew forward before circling around in the air.

A spatial rift then opened up before transforming into a murky gray spatial passageway, the edges of which were giving off a faint glow.

The gray figure stepped into the spatial passageway without sparing another glance at Han Li, instantly vanishing into thin air, and the spatial passageway also closed in a flash behind him right after he stepped through it.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was quite stunned by what he had seen.

Within the gray light was an ordinary-looking talisman with some profound golden patterns on its surface.

It was able to break through space with ease, and Han Li could sense a type of special law fluctuations emanating from it, so it clearly was no ordinary object, yet the gray figure seemed to have only been using it as a transportation device, and that certainly appeared rather excessive.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then flew away into the distance as a streak of light.

That night.

Luo Feng hurriedly arrived in the courtyard that Han Li was staying in with an urgent expression, and as soon as he arrived, he immediately cupped his fist in a respectful salute as he declared, "Luo Feng pays his respects to Senior Liu."

"Go and find me some high-grade spirit soils fit for growing spirit plants. There's no need to bring me too much of each type, but try and gather as many types as possible," Han Li instructed.

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately accepted the order without asking any questions.

......

Three days later.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in his secret chamber, and there was a white array plate hovering in front of him. The array plate was revolving on the spot while emitting a faint buzzing sound.

Moments later, a vast expanse of dazzling white light erupted out of the array plate, followed by a flurry of countless silver runes, which revolved around the array plate for a while before surging to the center of the plate to form a ball of white light.

The ball of white light swelled, then shrank, before scattering to reveal a palm-sized azure jade box hovering in the air above the array plate.

Han Li beckoned to the azure jade box, drawing it into his grasp, and after conducting a brief inspection to ensure that nothing was amiss, he removed the lid of the box.

Inside the box was a thumb-sized brownish-yellow seed that was dry and withered, resembling an unremarkable walnut.

Han Li carefully picked up the seed between two of his fingers, then held it in front of his eyes for a meticulous inspection.

After a long while, he shook his head as he concluded that the seed was indeed completely devoid of vitality, just as the gray figure had said.

Furthermore, he couldn't see anything special about the seed, so he didn't know why a seemingly high-ranking elder of the Transient Guild would go to such great lengths to have it revived.

After a moment of contemplation, he summoned his jade badge to open up the entrance to the secret area, then made his way inside before arriving on a plot of empty land behind the wooden hut. Once there, he flipped a hand over to produce a jade basin, which he set down onto the ground, and the basin was filled with some soil of different colors that were giving off strong spiritual power fluctuations.

This was a type of five-colored soil that he had mixed together on his own from the spirit soils that Luo Feng had gathered for him.

He wouldn't dare to proclaim that this composite soil would be capable of nurturing all spirit plants, but the majority of spirit plants would be able to live and grow in this five-colored soil

Han Li buried the seed in the spirit soil, then pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial.

It had been quite some time since he last used the vial, and a drop of green liquid had already appeared inside it.

He carefully dripped the drop of green liquid into the spirit soil, and the liquid quickly seeped in.

After that, he crossed his legs and sat onto the ground, closing his eyes as he released his spiritual sense to delve into the seed within the spirit soil.

Time slowly passed by, and close to half a day later, his eyes abruptly sprang open as an elated look appeared on his face.

As expected, a hint of vitality arose within the brownish-yellow seed around four to six hours after the green liquid seeped into the soil, and that hint of vitality was growing stronger at an extremely slow rate.

After making this observation, Han Li left the secret area and returned to his courtyard, setting up layers upon layers of restrictions before pulling out the small vial and placing it onto the ground.

It was already late at night, and the stars in the night sky were glowing brightly.

Countless rays of starlight instantly converged to fuse into the vial...

Time flew by in a flash, and in the blink of an eye, an entire month had passed by. At this point, another drop of green liquid had arisen inside the small vial, and Han Li immediately poured it onto the seed.

This time, hints of faint green coloration began to appear on the surface of the brownish-yellow seed...

Five months later, with the application of the sixth drop of green liquid, the vitality within the seed had recovered to close to 20%, and its originally dull and lifeless surface had also taken on a grayish-green color.

Another three months passed by in this fashion, and as Han Li applied one more drop of green liquid to the seed, a tiny little opening appeared on the surface of the seed amid a faint crack, and a tender seedling that was around an inch in length emerged.

Several white roots that resembled strands of silk also emerged from the underside of the seed, plunging themselves into the five-colored spirit soil.

Han Li was observing the green seedling before him with an intrigued expression.

He still didn't know what type of seed this was, but given its current state, it was definitely going to be an extremely remarkable spirit plant once it grew to full maturity.

The seed had originally been completely devoid of life, so the most difficult part was instilling it with a hint of vitality and preserving that newfound vitality. At this point, close to a quarter of the seed's vitality had already been restored, and it was gradually reaching a stable condition.

At this point, it had already been revived, and all that had to be done from here was to transfer the seed to some spirit soil, then slowly nurture it with a suitable wood-attribute spirit liquid, and it would only be a matter of time before it made a full recovery.

Of course, without the green liquid, this process could easily take tens of thousands of years, but that was not something for Han Li to worry about. In order to avoid unnecessary trouble, he had no intention of completely restoring the seed's vitality.

With that in mind, he returned to the secret chamber in the courtyard, and after putting on his cow mask, he flipped a hand over to produce that white array plate.

He placed the seedling and the jade basin onto the array plate, then waved a hand to activate the restriction enclosed within the plate.

A burst of white light arose from the array plate to envelop the jade basin, and in the next instant, the jade basin vanished into thin air.

Chapter 123: Black Sea Heavy Water Tome

Han Li continued to stare at the jade plate hovering before him in a silent, unblinking manner, and a long while later, the array plate began to emit a faint buzzing sound.

Bursts of white light then emerged from the jade plate to form a white array.

An indistinct gray shadow was standing in the array, and it was none other than the same Transient Guild envoy that had assigned Han Li his mission.

"I didn't think that you would actually be able to revive that seed, and it's even more remarkable that you managed to do it in less than a year. The elder who released this mission is quite curious about how you managed to accomplish this, and he requested me to ask about the method that you employed. He's willing to exchange for this method from you, and you can state the price," the gray figure said.

"I'm afraid I'm going to have to disappoint that elder. I just so happened to obtain a small vial of a special liquid by chance, and I used it to nurture the seed along with a type of five-colored spirit soil. Through some testing, I found that I was able to restore a hint of vitality within the seed, and only then did I dare to take on this mission.

“However, I only had a few drops of that liquid to begin with, and I used it all up to complete this mission. As for the method I used to create the five-colored spirit soil, I would be happy to offer that up for exchange if that elder is interested," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"That's a pity. If you ever get your hands on this type of liquid again, you can contact me at any time. That elder has told me that he's willing to offer you an immortal treasure in exchange. Now that you've completed your trial mission, from this day forth, you will officially be an azure member of our guild. This is your new mask, make sure to keep it safe."

The gray figure didn't ask any further questions, and he swept a hand through the air as he spoke.

A streak of azure light flew out of the jade plate, then fell into Han Li's grasp, revealing itself to be an azure cow mask. Aside from the color, which had turned from blue to azure, it was no different in appearance to Han Li's current mask, and it even retained the number "15" on its glabella.

"Thank you, esteemed envoy," Han Li said as he held onto the azure mask and extended a bow toward the gray figure in the array.

The gray figure didn't say anything further, and with a wave of his hand, he vanished on the spot, following which the white array around him also disintegrated into thin air.

Thus, peace and quiet returned to the secret chamber.

Han Li gently stroked the dense patterns on the mask while sensing the peculiar fluctuations emanating from it, and a moment later, he removed his blue mask before replacing it with his new mask.

After putting on the new mask, it immediately began to ripple with a gentle watery glow, and the blue cow mask that had just been removed disintegrated into nothingness without any warning.

In the next instant, a passage of glowing golden text surfaced in Han Li's mind.

The passage of text contained the method to utilize the mask's many functions. In addition to the old features, which included disguise adoption, aura alteration, and confidential voice transmission, he had also been given access to some new features, including releasing missions and exchanging resources with other members of the same tier.

After memorizing everything, Han Li raised his middle and index fingers together, then tapped them against his own glabella as he began to chant a peculiar incantation.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of gentle azure light emerged from the mask, much like a gentle breeze or a wave of rippling water, spreading throughout the entire secret chamber in a flash.

Within the area encompassed by the azure light, a projection of a massive array plate that took up virtually an entire wall of the secret chamber appeared before Han Li.

This was a square array plate that was of a glowing azure color, and it was riddled with complex array runes. At the very center of the array was a circular vortex roughly the size of a well, and it was slowly revolving while releasing bursts of spatial fluctuations.

The entire array plate was split up into two areas, one on the left and one on the right, with the circular vortex dividing the two. The top grids of the two areas contained the words "Missions" and "Exchange".

Right as Han Li was about to take a closer look, a burst of golden light emerged on the surface of the array plate, and a passage of golden text appeared on its surface, mostly comprised of some rules that had to be followed during exchanges.

Due to the fact that exchanges in the guild had to take place across realms, all of the items put up for exchange were appraised by professional personnel of the Transient Guild, and information like their quality, strengths and weaknesses, and even their places of origin, were all laid out in the descriptions attached to the items. To a certain extent, this ensured the fairness and openness of the exchanges.

Furthermore, if either side were to go back on an agreement, then the perpetrator would be dealt a severe punishment from the guild. In serious cases, they could even permanently lose their guild membership.

After Han Li was finished reading through the rules, the passage of text faded away.

Han Li took a deep breath, then continued to inspect the array plate.

On the left side of the array plate, under the heading of "Missions", there were a series of summaries of missions inscribed vertically, and listed after the descriptions of those missions were the rewards for completing them.

At a rough glance, Han Li saw a variety of missions, including requests to search for certain individuals, hiring notices for assassins, and invitations to join a group of cultivators to explore secret regions. There was a great deal of diversity in the missions on offer, and the rewards also fluctuated depending on the difficulty of the missions.

In contrast, the contents on the right-hand side "Exchanges" section were a bit more complex.

The items put up for exchange were split up into major categories like "spirit medicines", "spirit materials", "treasures", "talismans", and "scriptures", and all of the categories also had subcategories of different levels.

Han Li took a rough glance at all of the categories before focusing his attention on the "scriptures" category, where he began to take a closer look.

There were quite a few sub-categories under the "scriptures" category, and most of them contained cultivation methods of different attributes.

However, there weren't many cultivation methods for Ancestral Gods. In fact, there weren't even as many cultivation arts of this nature as what was available for sale in the Black Wind Sea. As for high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation arts, those were even rarer.

After searching for close to six hours, Han Li's eyes suddenly lit up, and he spotted an earth-attribute Earthly Immortal cultivation art by the name of the "Origin Earth Refining Arts".

According to the brief description provided, this was quite an advanced cultivation art, and upon attaining full mastery of the cultivation art, one would be able to at least reach the Golden Immortal Stage.

However, after seeing the asking price for this cultivation art, Han Li was immediately left feeling deflated. The owner of the cultivation art was asking for a mature Fire Origin Dragon Tooth Fruit in exchange.

According to the description, this was a type of spirit fruit that contained the power of laws of fire. Not only was it extremely difficult to find trees that this fruit that bore this fruit, the fruit itself also required tens of thousands of years to reach full maturity, just like a Profound Heavenly Fruit.

Furthermore, as soon as the fruit emerged, it would immediately begin to release a strong fragrant aroma, and it was often the case that the fruit would be eaten by spirit beasts before reaching full maturity. Hence, mature specimens of this fruit were extremely rare, and there was very little supply to meet the demand.

Hence, he had no choice but to give up on this cultivation art and search for another one.

Around an hour later, he found another Earthly Immortal cultivation art by the name of the "Heavenly Glacial Ice Arts". This was a cultivation art of an inferior caliber to the Origin Earth Refining Arts, but it was a water-attribute cultivation art, so it was very suited to the environment in the Black Wind Sea.

However, the asking price was just as steep. In exchange for the cultivation art, Han Li would have to go and search for an item in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

The mission duration was 100 years, and regardless of whether the requested item was secured or not, one would be able to obtain the cultivation art as long as they didn't perish in the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm.

Han Li naturally immediately gave up on this cultivation art as well.

Over the course of a day and a night, he scanned through virtually all of the cultivation arts up for exchange, and aside from those previous high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation arts, he only managed to find one more, a cultivation art by the name of the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome.

This was a rather intriguing cultivation art in that not only could it allow one to attain the power of water laws through harnessing the power of faith, one could also use the cultivation art to derive heavy water from seawater. This derivation process was also the process through which users of this cultivation art could attain more immortal spiritual power, so it was truly killing two birds with one stone.

According to the summary of the cultivation art, there were nine tiers of heavy water that could be derived using this cultivation art, and theoretically, it could help a cultivator progress beyond the True Immortal Stage to reach the Golden Immortal Stage.

The reason why it was stated that this was only achievable in theory was because no one had successfully accomplished this in practice. This wasn't because this cultivation art was too profound and difficult to cultivate. On the contrary, it was far easier to cultivate than the previous two cultivation arts, but the process of deriving heavy water was quite difficult, and it required an extremely long time.

Furthermore, the further one advanced in this cultivation art, the longer the time it would take.

The Earthly Immortal who invented this cultivation art was only able to derive three levels of heavy water, which roughly equated to the amount of water in a small creek, and even that had taken him close to 500,000 years. In the end, he was only just barely able to reach the mid-True Immortal Stage, and for a time, he was the laughingstock of all of his fellow daoists.

After that, he was also unable to bear the snail-like progress in this cultivation art, and he switched to a different one. By his estimates, it would've most likely taken him tens of millions of years for him to complete the cultivation of the subsequent six levels.

However, Han Li wasn't too bothered by this. After all, his objective was never to pursue the path of the Earthly Immortal, and he was only using an Earthly Immortal cultivation art as a temporary means for him to recover his magic power.

Furthermore, it was exactly due to this fatal flaw that the asking price for this cultivation art was far cheaper than for the other two. All that was being requested in exchange was any type of material that contained the power of laws.

After making up his mind, Han Li joined his middle and index fingers before tapping them against his own glabella, and a wisp of azure light flew out from within, then landed on the spot where the "Black Sea Heavy Water Tome" was situated on the array plate, where it vanished out of sight.

Around 15 minutes later, a beam of azure light was projected down into the secret chamber from the array plate.

A projection of a male figure wearing an azure raccoon mask, and his build was remarkably tall and muscular. He was dressed in a set of rather strange tribal attire, and he didn't seem to be human.

"I take it that my Black Sea Heavy Water Tome has caught your eye, Fellow Daoist?" the man asked as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li.

His voice was very loud and clear, but he spoke in a rather warm tone.

Han Li returned the man's salute, then replied, "Indeed. I can see that you've requested any type of material that contains the power of laws in exchange for the cultivation art, but you haven't offered any further information. Would you be able to elaborate, Fellow Daoist?"

Chapter 124: Grand Earth Fruit and Sea Condensing Crystal

"Just as there are disparities in the quality of cultivation arts, the same naturally also applies to materials that contain the power of laws. Hence, the number of items required to exchange for my cultivation art will depend on the quality of the items offered," the man said with a smile.

Han Li paused for a moment, then flipped a hand over, and one of those strange walnuts with human-face-like patterns etched on their surface appeared on his palm.

As soon as the item was summoned, it immediately began to release a powerful earth-attribute aura.

"Would something like this be satisfactory to you, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li asked as he took a glance at the man.

The man faltered slightly upon seeing this, and he reflexively took a half step toward Han Li, but then immediately caught himself, putting on a nonchalant smile as he said, "This Grand Earth Fruit does indeed contain a hint of earth law powers, but it's not very abundant at all, so if you want to exchange this for my cultivation art, then I'll be requiring at least 10 of them."

Grand Earth Fruit, eh? So that's what it's called...

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he filed this tidbit of information away in his mind, and he was in no hurry to respond. Instead, he merely watched the man in an expressionless silence.

The man heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this, thinking that the reflexive half-step he had taken toward Han Li just now had already exposed his desire for the fruits, and he amended, "If you have Grand Earth Fruits of a higher caliber than this one, then I can accept five instead."

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he raised two fingers as he bartered, "Two."

"That's a little unreasonable of you, is it not, Fellow Daoist? This Black Sea Heavy Water Tome is indeed a slightly flawed cultivation art, but it's still a genuine high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation. There's no way I can trade it for just two Grand Earth Fruits," the man said as he waved his hands insistently.

"While this is indeed a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation art, I would think you know better than anyone that it's not just 'slightly flawed'. Due to its limitations, this cultivation art is next to useless for the vast majority of people, so surely two Grand Earth Fruits will suffice in exchange for it," Han Li countered.

The man contemplated Han Li's words for a moment, then said in a hesitant manner, "I'm afraid I can't accept two Grand Earth Fruits. How about you add one more and make it three instead, Fellow Daoist?"

Han Li paused momentarily upon hearing this, then said, "I can throw in another one, but you have to answer a question for me first."

The man was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "Answer a question? That's all I need to do?"

"That's right, I'm sure you know the answer to this question, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said with a smile.

After some contemplation, the man nodded and prompted, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist."

"Truth be told, even though I managed to secure several Great Earth Fruits by chance, I don't know anything about what they do, and I was hoping you would be able to tell me, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said.

The man faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a wry smile appeared on his face as he replied, "You've asked the right person, Fellow Daoist. This fruit is a very special wood-attribute spirit fruit, and it requires 100,000 years to grow into a seedling, 1,000,000 years to develop into a tree, and 10,000,000 years to bear fruit that contains the power of earth laws. It's an exceptional material for refining high-grade immortal treasures and weapons."

"Thank you for enlightening me, Fellow Daoist. Let's complete this trade now," Han Li said with a faint smile.

The man didn't say anything further, merely nodding in silence.

The two of them each raised a hand at the same time, and an object emerged from each of their palms, then flew toward the vortex at the center of the array plate.

What was different was that Han Li had released a human-faced walnut that was giving off earthy yellow light, while the man had released an ancient book.

As soon as the three fruits flew into the vortex, they immediately vanished without a trace.

Shortly thereafter, a burst of light arose from the array plate, and an ancient book with a dark azure cover slowly flew out of the circular vortex.

Han Li reached out to catch the book, then gave it a brief inspection with his spiritual sense, and only after verifying that there was nothing amiss about the book did he turn his gaze back to the man.

At this point, the man just finished examining the three Great Earth Fruits as well, and he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li, then vanished on the spot.

An amused smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. He knew that the man was feeling a little angry that he had gotten the short end of the stick, but he didn't care. After stowing the cultivation art away, he turned his attention back to the array plate again.

He now had a high-grade Earthly Deity cultivation art, but he was still missing the materials required to refine an Earthly Deity Avatar.

Han Li had originally intended to use these Great Earth Fruits as the main material to refine his Earthly Deity Avatar, but now that he had decided to cultivate the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome, he had to find a material that contained the power of water laws, so he couldn't use those fruits anymore.

Given his current situation, this should've been a rather simple task.

He raised a hand toward the "Exchanges" section of the array plate, then put up his Great Earth Fruits in exchange for a material that contained water law powers.

Given his observations up to this point, he could tell that even though the Transient Guild was quite a mysterious organization, its operations clearly weren't limited to just the Black Wind Sea, and it had to have quite a high number of guild members. Otherwise, there was no way that such a massive intraguild exchange platform could've been established.

Seeing as there were so many people trading things on the exchange platform, Han Li was confident that it wouldn't be a difficult task to exchange his Great Earth Fruits for a material that contained the power of water laws.

After doing all of that, Han Li did away with the projection of the array plate with a sweep of his hand, then sat down with his legs crossed and pulled out the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome for a thorough reading.

Just as he anticipated, several people contacted him through his mask over the course of just seven or eight days, offering items to trade for his Great Earth Fruits.

However, Han Li didn't immediately accept any offer. Instead, he waited another few days, then carefully compared all of the dozen or so offers that he had received before deciding on a material known as the Sea Condensing Crystal.

The material contained an immense amount of water law powers, and it was extremely suitable to be used with the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome. Apparently, just this fingernail-sized piece of crystal alone contained the essence of a region of sea tens of thousands of kilometers in radius. Hence, it was far more precious than Great Earth Fruits, and Han Li had to exchange virtually all of his remaining Great Earth Fruits and some other spirit materials for that tiny piece of crystal.

Once everything was prepared, Han Li immediately went into seclusion.

The seasons changed, and over a year passed by in the blink of an eye, as was often the case in the True Immortal Realm.

During this time, Han Li continued to nurture the Soulbirth Flower using the green liquid produced by the vial while also studying the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome day and night, making final preparations for the refinement of his Earthly Deity Avatar.

On this day, on a certain region of the seabed around 10,000 kilometers away from Dark Veil Island.

The terrain of the seabed here was rather uneven, forming a series of rocky structures that resembled an underwater mountain range.

These rocky protrusions were dark red in color with bumpy and uneven surfaces, and they were formed by cooled magma.

A series of dark holes could be seen on the seabed here, and it was unknown where these holes led to.

This was a cluster of underwater volcanoes that erupted very often, so the general area was very rarely frequented.

On a certain flat section of the seabed was a massive hemispherical blue barrier that kept out the surrounding seawater, and it was impossible to see what was going on inside from outside the protective barrier.

Seated at the center of the array with his legs crossed was none other than Han Li.

There were around a dozen massive stone pillars standing around him, while at the center was a fire-attribute array engraved out of crimson runes.

A long while later, he slowly opened his eyes, and there was a solemn look on his face as he began to chant something.

The crimson array beneath him immediately sprang to life, and the dozen or so stone pillars around him began to glow with dazzling crimson light. Even through the blue protective barrier, the surrounding seabed in a radius of several kilometers was completely illuminated.

As he made a hand seal, the ground around him began to rumble and quake.

Moments later, he let loose a low cry, and a series of cracks abruptly appeared on the ground at the very center of the array. That area was around 10 feet in size, and there were no engravings on the ground there. All of a sudden, the cracks fell away to reveal a huge hole.

Within the hole was a vast expanse of bright red, and from there, one could clearly see waves of churning magma not far beneath the ground, as well as the scorching flames burning on top of the magma.

These flames were of a faint reddish-golden color, and it wasn't normal magma groundfire. Instead, it was a type of special fire known as deepsea groundfire, and not only was it capable of mixing and coexisting with seawater, it was many times more powerful than normal groundfire.

Extraordinary waves of heat were radiating out of the huge hole, causing the surrounding seawater to boil and churn.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared near the opening of the hole, then sat down once again with his legs crossed before flicking his fingers through the air in quick succession.

The surrounding array immediately began to operate a little faster, releasing bright red light that was flowing incessantly into the hole.

The magma underground also began to ripple and flow toward the hole's opening.

A pillar of light golden flames abruptly erupted out of the hole in the ground, and it rose up in a corkscrew fashion 70 to 80 feet up into the air, like a violent fiery geyser that could explode at any moment.

A serious look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he sped up even further with his output of incantation seals. As a result, the surrounding array began to glow even brighter, and wisps of red light surged out of the array to envelop the golden groundfire.

The violent groundfire instantly became more docile, as if it were a wild stallion that was slowly being tamed, taking on all types of different forms at Han Li's behest.

Only then did Han Li's serious expression ease slightly, and with a wave of his hand, a selection of materials of different colors appeared beside him.

Given his current level of magic power, it was impossible for him to refine these materials, so he had developed the bright idea to use this deepsea groundfire to do the job for him.

With a wave of his hand, a piece of white crystalline ore shot through the air before plunging into the groundfire, and the flames enveloped the piece of ore at his behest.

After an indeterminate period of time, the material slowly melted into a ball of semi-transparent white liquid.

Following a brief inspection, he swept his hand through the air again, and another material flew into the flames...

A month passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, almost all of the materials around Han Li had already been refined within the groundfire, and they had mixed together to form a millstone-sized blue ball that was slowly rolling in the fire.

His complexion was a little pale, and he flipped a hand over to summon a Cloud Crane Herb that he promptly devoured, and his complexion began to slowly improve. At the same time, he raised a hand to produce a dark blue crystal.

The crystal was glittering and translucent, and the blue radiance contained within it was clearly visible from the outside. The light was rippling gently like water, and tremendous power of water laws were radiating out from within.

This was none other than the Sea Condensing Crystal.

Han Li took a long look at the crystal, and after taking a deep breath, he tossed it into the groundfire before him.

The groundfire enveloped the crystal at his behest, and right at this moment, a layer of watery blue light suddenly appeared on the surface of the crystal, surging incessantly, making the entire crystal resemble a small ball of glittering water.

The deepsea groundfire was capable of melting metals with ease, yet it was completely kept out by this unremarkable-looking layer of faint blue light.

Chapter 125: Manifesting an Avatar

The Sea Condensing Crystal displayed no sign of melting at all, but Han Li wasn't surprised to see this. Instead, he was growing a little excited, and he began to chant an incantation before abruptly sweeping his arms through the air.

Dozens of array flags flew out of his sleeves in rapid succession, then arranged themselves in an orderly formation around the array before vanishing in a flash.

In the next instant, a series of balls of dazzling flames emerged in the surrounding area, then exploded one after another, and the red light radiating from the array immediately became around twice as bright as before. Countless red runes surged out of the array, forming streams of red light that fused into the groundfire.

A scorching aura surged forth violently from down below, and the surrounding temperature climbed once again, while the golden coloration of the groundfire deepened significantly.

Enveloped within the golden groundfire, the flow of blue light around the Sea Condensing Crystal finally began to slow, and the light was also being stripped away at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Finally, after an indeterminate amount of time had passed, the exterior of the crystal began to melt and take on a slightly murky appearance.

Han Li was quite relieved to see this, and he sped up even further in his hand seals.

As time passed, the Sea Condensing Crystal slowly transformed, taking on the shape of a heart.

Visually, it was still as bright and clear as ever, and its surface was radiating dazzling blue light.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li raised a hand, and the ball that all of the other materials had melted into flew forth at his behest while he cast an incantation seal with his other hand.

Another blue water-attribute array on the ground was instantly activated, glowing brightly to form a massive blue eight trigrams image that was buzzing incessantly.

All of the seawater in a radius of hundreds of kilometers began to tumble and churn, and countless vortexes of different sizes appeared on the surface of the sea before clashing violently with one another.

Traces of blue light that were barely visible to the naked eye emerged from the seawater, then converged toward Han Li while emanating incredibly rich water law fluctuations emanating.

Han Li made a hand seal, and countless wisps of blue light flew toward him, fusing into the blue ball in an orderly fashion at his behest.

A series of bulges instantly began to appear on the surface of the blue ball, only to then immediately vanish.

The ball slowly elongated, gradually transforming into a blue humanoid being, except it hadn't completely grown limbs yet, and its face was also completely devoid of features.

Han Li wore a solemn expression as he quickly chanted an incantation while releasing a series of incantation seals with his hands.

The blue humanoid creature continued to change shape, and finally, its limbs completely developed, and features that bore a strong resemblance to Han Li's also appeared on its face.

Han Li let loose a loud cry as a burst of azure light shot out of his hand to envelop the Sea Condensing Crystal beside him, slowly dragging it into the chest of the blue humanoid creature, where its heart was supposed to be.

A burst of dazzling blue light erupted into the sky from the blue humanoid figure's body, and even the surrounding groundfire was unable to impede it.

At the same time, a series of blue lines emerged from its chest, then quickly spread throughout its entire body like a system of meridians and blood vessels.

As more and more blue light converged from the surrounding area before vanishing into the humanoid figure's body, its liquid also quickly took on a solid state.

It didn't take long before a blue male figure appeared in mid-air, and a hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

At this point, the initial stage of his Earthly Deity Avatar's refinement was complete, and the process was going quite smoothly.

It was only thanks to the observations that Han Li had made on Luo Meng and Wyrm 8's flawed Earthly Deity Avatar that the creation of his own avatar was going so smoothly.

However, the Earthly Deity Avatar had only just taken shape, and it had to continue to be refined in groundfire in order to be consolidated.

Thus, he took a deep breath and began to make hand seals again.

Groundfire surged and enveloped the Earthly Deity Avatar, forming a fireball to continue the refinement process.

Time slowly passed by, and 49 days flew by in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and with a sweep of his sleeve, the giant fireball instantly scattered to reveal the Earthly Deity Avatar inside.

The avatar had shrunk significantly, but it was more condensed, and its entire body was giving off watery blue light, indicating that the refinement process was complete, but it still looked like nothing more than a lifeless empty vessel.

The next step was the final step to refining an Earthly Deity Avatar, and it involved imparting sentience upon the avatar.

With that in mind, Han Li looked around for a moment, then flipped a hand over to produce an object that was dripping with blood. It seemed to have been the heart of a certain demon beast, and it was set down onto the ground beside him.

A strong bloody odor that was interspersed with a peculiar fragrance was released by the heart.

On the bottom of a deepsea trench on the seabed hundreds of kilometers away from Han Li was a massive black hole. The edges of the hole were incredibly smooth, and it seemed to have been the lair of a certain sea beast.

All of a sudden, a massive black shadow shot out of the hole amid a resounding boom, revealing itself to be a massive fish demon that was several thousand feet in length.

The fish demon's entire body was as pristine as white jade, and there was a human face on its head with a mouth that was filled with two rows of sharp white fangs, presenting a terrifying sight to behold.

The fish demon sniffed around vigorously for a moment, following which an excited look appeared on its face, and it shot forth rapidly in a certain direction as a white shadow.

The white fish demon was incredibly fast, covering several kilometers in mere moments before drawing to an abrupt halt.

A ball of faint blue light was visible close to 10 kilometers up ahead, and it was giving off the alluring aroma of its favorite prey, the Sand Pig Beast.

However, there was a young human standing within the blue light, and even though his aura was quite weak, the fish demon's sharp intuition told it that this human was not to be messed with, and it was immediately left feeling a little hesitant.

The young human was naturally none other than Han Li, and a faint smile appeared on his face, even as his head remained lowered. Immediately thereafter, he abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, a loud splash rang out from the seawater beside the white fish demon, and Han Li appeared out of nowhere, then reached out and made a grabbing motion toward the fish demon.

A burst of terrifying power surged forth, and an explosion boom rang out from the surrounding seawater as it erupted to either side to produce a vacuum area.

The white fish demon was greatly startled by this turn of events, and dazzling blue light began to radiate from its body as it swept its pair of front claws forward.

The nearby seawater churned, and an incredibly thick pillar of water shot forth toward Han Li.

The pillar of water was filled with blue light that was rippling incessantly, and rumbling thunderclaps were ringing out from within.

The two bursts of power collided violently amid an earth-shattering boom, and the pillar of blue water abruptly exploded, while a series of arcs of blue lightning appeared out of thin air before hurtling toward Han Li.

These arcs of blue lightning were actual lightning. Instead, it was water lightning, which was only more powerful than normal lightning.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph, and he made no effort to take evasive measures as he flew directly toward the fish demon.

The arcs of blue lightning instantly exploded upon striking his body, and they were unable to inflict any damage upon him.

The white fish demon was clearly extremely alarmed to see this, and right at this moment, Han Li appeared behind the fish demon in a wraith-like manner, not giving it any time to react before throwing a punch into its head.

The fish demon's head instantly exploded, sending intracranial fluids splattering in all directions to instantly stain the surrounding seawater red.

A ball of blue light flew out of the sea of blood, then fled into the distance as quickly as it could.

Before the ball of blue light was able to get very far, an azure-robed figure suddenly appeared out of thin air, then reached out to grab the ball of blue light, which contained none other than the soul of the white fish demon.

The fish demon struggled vigorously, but was unable to break free.

Han Li took a glance at the soul in his grasp, then returned to the blue array in a flash.

This fish demon was known as a Net Maiden Demon, and it was an extremely rare water-dwelling demon.

In order to impart sentience upon a newly created Earthly Deity Avatar, one of these demons had to be killed on the spot so that its soul could be used as a catalyst.

Han Li had spent a great deal of time and effort to search for one recently, and he had finally managed to find a Net Maiden Demon nearby. Aside from the presence of the underwater volcanoes here, this was the other reason why he had decided to refine his Earthly Deity Avatar in this place.

He sat down with his legs crossed, then released an incantation seal, and the Earthly Deity Avatar also sat down with its legs crossed across from him.

He opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light, which enveloped the blue soul in his hand before descending onto the top of the Earthly Deity Avatar's head. At the same time, he was casting a rapid series of incantation seals.

Translucent light was shimmering on his glabella, and it was becoming brighter and brighter, gradually concealing his facial features and giving them a blurry appearance.

Fine beads of sweat began to slowly flow down his forehead. This was not a simple process for him, and he had to give it his full concentration.

After a long while, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and two bursts of translucent light erupted out of his pupils like two bolts of lightning flashing through the night sky.

He then made a hand seal, and a speck of green light flew out of his glabella. It was a miniature green figure, and it was none other than a small part of his soul.

In order to bestow sentience upon the Earthly Deity Avatar, he had split off a part of his soul to be injected into it. Only then would he be able to control the Earthly Deity Avatar as he pleased.

The miniature green figure vanished into the blue soul on top of the Earthly Deity Avatar's head in a flash, and it immediately released a vast expanse of green light to envelop the blue soul, as if the former were trying to assimilate the latter.

The blue soul immediately retaliated, opening its mouth to bite at the miniature green figure, only for the green figure to send it flying with a punch. As a result, the blue soul was sent crashing into the surrounding azure light, becoming rather feeble and dazed from the impact.

The miniature green figure grabbed onto the blue soul, then opened its mouth and bit down onto the soul before tearing a chunk off its body.

The blue soul immediately let loose an agonized howl as it struggled with all its might, but the miniature green figure was far stronger than it, and it tore another chunk out of the blue soul with its mouth.

In the blink of an eye, the blue soul was completely devoured by the miniature green figure.

Bursts of blue light appeared on the surface of the miniature green figure's body, and the blue and green light intertwined with one another, while the green figure sat down with its legs crossed atop the Earthly Deity Avatar's head. Meanwhile, Han Li was continuing to cast a rapid series of incantation seals, all of which vanished into the Earthly Deity Avatar's head.

All of a sudden, the Earthly Deity Avatar's eyes abruptly sprang open, and a hint of life had appeared in its previously empty and soulless eyes.

Han Li was very encouraged to see this, and he accelerated even further in his casting of incantation seals.

One streak of translucent light shot out of his glabella after another before vanishing into the Earthly Deity Avatar's head, and with each streak of translucent light that disappeared into its head, the Earthly Deity Avatar's eyes would become a bit more lively.

Han Li couldn't help but give a slight nod upon seeing this. Up to this point, everything in the refinement process had gone very smoothly, and all he had to do from here was to inject the juice of the Soulbirth Flower in order to stabilize the soul fragment within the avatar's body.

This was the most important step, and it was going to decide whether the refinement of his Earthly Deity Avatar was going to be successful or not.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over, and a dark green jade box appeared over his palm.

In the instant that the lid of the box was removed, a burst of dazzling golden light was revealed, and there was a golden peony-like spirit flower laying inside.

However, right at this moment, a wary look suddenly appeared in Han Li's eyes.

Five or six streaks of light had suddenly appeared in the nearby area, and they were rapidly approaching him from all directions.

Each streak of light was giving off a powerful aura, all of which were at the True Immortal Stage!

Chapter 126: Coercion

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he closed the jade box in his hand.

With his spiritual sense, he was able to instantly identify the unwelcome guests as soon as they appeared.

Flying at the forefront of the group was a burly man in a suit of engraved white armor with a hollow visor on his face. This was none other than Ancestral God Han Qiu's Earthly Deity Avatar, which Han Li had already battled once before.

Even through the mask, Han Li could still sense the cold killing intent in the Earthly Deity Avatar's eyes.

As for the five people behind the avatar, judging from their life-like features, yet slightly wooden expressions, it was clear that they were avatars as well.

Aside from a black-armored man and an elderly man with a yellow beard, there was also a pair of azure-robed daoist priests that seemed to have been a pair of identical twins. Han Li had never seen these people before, but from the information provided by Luo Feng, he was able to identify them as the Ancestral Gods of the nearby islands.

As for the final assailant, a woman in blue, that was a familiar face. It was none other than Mistress Gu Gu, who had accompanied Han Qiu on his previous visit.

The six of them seemed to have somehow concealed their auras, so Han Li was completely oblivious to their presence, even though they had appeared no more than several thousand kilometers away from him.

For True Immortals, a distance of several thousand kilometers was one that could be crossed in an instant.

Flying along at the front of the group, Han Qiu swept a hand through the air to release a streak of white light. It was a glowing white sickle, and in the blink of an eye, it swelled to over 1,000 feet in size before hurtling viciously toward Han Li.

The sickle wasn't an immortal treasure, but it was still a treasure that contained tremendous power, and even before it arrived, the nearby seawater had already been parted by its formidable aura.

At this moment, Han Li was at a vital juncture in the refinement of his Earthly Deity Avatar, and he wasn't even able to get up, much less defend himself.

However, he wasn't alarmed in the slightest as he calmly made a hand seal, then pointed in a certain direction.

A burst of blue light flew out of his fingertip, then vanished into the blue light barrier around him in a flash.

The blue light barrier glowed brightly as it became incredibly substantial and thick, following which countless wave projections appeared on its surface amid a splashing sound.

The light barrier was clearly an extremely powerful restriction, and as soon as it took shape, it was struck by the white sickle.

A resounding metallic clang rang out, and sparks flew in all directions as the sickle was repelled back through the air.

Meanwhile, the wave projections on the surface of the blue light barrier surged violently, but it wasn't sliced apart.

At the same time, Mistress Gu Gu and the others had already summoned their treasures as well. The black-armored man had summoned a dark golden scepter, the yellow-bearded elderly man was wielding an earthy yellow seal, the two azure-robed daoist priests had armed themselves with a pair of long blue halberds, while Mistress Gu Gu was holding a black longsword.

All five treasures were giving off dazzling radiance, and they struck the blue light barrier in unison right after the white sickle.

A string of resounding booms rang out, while the nearby seawater tumbled and churned violently.

However, these treasures were also kept out and repelled by the blue light barrier, just like the white sickle from before.

The blue light barrier trembled violently like a willow tree in the wind, and its surface churned and rumbled once again as if a series of massive waves were washing over it, and even though it quickly stabilized once again, the blue light radiating from it had already dimmed significantly.

Even though it was impossible to see clearly into the light barrier from the outside, one could just barely make out a pair of blurry figures seated across from one another with their legs crossed.

"Fellow Daoist Han Qiu, our differences from last time have already been settled. What is the meaning of this?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

"You can only blame yourself for being too greedy. If you really hadn't found Luo Meng's Soulbirth Flower, then why have you begun refining an Earthly Deity Avatar? That Soulbirth Flower is still some way away from reaching 10,000 years of age, but it should still just barely suffice," Han Qiu chuckled.

"I see that you're very familiar with the Earthly Deity Avatar refinement process. You waited this long before appearing right as I've reached the final step of my avatar refinement process. I'm assuming you did this because you're certain that I wouldn't be able to retaliate, right?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

"You're a smart man, Fellow Daoist. Right now, you have two choices, the first of which is to hand over the Soulbirth Flower, and we'll leave right away. You can continue to rule over Dark Veil Island, and we won't interfere with your rule. As for the second choice, I'm sure I don't need to spell it out for you," Han Qiu said with a cold smile.

Instead of responding to Han Qiu, Han Li turned to the other Ancestral Gods as he said, "Fellow daoists, I have no vendetta against any of you. Do you insist on working with Fellow Daoist Han Qiu to have me killed?"

"I may have only met you once before, but I'd consider us to be acquaintances, Fellow Daoist Liu. Hence, I'd advise you not to bother putting up futile resistance, Fellow Daoist. Seeing as you've already chosen to pursue the path of a Profound Immortal and attained a True Extreme Body, why would you go down the path of the Earthly Immortal?

“As long as you're willing to cooperate with us, we would be more than happy to allow you to continue to rule over Dark Veil Island," Mistress Gu Gu said.

"Cooperate? I see, so all of you just want me to become a puppet island master that will do your bidding like a lapdog," Han Li chuckled.

"We tried to be nice, but you've swatted our olive branch aside, so don't blame us for turning to violence. Fellow daoists, as long as you can help me kill this man, I'll be sure to follow through on everything I promised you," Han Qiu assured as he made a hand seal, and the white sickle swept toward Han Li once again.

The other five Ancestral Gods didn't say anything further as they also called upon their treasures, which crashed into the blue light barrier as streaks of light.

The blue light barrier trembled violently, and even though it was able to keep all of the attacks at bay, it had dimmed significantly once again, and there was only a thin layer of it left.

Inside the blue restriction, Han Li had fallen silent, and it was unclear what he was doing.

Han Qiu let loose a loud roar as he made a hand seal, and eight identical giant sickle projections appeared around the white sickle before revolving around it like the petals of a pristine white lotus flower.

The giant sickle lotus flower screeched through the air before crashing into the blue light barrier with an earth-shattering boom, and that was finally enough to shatter the light barrier into countless specks of blue light, revealing Han Li and his Earthly Deity Avatar inside.

The surrounding five treasures from the other Ancestral Gods instantly converged toward Han Li, and right at this moment, specks of blue light appeared around Han Li once again.

A series of hemispherical blue light barriers reappeared around him amid the sound of loud crashing water, and the light barriers appeared to be slightly thinner than the original one, but there were dozens of them this time.

Dazzling blue radiance erupted from the light barriers, giving them a mysterious appearance.

The five streaks of light crashed into the outermost light barrier, which was instantly destroyed, but the treasures contained within the streaks of light were also repelled.

Right at this moment, the other blue light barriers began to buzz incessantly, and the blue radiance glowing on their surface rippled like water. Streaks of blue light shot out of the surrounding seawater, and in the blink of an eye, the broken blue light barrier was restored.

Han Qiu was staring intently at the blue light barriers with a grim expression, and his expression was mirrored on the faces of his five allies as well.

Meanwhile, Han Li was situated in the array with his expression completely unmoved.

He was well aware of the risks involved in refining an Earthly Deity Avatar, and that was why he had secured this Thousandfold Wave Array for a heavy price as a safety precaution.

This array didn't possess any offensive capabilities, but its defensive prowess was incredible, and even with six True Immortals attacking it at once, it was not going to be broken so easily.

At this moment, a jade vial that was filled with golden liquid had already appeared in Han Li's hand, and he was beginning to tip the liquid onto the glabella of the Earthly Deity Avatar down below.

Outside the blue array, Gu Gu and the others didn't strike right away. Instead, all of them were looking at Han Qiu.

"Fellow Daoist Han Qiu, I don't think this man is just an ordinary Profound Immortal. It's not going to be easy to break through this array," the elderly man with the yellow beard mused with a grim expression.

"There's no need to be concerned at all, Fellow Daoist Ge. That man is trying to use a mere 8,000-year-old Soulbirth Flower to stabilize the soul of his Earthly Deity Avatar, and that's going to take at least a day and a night. With that much time on our hands, we'll definitely be able to break through this restriction," Mistress Gu Gu said with a cold smile.

"Indeed. Even with a mature 10,000-year-old Soulbirth Flower, there's no way he can complete this process without at least four to six hours," one of the azure-robed daoist priests chimed in with a nod.

"That is correct, fellow daoists. Let's kill this bastard, and we'll split the resources of Dark Veil Island evenly among ourselves!" Han Qiu urged.

His white sickle then began to glow brightly, and the white lotus flower was manifested once again before hurtling toward the blue light barrier.

At the same time, he made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a translucent little blue sword appeared before plunging forward like lightning.

A streak of blue swordlight that was several hundred feet in length swept through the air, and it was giving off a glacial aura that was tinged with hints of law powers as it flew toward the blue light barrier.

The outermost light barrier flashed erratically, and most of it was instantly frozen into ice.

The white lotus flower immediately took advantage of this opportunity to destroy that light barrier.

Everyone else also unleashed their own attacks, breaking through several more light barriers in the blink of an eye.

A derisive sneer appeared on Han Qiu's face upon seeing this, and with a flick of his wrist, a vast expanse of blue sword qi instantly surged forth, forming a sword mountain that crashed toward the blue light barrier.

The blue light barrier rippled violently once again before shattering moments later, and in the blink of an eye, the six Ancestral Gods had broken through around a dozen light barriers in succession.

Even though the Thousandfold Wave Array had a self-regenerative ability, the attacks coming from the six Ancestral Gods were too thick and fast for its self-repair ability to keep up.

As more and more light barriers were destroyed, they discovered that the deeper they went, the more resolute the light barriers became, thereby requiring more and more time to break through each light barrier.

This was a rather concerning discovery for them, and they all began unleashing their trump card abilities to attack the light barriers.

Time slowly passed by, and over two hours flew past in the blink of an eye.

At this point, the majority of the dozens of light barriers had already been broken, and there were only around seven or eight left.

However, these remaining light barriers were incredibly strong, and even though they were quivering incessantly in the face of the attacks from Han Qiu and the others, they displayed no signs of breaking at all.

An urgent look had crept into Han Qiu's eyes, and as he cast his gaze toward Han Li within the array, he was suddenly struck by an inexplicable sense of unease.

All of a sudden, he stopped what he was doing, then flipped a hand over to produce an egg-sized ball that was dark red in color, with red patterns visible on its surface, and it was giving off a peculiar aura.

Chapter 127: Surprise

"Everyone, get back!" Han Qiu yelled.

"That's Astral Yin Blood Lightning!" Mistress Gu Gu exclaimed at the sight of the dark red ball, then hurriedly backed away with everyone else.

At the same time, all of the other Ancestral Gods conjured up protective barriers of different colors over their bodies to shield themselves.

The red ball flew out of Han Qiu's grasp, transforming into a red shadow that crashed violently into the water barrier.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and a ball of scintillating crimson light that was thousands of feet in size appeared.

The enormous ball of light lingered in the air for several seconds before finally fading away.

At this point, several more of the blue water barriers around Han Li had already been destroyed, leaving only one final one left. Despite the wave projections surging incessantly over the surface of the water barrier, Han Li and the avatar seated across from him could already be clearly seen.

The explosion of crimson light had also blown a massive crater into the ground, and large volumes of red-hot magma were pouring out from down below before erupting in all directions, causing the nearby seawater to instantly bubble and boil.

This had no impact on Han Qiu and the others, and they were able to ward off the magma and the scorching temperatures with ease.

"As expected of Astral Yin Blood Lightning! Fellow Daoist Han, if you have one more of those, we'll be able to destroy the rest of this array in an instant!" the black-armored man said in an ecstatic voice.

"I only have one ball of this lightning, and I purchased it for a massive price several centuries ago during the Black Wind Island auction," Han Qiu harrumphed coldly with a pained look in his eyes.

"We still have plenty of time left. As long as we combine all of our efforts, we'll be able to break through this final barrier in no time!" Mistress Gu Gu said.

However, as soon as her voice trailed off, a long cry rang out from within the blue water barrier.

Blue light erupted from Han Li and his Earthly Deity Avatar in unison, forming an enormous pillar of radiance.

All of the water-attribute world's origin qi in a radius of hundred of kilometers converged toward the scene in a frenzy, forming an enormous vortex of spiritual qi that gushed into the Earthly Deity Avatar's body, causing the blue light that it was releasing to become brighter and brighter.

Within the blue light, the Earthly Deity Avatar stretched its limbs as if it had just awoken from a long slumber, and its face was just as expressive and full of life as a normal person.

"It's already done?"

"That's impossible!"

Han Qiu and the others were astonished by what they were seeing.

Han Li turned toward Han Qiu and the others through the water barrier with an indifferent expression, then flashed them a faint smile as he pointed a finger at the water barrier around him.

The final water barrier instantly faded away into countless translucent blue threads, which shot forth toward Han Qiu and the other Ancestral Gods like lightning.

Han Qiu and the others were still in a state of astonishment, and they hurriedly shot back in retreat, no daring to face the oncoming blue threads head-on.

Right at this moment, blue light flashed within the eyes of Han Li's Earthly Deity Avatar, and it raised its arms up into the air as it let loose a loud roar.

The blue light around it instantly brightened before churning violently like a ferocious wave, and a burst of laws of water surged through the blue radiance in a flash.

All of the seawater in a radius of several hundred kilometers instantly rose up to form an enormous wave that converged toward the Earthly Deity Avatar in a frenzy.

Han Qiu and the others were still rushing back in retreat, and they were caught completely off guard as the waves of seawater crashed into their bodies, exerting a burst of tremendous force upon them that slowed them down in their tracks.

However, as Earthly Immortals, they were never going to be impeded by the waves for any extended period of time, and they quickly broke free before continuing to fly back in retreat.

Mistress Gu Gu was the slowest out of everyone to react, and her body was instantly bound by the thin blue threads.

Right as she was about to unleash an ability to struggle free from the threads, they rapidly spread over her body as if they were living creatures, binding her up in layers to form a huge blue cocoon.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared beside the cocoon in a wraith-like manner before throwing a punch with a cold expression.

Even before his fist arrived, a devastating aura swept directly toward the ensnared Mistress Gu Gu.

Despite the predicament that she was in, Mistress Gu Gu didn't panic at all as she began to chant an incantation.

A black longsword instantly appeared outside the blue cocoon, then hurtled directly toward Han Li as a massive streak of black swordlight that was giving off indescribably fearsome sword intent.

Even before the streak of black swordlight reached Han Li, the terrifying sword intent that it carried had already infiltrated his mind, threatening to tear his soul apart.

Seeing as Han Li had just finished refining his Earthly Deity Avatar, Mistress Gu Gu was confident that his soul had to be in a very feeble state, and she was targeting that perceived weakness.

However, to her surprise, Han Li made no effort to evade the attack. His semi-transparent True Extreme Membrane appeared over his body in a flash, and his fist didn't slow down in the slightest as it crashed heavily into the blue cocoon as a golden shadow.

A blood-curdling howl rang out from within the cocoon, followed by a dull thump, and the cocoon bulged violently as the howl abruptly cut off.

Almost at the exact same moment, the streak of black swordlight also struck Han Li's shoulder with a loud clang.

The True Extreme Membrane on his body shuddered slightly before instantly returning to normal, warding off the fearsome attack. As for the burst of sword intent that the swordlight carried, it vanished into Han Li's mind without producing any effect, not even triggering the slightest change in his expression.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and by the time Han Qiu and the others returned to their senses and rushed forward to save Mistress Gu Gu, the aura of her Earthly Deity Avatar had already completely disappeared.

Han Li slowly withdrew his arm before releasing an incantation seal with a sweep of his hand, and the thin blue threads parted to reveal a broken Earthly Deity Avatar inside. The avatar was already completely shattered, and the spiritual light on its surface had also faded, making it resemble a cluster of broken rocks.

Han Qiu and the others exchanged a glance upon seeing this, and each of them could see their own shock and wariness mirrored in one another's eyes.

At the same time, the other four Ancestral Gods were all glowering at Han Qiu with furious expressions.

If they had known that they were going to be dealing with a Profound Immortal who was capable of destroying an Earthly Deity Avatar with just a single punch, then they would've never come here.

With a casual wave of his hand, Han Li stowed Mistress Gu Gu's storage treasure and that black longsword away. At the same time, his Earthly Deity Avatar vanished into his body in a flash as a blue shadow.

Only after doing all of that did he slowly sweep his gaze over the remaining Ancestral Gods, ultimately settling his gaze on Han Qiu.

His eyes didn't seem to bear any malice, but Han Qiu's heart instantly jolted at the sight of Han Li's scrutiny, and an intense sense of foreboding welled up in his heart.

All of a sudden, Han Li's body blurred, and he vanished on the spot.

"Look out!" Han Qiu yelled with a grim expression.

Immediately thereafter, he began to chant an incantation while sweeping his sleeves through the air, releasing a large plume of white smoke that formed a sea of white mist around him that was several hundred feet in size.

The other four Ancestral Gods were already considering retreat, and they hurriedly summoned their treasures or unleashed secret techniques to protect themselves.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared above Han Qiu in a wraith-like manner, and one of his arms had already swelled significantly in size. A layer of golden ape fur had also appeared on the arm, and it was glowing with dazzling golden light.

He let loose a low roar as he thrust his fist through the air, and spatial fluctuations instantly erupted above Han Qiu, following which a rapidly revolving golden vortex appeared.

An enormous golden fist projection flew out of the vortex with devastating power, and as it came crashing down, the white smoke around Han Qiu churned and tumbled violently, looking as if it could crumble away at any moment.

Han Qiu was horrified by this turn of events. This punch was far more powerful than any attack that Han Li had unleashed during their previous clash!

In a fit of desperation, he let loose a wild roar as he hurriedly made a hand seal.

A glacial aura instantly erupted out of the white mist, freezing the surrounding seawater into ice. A white mountain of ice that was giving off faint law fluctuations instantly took shape above Han Qiu's head.

The tip of the mountain was extremely sharp, and it rose up toward the golden fist projection like a giant sword of ice.

The two clashed with an earth-shattering boom, and the white mountain of ice shuddered violently before exploding, sending countless chunks of ice flying in all directions.

In contrast, the golden fist projection wasn't even slowed down in the slightest as it continued to crash down with incredible force.

In this dire situation, a metal shield flew out of Han Qiu's body, and it was giving off a burst of law fluctuations as it transformed into a black light barrier to stop the golden fist projection in its tracks for a brief moment.

The black light barrier was then instantly shattered, following the same fate as the white ice mountain.

However, Han Qiu was able to take advantage of that brief instant of respite to fly away into the distance as a blue shadow. Unfortunately for him, his left arm was grazed slightly by the fist projection, and it had been destroyed in an instant.

At this moment, Han Qiu's heart was filled with shock and horror, and he didn't even dare to take a single backward glance.

Right at this moment, a cold harrumph sounded beside his ears, and he was instantly struck by a burst of excruciating pain in his head, as if someone had driven a red-hot dagger straight into his brain.

He immediately stopped cold in his tracks as he threw his hands over his head and let loose a blood-curdling howl.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared directly in front of him before throwing a vicious punch, and Han Qiu's Earthly Deity Avatar also followed the same fate as Mistress Gu Gu, shattering into a pile of powder.

The other four Ancestral Gods were horrified to see this. They were already considering retreat, and they didn't hesitate any longer as they sped away into the distance as four streaks of light.

Han Li watched as the four Ancestral Gods fled the scene, making no effort to pursue them. Instead, he took Han Qiu's storage tools and treasures in an unhurried manner before inspecting the contents of the former with his spiritual sense.

After fleeing for tens of thousands of kilometers without rest, the four Ancestral Gods finally realized that they weren't being pursued, and they gradually drew to a halt as they stopped to catch their breath.

"Han Qiu has completely screwed us over! What was he thinking, inviting us to take on such a powerful enemy?" the yellow-bearded elderly man snapped in a furious voice.

The other three Ancestral Gods were also enraged.

"Judging from that man's abilities, he seems to be a Profound Immortal. No wonder he was so powerful," the black-armored man said with a hint of fear in his voice.

The two azure-robed daoist priests' expressions changed drastically upon hearing this.

They had only become Ancestral Gods a few dozen millennia ago, and they were among the weakest Ancestral Gods in the entire Black Wind Sea, so they were even more horrified to hear this.

"I couldn't care less about what happens to Han Qiu, but he's dragged up into this mess with him! I don't think that man is just going to let things slide and forgive what we did!" the yellow-bearded elderly man said with a concerned expression.

As Ancestral Gods, they were tied to their respective territories, so they couldn't just run away without suffering a severe loss in power.

This was exactly why all Ancestral Gods and Earthly Immortals were extremely cautious with everything that they did, taking the utmost care not to make enemies that they couldn't afford to make. On this occasion, they were lured in by the benefits promised to them, and they were of the opinion that this was virtually a done deal, which was why they had accepted Han Qiu's invitation, but never did they think that this would be the outcome.

The four of them exchanged a series of uneasy glances with one another.

They were only mere Ancestral Gods with no backers, so if Han Li were to come after them in vengeance, they were as good as dead.

Chapter 128: Breaking the Chains (1)

Han Li opened his eyes, then withdrew his spiritual sense from the storage treasure.

The Soulbirth Flower he had prepared had already reached 100,000 years of age, so the final soul manifestation process was completed in no more than 15 minutes. Furthermore, the outcome was close to perfect, and he was able to control the Earthly Deity Avatar as he pleased.

The reason why he had waited for over two hours was both to fool his opponents, as well as to lure them into expending more of their trump cards. Furthermore, he had expended a great deal of energy refining this Earthly Deity Avatar, and this gave him some time to recover.

Thankfully, he hadn't decided to reveal himself early. Otherwise, that bolt of Astral Yin Blood Lightning would've been nasty to run into.

Now that he had successfully attained an Earthly Deity Avatar, he had more important things to do, and those four Ancestral Gods were nothing more than small fry, so it didn't matter that he had allowed them to escape.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed away the array tools on the ground with a wave of his hand, then emerged from the sea before flying toward Dark Veil Island.

One morning, several days later.

Basked in the light of the rising sun, it was as if Dark Veil Island had been plated in a layer of gold, and the entire island was giving off a soft and warm glow.

Many residents of the island had already gathered in front of the Ancestral God statues on the island, and all of them wore solemn and reverent expressions as they clasped their hands together in front of their chests in prayer while chanting prayers incessantly.

At this moment, Luo Feng was in his usual azure scholarly robe, standing on the plaza at the center of the island as he looked up at the renovated Ancestral God statue.

Unlike the island residents behind him, he didn't participate in the prayers. Instead, his hands were hanging down by his sides, and he seemed to have fallen into deep thought.

Right at this moment, a streak of light suddenly flashed past above everyone, arriving at an incredible speed from afar before landing beside Luo Feng.

"Senior Liu!" Luo Feng greeted in a loud voice as he extended a deep bow toward the new arrival.

That person was naturally none other than Han Li, who had just returned to Dark Veil Island after successfully refining his Earthly Deity Avatar.

All of the residents of Dark Veil Island hurriedly ceased their prayers and turned to Han Li before extending respectful bows.

"Come with me," Han Li instructed in an indifferent voice, then flew up into the air again, traveling toward the courtyard that he was staying in.

Luo Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, then also immediately followed along as a streak of light.

The two of them landed one after another in the open-air area of the courtyard, and Han Li sat down beside the stone table before waving a hand at Luo Feng, indicating for him to take a seat as well.

"Chief Luo, there's something that I've been keeping from you this entire time, but there's no need for me to keep the secret any longer. Truth be told, Ancestral God Luo Meng of your Dark Veil Island has already been dead for over 1,000 years."

Luo Feng's complexion paled slightly upon hearing this, and a wry smile appeared on his face as he replied, "Senior Liu, I had already roughly guessed that this was the case, and the other elders on the island are aware of this as well, but we've all made an unspoken agreement not to speak about this as we didn't want to spark a panic among the island's residents.

“We'll be counting on you for the continued protection of our island, Senior Liu. Words cannot begin to express my gratitude to you."

"You don't have to worry about that. I made a promise to you, and I intend to see it through. At this point, I've already successfully refined an Earthly Deity Avatar and found a high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation method. Now, I need you to erect deity statues of myself on the island so I can begin to gather the power of faith," Han Li said with an indifferent expression.

Luo Feng was slightly taken aback to hear this, but he then quickly cupped his hand in a salute as he replied, "Rest assured, Senior Liu, I'll get that arranged as soon as possible."

"Here are some treasures and scriptures for you to use on nurturing the brightest talents on the island. Their growth will be the key to Dark Veil Island's future prosperity."

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and a storage bracelet flew through the air before arriving in front of Luo Feng.

Luo Feng caught the bracelet, and after only a brief inspection of its contents, a stunned look appeared on his face. The quantity and the value of the items in the storage bracelet far exceeded his imagination.

In fact, it was no exaggeration to say that just the scriptures, treasures, pills, and materials contained within this storage bracelet alone already far exceeded everything that had been accumulated on the island over the past tens of thousands of years.

Unbeknownst to him, this was only a small portion of the spoils that Han Li had obtained from his prior trip to Red Moon Island. The life savings of any True Immortal, even if they were merely a vagrant immortal, was nothing to be scoffed at.

Luo Feng held the storage bracelet with both hands, and his body was trembling uncontrollably as he knelt down and kowtowed onto the ground. "Senior Liu, our Dark Veil Island will eternally remember what you've done for us."

"There's no need for such formalities. From this point onward, I'm going to go into seclusion for a while, so don't come to find me unless something urgent comes up," Han Li said with a wave of his hand.

"Yes, Senior Liu," Luo Feng replied in a solemn voice, then departed from the courtyard.

Half a month later, all of the original deity statues on Dark Veil Island were removed and replaced by new statues, which were erected all over the island in a higher concentration.

The newly constructed deity statues still bore a slight resemblance to the former deity statues, but they represented a different person.

Every morning and night, large numbers of island residents would gather beneath Han Li's statues and pray, just as they had always done in the past.

On this night, a resounding boom suddenly rang out in the sky above Dark Veil Island, and a vast expanse of dazzling silver radiance cascaded straight down from the night sky before surging into the courtyard that Han Li was staying in like a falling galaxy.

There were seven or eight huge silver flags standing around the courtyard, and all of them began to glow brightly before quickly being enveloped in a layer of dense silver mist.

At this moment, the azure-robed Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in an empty area in his courtyard, and his Earthly Deity Avatar was also seated across from him with a solemn look on its face.

"Let's begin," Han Li declared.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately closed his eyes, and his spiritual sense descended into his dantian.

Inside his dantian, the golden nascent soul's eyes were still tightly shut, but there was no pain etched on its face.

Furthermore, it was enveloped in a layer of shimmering translucent light, and that was the spiritual sense that Han Li had left behind to conceal the black chains.

The translucent light around the nascent soul instantly brightened significantly at his behest, then surged back into his consciousness like flowing water.

Immediately thereafter, black light flashed over the body of his nascent soul, and the nine inky-black chains emerged, while a vast expanse of black mist rose up around them.

Meanwhile, the entire courtyard was basked in radiant starlight, and seven balls of dazzling blue light also appeared on Han Li's chest and abdomen. The Earthly Deity Avatar seated across from him immediately made a hand seal upon seeing this, then pointed a finger at his dantian.

As it did so, Han Li felt a burst of heat rise up within his dantian, and a surge of vast and warm magic power immediately flowed forth like a mighty river to wash through his entire body.

At the same time, the starpower within his body began to rapidly circulate, transforming into countless thin silver threads that surged through his limbs and his meridians.

As Han Li made a series of hand seals, the two bursts of power finally gathered in his dantian without any obstacle, then transformed into thin threads of bright silver light that plunged straight toward his nascent soul.

In contrast with last time, both the number of silver threads and the power of the aura imbued within them exceeded the previous batch by over a hundredfold.

In fact, Han Li could sense traces of power of laws that hadn't been present previously in this aura.

A resounding boom rang out like a rumbling thunderclap in Han Li's dantian, and the converging threads of silver light instantly surged into the vast expanse of dense black mist with unstoppable force, much like a mighty army of cavaliers.

Immediately thereafter, a loud string of cracks and pops rang out within Han Li's dantian, and the black mist was completely torn apart, quickly dissipating to reveal the black chains concealed within.

The threads of silver light showed no signs of stopping there, and they continued to converge toward the black chains.

This time, Han Li didn't try to hurry the process by distributing the threads of light onto all of the chains at once. Instead, he selected one of them and directed all of the threads of light to wrap around that single chain.

A burst of loud sizzling akin to the sound of red-hot metal being cooled in water rang out, and plumes of black smoke immediately began to rise up from the black chain. The chain began to tremble violently, and the black light glowing from its surface rapidly faded.

At the same time, countless tiny black runes also emerged from the black chain, trying to replenish the black light that was being rapidly whittled down.

All of the threads of silver light were enveloped in a layer of watery blue light that was giving off law fluctuations, and this blue light was fusing with the black runes to significantly hamper the restoration effect that the runes had on the chain. As a result, the rate at which the chain was recovering was nowhere near as fast as last time.

Han Li immediately activated his Spirit Refinement Technique upon seeing this, and the vast spiritual sense in his consciousness instantly transformed into translucent threads of spiritual sense that surged into his dantian in the blink of an eye.

The translucent threads of spiritual sense intertwined with one another at his behest to form a giant ax, which sprang up before crashing down upon the black chain.

If the threads of silver light from before could be compared with an army of cavaliers, then this ax of spiritual sense would be akin to a unit of heavy infantry, charging through the opening created by the cavaliers to deal the enemy a lethal blow.

A sharp clang rang out, and the black chain shuddered violently, while the ax of spiritual sense was sent flying back.

The clang ringing out from the clash was extremely penetrative, and even though it had originated in Han Li's dantian, it was able to resonate all the way to his consciousness, striking him with a burst of sharp pain.

However, the entirety of his attention was focused on the chain in his dantian, and he couldn't afford to get distracted.

A clear chip had appeared on the chain at the spot where it had just been struck by the ax, and Han Li was instilled with an immense sense of confidence upon seeing this.

He paid no heed to the sharp pain spearing through his consciousness as he continued to hack away at the chain with the ax.

One strike, two strikes, three strikes...

As the seventh strike was dealt, a dull thump rang out, and the black chain snapped in half before disintegrating into black light.

However, instead of dissipating into nothingness, the black light surged into the remaining eight chains, vanishing into them in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, the eight chains lit up in unison, and the number of black runes on their surfaces instantly increased, while the black light glowing from them also became denser and more substantial.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a wry smile appeared on his face.

If every single one of these chains was going to fuse with the other chains after being snapped, then that meant that each subsequent chain would become more difficult to sever than the previous one.

Chapter 129: Breaking the Chains (2)

Right as the first chain around Han Li's nascent soul was destroyed, the thin and withered man seated on the huge black chair in the underground palace countless kilometers away from the Black Wind Sea suddenly stirred slightly. His eyelids then slowly peeled back to reveal a pair of murky eyes that appeared as if they were affected by cataracts.

At the same time, all of the dark azure chains in the entire underground palace around him immediately rose up from the ground as if they were weightless feathers, and they began to tremble and screech incessantly.

A contemplative look appeared on the man's face, but that was quickly replaced by a cold smile, and he slowly closed his eyes again without doing anything further.

All of the chains in the palace quietly descended onto the ground again, and peace and quiet were restored.

……

In the small courtyard on Dark Veil Island, Han Li's eyes were tightly shut, and he was focusing all of his attention on directing the threads of silver light toward the second black chain.

Right at this moment, his brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and something resonated within his consciousness.

He had a vague feeling that by severing the first chain, he seemed to have alerted a certain terrifying being on the other end of the chain.

This immediately struck him with a sense of anxiety, and he was very concerned that a new chain would appear in his dantian out of nowhere like last time.

Thankfully, even after a long while had passed, no new chains appeared, and he was quite relieved as he returned his attention to the second chain.

The silver threads of light formed by his magic power and starpower latched onto the second chain one after another, quickly enveloping the entire chain.

Just like last time, black smoke immediately began to rise up from the surface of the chain, while the black light radiating from it rapidly receded.

However, compared with last time, the rate at which the black light was receding was clearly slower, and at the same time, Han Li's threads of silver light were also being whittled down at a faster rate.

As a result, progress was significantly slower.

……

One night, several days later, the pillar of silver light in the courtyard disintegrated into specks of silver light amid a resounding boom.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes as he cast his gaze toward the Earthly Deity Avatar seated across from him, and a hint of exhaustion flashed through his eyes.

During these past few days of tireless toil, a large number of the black runes on the second chain had been erased, and in the end, he was able to snap it with several dozen strikes of his spiritual sense ax.

However, following this ordeal, what little magic power that Han Li had in his body and the magic power that had been converted from the power of faith by his Earthly Deity Avatar had all been exhausted, so he was forced to temporarily stop what he was doing.

"Looks like I'm in it for the long haul," Han Li sighed to himself, then flipped a hand over to produce a pill, which he devoured before closing his eyes to meditate.

Meanwhile, his Earthly Deity Avatar was seated beside him with a placid expression, and its entire body was glowing with blue radiance as it absorbed the power of faith being transmitted to it from the deity statues all over Dark Veil Island.

……

Meanwhile, in the Driftcloud Realm.

High up in the sky, there were countless massive clouds of different shapes and forms scattering and gathering haphazardly with the blowing of the wind.

As the sun continued to travel across the sky, the angle at which the sunlight was cascading down was constantly changing, and as a result, the colors of the clouds were also changing, taking on all of the colors of the rainbow.

Beneath a huge cloud that resembled a five-colored phoenix was a lush mountain range that stretched for over 1,000 kilometers in length. The meandering mountain range resembled a hibernating wyrm, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

At the very center of the mountain range was a lone mountain that was over 10,000 feet tall, towering far above the other mountains around it.

The entire bottom half of the mountain was covered in lush greenery, while the plants on the mountain summit, which reached all the way up into the clouds, were more sparse, and there were exposed slabs of white rock everywhere.

A spacious white plaza had been constructed on the mountain summit, and near the cliff at the rear of the plaza stood a majestic golden palace.

At this moment, there were several dozen cultivators dressed in all types of different attire gathered in the palace, resembling officials of mortal empires as they stood on either side of the palace with respectful expressions.

There were people of both genders and a wide range of different ages and appearances among these cultivators, but every single one of them was at the Grand Ascension Stage, with no exceptions.

At this moment, the main seat at the center of the palace was occupied by a young man dressed in a tight-fitting black robe. He appeared to be no more than 20 to 30 years of age, and he was very handsome, with a pair of sharp and piercing eyes. This young man was none other than Fang Pan, who had been sent to the Driftcloud Realm to quell the beast tide.

Among the Grand Ascension cultivators, an elderly man in a gray daoist robe stepped forward, then informed Fang Pan in a respectful voice, "Immortal Envoy Fang, thanks to the combined efforts of the Immortal Revelation Sect, the Eminent Flame Sect, and many other cultivation sects on the Eastern Stream Continent and the Western River Continent, the beast tide on those two continents have already been completely suppressed. I'm sure it won't take long before the beast tide is completely quelled."

Everyone in the palace was full of awe and veneration toward this immortal envoy who had come from the Immortal Realm, not just because he possessed unfathomable power, but also because of his excessive brutality.

Upon arriving in the Driftcloud Realm, he immediately announced a series of countermeasures to be adopted against the beast tide, and not only had he instructed all of the sects to strictly follow these measures, he had personally overseen their implementation.

Several of the elders from major sects had been killed for not carrying out his instructions with a satisfactory level of efficiency, but none of the cultivators in the palace dared to harbor even the slightest resentment toward the immortal envoy.

Of course, part of this was because they didn't dare to harbor such feelings, but another reason for this was that he had been extremely diligent in dealing with the beast tide, even more so than the people of the Driftcloud Realm themselves.

On many occasions, they had witnessed him charging into the beast tide on his own to slay the most fearsome queen beasts concealed within.

After hearing this report, Fang Pan gave a slight nod, and he was just about to say something when a burst of yellow light suddenly lit up on his waist, accompanied by an urgent buzzing sound.

His expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he pulled out a circular communication plate before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Moments later, his expression began to darken slightly, and in the end, he was looking absolutely livid.

All of the cultivators in the hall were extremely anxious to see this, and they didn't even dare to breathe too loudly for fear of drawing attention to themselves.

After stowing the communication plate away, Fang Pan turned to everyone in the hall and declared, "All of you, set off at once. Order all of the sects to deploy all of their cultivators and eradicate the remnants of the beast tide on the two continents as soon as possible. Anyone who dares to go against this order will be executed on the spot!"

Everyone was stunned to hear this, but they didn't dare to raise any objections, and all of them accepted the order before departing from the palace.

It didn't take long before Fang Pan was the only one left in the palace.

He flipped a hand over to produce a semi-transparent white jade vial, which he held up in front of his own eyes. Looking at the drop of golden blood essence that was slowly sliding along the wall of the vial, he murmured to himself, "So what if you can break the Origin Separation Law Chains?

“Now that you've returned to the Immortal Realm, I'll be able to use this drop of blood essence to track down your exact location. Once I'm finished with this matter, I'll return to the Immortal Realm and deal with you myself! This time, you won't be getting away..."

A sinister look appeared on his face as he spoke, and his eyes were filled with cold killing intent.

……

Time continued to pass by, and an entire year flew past in the blink of an eye.

During this year, a silver pillar of light could be seen shining down from the night sky on Dark Veil Island virtually every night, and strange sounds were also frequently heard all over the island.

All of the island's residents knew that this was because the Ancestral God protecting their island was cultivating in seclusion.

Initially, they were rather disgruntled by this, but over time, they gradually grew accustomed to the commotion, and at this point, they were finding it difficult to sleep at night without the usual commotion.

However, on this night, the disturbance on the island was far more severe than normal, and the entire island was trembling incessantly. Even the sea around the island was being affected, resulting in the formation of countless giant waves.

Many of the island's residents were unable to sleep, so they gathered in front of the deity statues all over the island to offer up their earnest prayers.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in that small courtyard at the center of the island. His entire body was basked in bright starlight, and his eyes were tightly shut with a solemn look on his face.

His Earthly Deity Avatar was seated across from him, and watery blue light was glowing around its entire body. It was converting the power of faith in its body into magic power, which it was constantly injecting into Han Li's body.

At this moment, Han Li's dantian was completely filled with glowing white starpower, and his golden nascent soul was hovering within the white radiance.

At this point, eight of the black chains protruding out of its body had already disappeared, and there was only a single chain left. It was extending out of the nascent soul's lower abdomen, and it was a virtually substantial chain of a dark azure color.

This chain was the final chain that remained in the wake of the destruction of the eight other chains.

Thanks to the combination of the array and Han Li's starpower and magic power, Han Li was able to whittle down the black light glowing from the chain, and after over three months of toil, the black light was finally eradicated to reveal the chain within.

A translucent ax formed by spiritual sense appeared in Han Li's dantian at his behest, then rose up before crashing heavily down onto the final chain.

A resounding boom akin to a rumbling thunderclap rang out within Han Li's dantian, and the ax of spiritual sense was flung back before disintegrating into specks of translucent light, while the chain remained completely unharmed, with not even the slightest scratch on its surface.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, and it seemed that he had already anticipated this.

All of a sudden, he let loose a low cry, and all of the magic power in his body immediately surged forth, gathering all of the starpower in his dantian to form a glowing silver hand, which grabbed onto the chain.

At the same time, his consciousness began to churn violently under the effects of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and immense spiritual sense surged into his dantian, forming a giant translucent hand that also grabbed onto the chain.

After the two hands closed themselves tightly around the chain, both of them pulled back vigorously at Han Li's behest.

The black chain was instantly stretched taut amid a loud clang, and a burst of sharp pain speared through the nascent soul's body.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he injected more and more of his spiritual sense into his dantian, and at the same time, the two giant hands continued to tug on the chain with all their might.

The black chain was clanging and groaning incessantly, but it showed no signs of coming loose.

Chapter 130: Familiar

Right at this moment, a burst of azure light suddenly appeared on the dark azure chain, and a series of tiny dark azure runes emerged, releasing a burst of strange law fluctuations.

At the same time, Han Li felt a burst of strong suction force act upon the pair of translucent hands that were manifested from his spiritual sense, and both his magic power and spiritual sense began to quickly seep out, as if they were being drawn into the chains before being sealed away.

His eyes immediately sprang open as a hint of alarm on his face, and his Earthly Deity Avatar switched to a different hand seal at his behest before pointing both of its index fingers at his dantian.

A burst of water-attribute power of laws instantly flowed into his dantian, forming a blue light barrier that closed in on the dark azure chain before completely enveloping it.

The runes on the surface of the chain were instantly isolated within the blue light barrier, and the peculiar fluctuations that it was releasing also began to wane.

Right at this moment, a burst of light flashed within Han Li's eyes, following which a series of animalistic cries rang out from within his body.

Immediately thereafter, several balls of golden light erupted out of his body, then transformed into a series of palm-sized projections that included an ape, a phoenix, a Lightning Bird, and a peacock, among others. The projections circled around Han Li momentarily, then flew into his dantian in a flash.

After flying into his dantian, the projections instantly elongated to form a series of glowing hands that grabbed tightly onto the dark azure chain.

"Get out!"

Han Li let loose a low roar through gritted teeth as he endured the excruciating pain shooting through his nascent soul, and all of the hands in his dantian glowed brightly as they tugged on the chain with all their might in unison.

A string of loud clangs rang out incessantly as the runes on the dark azure chain finally began to explode one after another in the face of the tremendous pulling force being exerted upon it, and the chain itself was slowly and agonizingly dragged out of his nascent soul.

As soon as the chain was pulled out of Han Li's nascent soul, it immediately began to writhe and struggle violently like a living creature, doing everything in its power to re-enter the nascent soul.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as dazzling light flashed from the hands locked around the chain in his dantian, and they reverted back into their true spirit projection forms before grabbing onto the chain with their claws, paws, talons, and jaws, then forcibly dragged the chain out of his lower abdomen.

After emerging from Han Li's body, the chain was revealed to be around as thick as an infant's arm, and it was only roughly 10 feet in length. Most of the dark runes on its surface had already faded, but it was still giving off faint law fluctuations incessantly.

Han Li immediately flipped a hand over to produce a white jade box that he had prepared in advance, then grabbed the chain before placing it into the box.

A crisp snap then rang out as the lid of the box was placed tightly over it.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li pulled out a silver talisman before plastering it onto the box.

A burst of gentle silver light flashed from the talisman to envelop the entire jade box, and the aura of the chain within the box was completely contained, severing its connection with the outside world in its entirety.

Only after doing all of that did Han Li heave a long sigh of relief, and he beckoned toward the true spirit projections circling around him, upon which they immediately flew into his body and disappeared.

Right at this moment, a surge of warmth appeared in Han Li's dantian. It wasn't very intense, but it carried an indescribable sense of familiarity.

He faltered slightly upon feeling this sensation, then directed his spiritual sense back into his dantian to discover that the golden nascent soul inside had finally awakened from its slumber, and it was inspecting its surroundings with wide eyes.

The golden light radiating from its body was slightly dim, indicating that it seemed to have also been severely damaged during the process that had just taken place.

Furthermore, a series of wave-like azure ripples had appeared beneath it, looking much like water splashing out of a fountain.

Han Li knew that this was the magic power that he had been deprived of for the past several centuries!

The influx of magic power seemed to be quite gentle and feeble, but it wasn't going to take long before his entire dantian was filled.

With the seal on his nascent soul removed, an enormous weight had been lifted from Han Li's shoulders. He slowly opened his eyes as he looked up at the sky, and an elated smile appeared on his face to reflect the emotions in his heart.

Several days passed by in a flash, and the large silver flags around the courtyard had already been withdrawn but Han Li still remained inside.

One day at around noon, a streak of light suddenly sped up into the sky, reaching an incredible altitude in no more than the blink of an eye. The streak of light was so fast that many people on the island caught a glimpse of it, but no one was able to see it clearly.

The streak of light flew over to an uninhabited part of the sea that was quite far away from Dark Veil Island, then faded to reveal none other than Han Li.

At this moment, his robes were flapping audibly in the wind, and he was giving off an astonishingly powerful aura, having already recovered his early-True Immortal Stage cultivation base.

He had thought that the surge of warmth flowing back into his dantian was his magic power returning to him, but only on this day, after the process had concluded, did he come to realize that his dantian was actually filled with immortal spiritual power rather than magic power.

He was ecstatic at this discovery, and he came all the way here with the intention of testing out his powers.

He let loose a joyful cry as silver light flashed all over his body, and a burst of dazzling lightning erupted forth in all directions, encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet.

Countless arcs of silver lightning were flashing incessantly through the air while springing erratically over the surface of the sea, and some were even shooting into the water from thousands of feet up in the sky.

A series of massive waves that were hundreds of feet tall were instantly swept up over the surface of the sea as if the water had been brought to a boil.

Han Li then suddenly removed the Heaven Controlling Vial from around his neck before tossing it through the air, and it began to glow with dazzling green light, then abruptly vanished into the thin air after revolving on the spot for a brief moment.

In the next instant, gusts of fierce wind suddenly began to sweep over the surface of the sea, and a series of five-colored spirit clouds appeared.

The sound of rumbling thunderclaps rang out despite the clear skies, and a massive vial opening that threatened to swallow up the heavens emerged from the spirit clouds like a wyrm rearing its head, then trembled slightly before releasing a torrent of countless dark green runes.

In the instant that the runes surged out of the opening of the vial, they immediately transformed into clouds of azure mist that exploded one after another.

A burst of extremely powerful law fluctuations instantly encompassed the entire area, following which more thunderous rumbling rang out.

The entire space shuddered slightly, and all of the air within a radius of several thousand feet tightened at once as countless arcs of silver lightning rapidly contracted, converging toward the five-colored spirit clouds.

Immediately thereafter, the waves that were rising up from the surface of the sea became even taller, forming enormous pillars of seawater that resembled soaring wyrms as they rose up into the sky in a twisting fashion.

However, regardless of whether it was the lightning or the seawater, all of it would instantly be reduced to powder upon reaching within 10,000 feet of the vial opening before being sucked away by a burst of invisible suction force.

Within mere moments, all of the silver lightning in the sky had been completely sucked in, leaving only the hundreds of enormous pillars of seawater still rising up incessantly toward the heavens.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, he raised a hand, and all of the five-colored spirit clouds in the sky began to blur before gradually fading away, leaving only a small green vial that slowly descended from the heavens.

At the same time, the seawater that had already risen into the sky instantly scattered, having lost the force that had drawn them up there in the first place, and as the vast volumes of seawater came crashing down, more enormous waves were swept up over the surface of the sea.

After withdrawing the Heaven Controlling Vial, Han Li gently stroked the patterns on its surface with his fingers, and judging from his expression, he seemed to have fallen into deep thought.

Only after a long while did a peculiar look appear on his face as he murmured to himself, "Now that I already possess immortal spiritual power, I should give that a try. Perhaps I'll be able to recover some of my lost memories."

With that, a surge of warmth instantly rose up within his dantian, and immortal spiritual power flowed through the meridians in his body before quickly gushing into the Heaven Controlling Vial through the palm of his hand.

A burst of dark green light instantly lit up from his palm, and initially, it was rather dim, but it quickly brightened.

As the light radiating from the small vial gradually brightened, it also began to tremble violently.

Moments later, the burst of light had already spread through the air like a scintillating green sun, illuminating most of the surrounding sea with bright green radiance.

As the light grew brighter and brighter, the tremors also grew more and more intense, as if the vial were trying to fly out of Han Li's grasp.

Right as Han Li was on the verge of losing his grip on the vial, a burst of green light suddenly flashed from its opening, following which it released a vast expanse of dark green runes.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he instantly directed his attention toward the runes.

As it turned out, these runes were an incantation composed from golden seal text, [1] and they were hovering within the green light as if they had been carved out of jade, giving off a peculiar aura.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he read the passage of golden seal text, following which he suddenly began to chuckle with amusement as he murmured to himself, "Looks like I already tried something similar to this before I lost my memories."

After that, he stroked a finger over the surface of the vial, and all of the dark green runes instantly flowed back into the vial as a burst of azure qi.

Han Li then tossed the vial high up into the air before chanting the incantation that he had just read.

At the same time, he pointed a finger up at the opening of the vial, continuing to inject immortal spiritual power into it.

As the mysterious incantation rang out, all of the world's origin qi in the surrounding area seemed to have been mobilized, and it began to ripple and resonate with the incantation in a strange fashion.

A peculiar azure light barrier that resembled a constantly expanding ball of azure light slowly swelled in all directions, encompassing an area with a radius of several hundred kilometers and isolating it from the outside world.

Right at this moment, a burst of blue light suddenly appeared on Han Li's body, and a humanoid figure emerged involuntarily beside him. It was none other than his Earthly Deity Avatar.

Blue light was flashing above its head, within which were a series of extremely thin blue threads that were releasing clear law fluctuations.

[1]. For more information on golden seal text, please refer to RMJI Chapter Chapter 1167: Revisiting a Familiar Place.

[Back]

Chapter 131: Crystallization of the Spirit Liquid

Han Li watched the peculiar changes taking place in the avatar across from him, and a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

Immediately thereafter, his attention turned to the small vial, which was hovering high up in the air, and he noticed that a drop of shimmering green spirit liquid was slowly flowing out from within.

As soon as the drop of spirit liquid dropped out of the vial, it was suspended in mid-air by a burst of inexplicable force, preventing it from falling any further.

Moments later, silver light suddenly flashed from the surface of the small vial, following which a pair of black lines emerged. The pair of lines then abruptly split open to reveal a pair of round eyes, which were no different in shape from the eyes of a person, but the pupils were a silver color.

As soon as the pair of eyes appeared, they immediately took a glance in Han Li's direction, following which two bursts of silver light were released from within to envelop the drop of spirit liquid.

In the next instant, a mouth suddenly appeared beneath the eyes on the vial as well, and a semi-transparent ball of fire erupted out from within to envelop the drop of spirit liquid as well.

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling akin to a thunderclap rang out, accompanied by a burst of subtle fluctuations that were barely visible to the naked eye.

Han Li quickly inspected his surroundings, following which his pupils immediately contracted slightly.

As it turned out, the sea down below had also been affected by that burst of peculiar fluctuations, and the huge waves that were swept up by the gusts of ferocious wind were all completely pulverized by that burst of fluctuations, stirring up layers upon layers of white foam.

At the same time, fierce winds were howling incessantly, and rays of light that were imbued with the world's origin qi suddenly appeared out of thin air, then began to converge toward Han Li like schools of semi-transparent fish.

In the beginning, there were several hundred of these rays of light, but their numbers rapidly increased to the thousands, then to the tens of thousands as they continued to converge from all directions.

After just mere moments, Han Li found himself unable to discern the individual rays of light anymore as there were simply far too many of them. They were stacking up on top of one another, compressing each other to form a continuous band of light as they surged rapidly toward the drop of spirit liquid suspended in mid-air.

As more and more of the light appeared and they began to travel faster and faster, an enormous vortex formed by the world's origin qi appeared. The vortex was several hundred kilometers in diameter, and it stood above the sea like an enormous spiraling pagoda that connected heaven and earth.

The sky was originally bright and clear, but a massive cloud that extended for hundreds of kilometers quickly took shape, encompassing a vast section of the sea beneath it.

Simultaneously, all of the world's origin qi within a radius of thousands of kilometers became extremely erratic, churning like boiling water as they converged toward the area that Han Li was situated in in a frenzy.

Even the islands situated tens of thousands of kilometers away were affected by these phenomena, and the cultivators on the island were greatly alarmed. Hundreds and thousands of figures flew out of their islands one after another before turning their eyes collectively in the direction that Han Li was situated, and there were several True Immortal cultivators hovering in the air in front of the azure light screen several hundred kilometers away from Han Li.

All of the True Immortals seemed to have been familiar with one another, and they were all exchanging glances with apprehension and befuddlement in their eyes.

They had thought that some type of powerful treasure had just emerged, so they had rushed here from their respective islands in anticipation and excitement, but upon their arrival, they quickly realized that they seemed to have been mistaken.

A handsome young man in a pristine white robe turned to an elderly man beside him as he said, "Fellow Daoist Qin, you've always possessed the most powerful spiritual sense out of all of us, and you were the first one to get here. Do you know exactly what's happened here?"

"This light barrier before us keeps out all spiritual sense, so I'm unable to detect what's happening inside. However, judging from the looks of it, it seems like someone is refining a powerful treasure here," the elderly man replied with a shake of his head.

"Have any of you considered the possibility that it could be someone refining an Earthly Deity Avatar?" a red-robed man with a rather effeminate appearance speculated with narrowed eyes.

"I don't think that's the case. I think Fellow Daoist Qin's theory is more likely."

"I agree."

"What's the point in making these empty speculations? Let's just go in and find out what's happening! If we join forces, surely there's nothing for us to fear," a hideous dark-skinned man suggested.

Despite the urgent tone of his voice, he hadn't moved in the slightest.

A cold smile appeared on the elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he said, "A being capable of setting up a spiritual sense obstructing restriction like this is not someone I can afford to mess with. If you want to know what's happening, you can feel free to go in, but I won't be accompanying you."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately sped away as a streak of light.

The remaining few True Immortal exchanged a few glances with one another, and all of them were looking rather awkward. They were all sly old foxes that had lived for countless years, and none of them were willing to take the risk to infiltrate the restriction first.

With the departure of the elderly man, they quickly lost interest in staying any longer, so after exchanging some small talk, they flew back to their respective islands.

Given the situation here, it was most likely the case that no powerful treasure had emerged, and if the elderly man's theory were correct and there really was an extremely powerful senior refining a treasure here, then there was a chance that they would turn on any bystanders in the area once they were done refining their treasure.

As long as they departed of their own accord before that senior completed the refinement of their treasure, there was nothing for them to fear.

Han Li was naturally completely oblivious to what these True Immortals were thinking. In fact, he was far too preoccupied with other matters to even consider such a thing.

Just now, the vast vortex of origin qi had abruptly collapsed inward to form a massive pillar of light that extended straight up into the heavens, and the clouds in the sky were also swirling incessantly around the pillar of light in a frenzy.

Right at this moment, a layer of hazy azure light suddenly appeared around Han Li, and before he had a chance to figure out what was happening, the immortal spiritual power in his body began to spill out like a turbulent wave under a burst of immense suction force, then surged directly toward the drop of spirit liquid that was enveloped in silver light.

This was naturally a very alarming turn of events, and Han Li immediately raised a hand to make a series of hand seals, causing the azure light around him to tremble slightly while the leakage of immortal spiritual power from his body was slowed.

At the same time, a layer of azure light also appeared around the Earthly Deity Avatar, and the magic power in its body that was converted from the power of faith was almost completely sapped away in the span of just a few seconds.

With a wave of his hand, Han Li stowed the avatar away, but that wasn't the end of his troubles.

Even though he was doing everything in his power to hold back his immortal spiritual power, it was still constantly flowing out of his body, except at a far slower rate than before.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce several pills, all of which he devoured at once.

As the spiritual power within the pills was converted into immortal spiritual power in his body, the sense of emptiness in Han Li's dantian finally abated slightly.

He raised his head to look up at the drop of dark green spirit liquid in the air, and a complex look appeared in his eyes.

Five whole days passed by, but the phenomenon taking place around Han Li hadn't changed in the slightest. Situated right in the eye of the storm, Han Li was struggling immensely.

If someone familiar with him were to see the state that he was currently in, they would've most likely been given a massive fright.

At this moment, Han Li had a pair of sunken eyes, skin with a waxy yellow complexion, and there was even a layer of dry dead skin on his lips. It seemed that his essence and energy were both severely depleted, and only his eyes remained as bright as ever.

The reason for this was that the immortal spiritual power in his body had been constantly seeping out over the course of the past few days, and at this point, the supply was already completely exhausted, along with a large chunk of the stash of high-grade pills that he had accumulated.

At this point, he discovered that taking further pills only had an infinitesimal effect on his immortal spiritual power recovery, and he wasn't going to be able to last much longer at this rate.

However, for some reason, there was a voice in his heart telling him that as long as he persevered, he was going to reap a tremendous reward in the end.

Han Li took a deep breath as he stowed away the several pills that he had summoned back into his storage treasure. He then gritted his teeth and made a strange hand seal, and his dried and cracked lips parted slightly as he began to chant an incantation.

As he did this, the complexion of his skin suddenly began to improve, and his sunken eyes also returned to normal.

He resembled an old tree that was on the brink of death abruptly being rejuvenated by a bout of heavy rainfall.

Unfortunately, this was a secret technique that allowed one to regain their vitality and increase the amount of immortal spiritual power in their body, but at the cost of burning through blood essence, and the price that he was incurring for using this secret technique was far beyond what the average person could imagine.

……

Another three days and three nights passed by in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, the azure ball of light that encompassed a vast area around Han Li began to rapidly shrink without any warning. After no more than 20 seconds, it had already shrunk down to a radius of only around 10 feet, and that drop of spirit liquid, which had already turned virtually completely translucent, was enveloped within it.

Within this small area, a vast volume of extremely dense world's origin qi was still surging toward the drop of spirit liquid at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and the azure light barrier shrank once again. As it did so, even more world's origin qi was compressed to the extreme and forced into the drop of spirit liquid.

The drop of spirit liquid that was hovering in mid-air instantly solidified, transforming into a semi-transparent crystal that fell out of the air.

At the same time, a dry and withered hand suddenly shot out to catch the crystal.

The owner of the hand was naturally none other than Han Li, and following the ordeal that he had just endured, he had become unrecognizably emaciated, looking like nothing more than a sack of skin and bones. His robes were draping down all around his body, making him resemble a clothes rack that the azure robe was hanging from.

Even though he was in terrible shape, there was a smile on his face, and there was a look of utter exhaustion in his eyes, but they were still shining as bright as ever.

He raised his head to look up at the small vial, which was still hovering in mid-air, only to find that its original dark green color had faded, and the mouth and that pair of eyes had also vanished. Furthermore, it was looking rather blurry and indistinct, almost impossible to see clearly.

He was rather surprised to see this, but he wasn't concerned as a vague sense of familiarity had surfaced in his mind, and he was confident that the vial would return to normal after absorbing moonlight for a few days.

Chapter 132: Heavy Water

After stowing the small vial away, Han Li began to carefully inspect the crystal in his hand.

The crystal also struck him with a sense of familiarity, but he couldn't recall how to use it.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he closed his eyes, following which a translucent thread shot out of his glabella before wrapping itself around the crystal.

Moments later, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and a bemused look appeared on his face.

"How did this happen?" Han Li murmured to himself.

Through his spiritual sense, he discovered that this crystal was a spirit material that contained a type of law powers, which was identical to the type of law powers imbued within the eyeball of that one-eyed giant.

However, the law powers imbued within this crystal weren't even a tenth as potent as what was in that eyeball.

Given the small vial’s various abilities and the series of phenomena that had taken place earlier, Han Li was able to conclude with relative confidence that this wasn't some type of earth-attribute law powers.

However, as for exactly what it was, he didn't have much of an idea, and he decided that he was going to see if he could find some information from the array plate of the Transient Guild once he returned to Dark Veil Island.

As he was contemplating this matter, he took the time to swallow a few pills, and the pills quickly melted into bursts of pure energy that flowed to all parts of his body, giving his complexion a visible improvement.

He took a glance at his surroundings, then rose up into the air as a streak of light before flying toward Dark Veil Island.

He returned quietly to the island without alerting anyone, then went straight into the secret chamber in the courtyard he was staying in.

Shortly thereafter, the world's origin qi within a radius of hundreds of kilometers began to converge toward the small courtyard, forming a massive vortex of spiritual qi.

At this point, all of the residents of the island, regardless of whether they were cultivators or mortals, were already accustomed to the phenomena brought about by Han Li.

The phenomenon of converging spiritual qi lasted all the way until nighttime before slowly dissipating.

However, not long after that, bursts of starpower from the Big Dipper shone down from the night sky, forming seven huge pillars of starpower that descended into the courtyard.

This cycle of gathering spiritual qi during the day and harnessing starpower at night went on for an entire month.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li was slowly revolving within a cocoon of bright azure light.

All of a sudden, the azure light faded in a flash to reveal Han Li inside, and at this point, he had already made a full physical recovery.

He quickly inspected his internal condition with his spiritual sense, upon which a relieved look appeared on his face.

Thankfully, having cultivated the Big Dipper Origin Arts, he had built up a tremendous physical foundation, so he was able to make a full recovery despite the grueling ordeal he had endured.

As for the Heaven Controlling Vial, just as he had anticipated, it had also returned to its original appearance after absorbing starpower during this period.

Han Li exhaled as he pulled out that crystal formed by the drop of spirit liquid once again, and he plucked the crystal between his fingers as he raised it to his eye, while a contemplative look appeared on his face.

He then flipped his hand over to produce the eyeball of the one-eyed giant, then closed his eyes and injected his spiritual sense into it.

Sure enough, the law powers contained within the crystal were identical to the type imbued within the eyeball, but up to this point, Han Li still hadn't managed to figure out exactly what this type of law powers was.

As he opened his eyes, he came to a decision.

He had almost been sucked completely dry for the sake of this crystal, so he had to figure out what it was no matter what.

With that in mind, he pulled out the azure mask from the Transient Guild before putting it on, then pointed a finger at his own glabella while chanting an incantation.

Rippling azure light that resembled water rose up from the mask, forming a huge array plate projection in front of him.

He navigated directly to the missions area, where he released a mission of his own. He provided a description of the one-eyed giant and promised a handsome reward to anyone that could identify the creature.

After that, Han Li stowed the crystal and the mask away before making his way out of the small courtyard and flying away into the distance.

In a certain region of the sea near Dark Veil Island, turbulent waves were rumbling incessantly, and there was a massive vortex that was over 100 kilometers in size, churning everything that fell into it straight to the seabed.

Han Li appeared in a flash, then flew into the center of the vortex without any hesitation, quickly reaching the seabed.

A blue figure was seated with their legs crossed on a large rock on the seabed, and it was none other than Han Li's Earthly Deity Avatar.

The avatar had its arms encircled in front of its chest, and black rippling light was shimmering all around it as it cultivated the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome.

Bursts of power of faith were being transmitted to the Earthly Deity Avatar from afar, and a law thread had emerged above the avatar's head, giving off bursts of water law fluctuations.

Han Li gave a slight nod at the sight of the law thread.

This method of cultivation used by Earthly Immortals to manifest law powers using the power of faith was quite unique, and just the power of faith supplied by the people of Dark Veil Island alone was enough to allow the Earthly Deity Avatar to manifest a law thread so soon.

At the same time, the avatar had also accumulated a sizeable amount of magic power in its body, but it was rather scattered and chaotic, perhaps due to the fact that the magic power was mixed with the power of faith.

The cultivation method employed by Han Li was different from that of other Earthly Immortals, and the difference was that he didn't allow any of the power of faith harnessed by his Earthly Deity Avatar to flow into his body.

As a result, he was unable to enjoy the benefit of manifest law powers using the power of faith, but on the flip side, his immortal spiritual power wouldn't be contaminated by the power of faith.

After all, he had only refined this Earthly Deity Avatar in order to break the seal on his nascent soul.

All of a sudden, he turned his gaze toward the hands of his Earthly Deity Avatar, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

There was a ball of black water the size of an infant's fist hovering above the avatar's hands, and it was shimmering with black light, giving it a rather peculiar appearance.

Sure enough, the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome really was living up to its reputation of being extremely slow to progress in.

Not long after he returned to Dark Veil Island, he had left his avatar here to cultivate the first level of heavy water, and it had only managed to manifest such a tiny amount in over a month.

It was no wonder that the creator of the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome had taken over 500,000 years just to manifest enough heavy water to fill a small creek.

Han Li beckoned to the ball of heavy water, and it flew over to him before landing on his palm.

It was only a tiny ball of heavy water, but it was no lighter than a small mountain.

After inspecting the ball of heavy water for a moment, he stored it into a jade vial, then flew away without lingering any longer. Right as he emerged from the sea and was about to return to his courtyard, an astonishing phenomenon suddenly began to unfold above Dark Veil Island.

All of the world's origin qi in a radius of thousands of kilometers had converged to form an enormous spiritual qi vortex, and spiritual qi was trailing down from the vortex like rays of light, forming a giant waterfall of light that surged into a palace on Dark Veil Island.

That palace was none other than Luo Feng's residence.

At this moment, the palace was surrounded by a vast sea of five-colored light, and all types of light of different colors were surging incessantly amid bursts of loud rumbling.

Han Li took a glance in the direction of the palace from afar, then abruptly vanished on the spot.

The massive commotion was clearly visible and audible across the entire island, but no panic had ensued. Instead, all of the members of the Luo Clan, particularly the Spatial Tempering and Body Integration cultivators, all appeared extremely excited.

This phenomenon was a clear indication of a Body Integration cultivator making a breakthrough to the Grand Ascension Stage!

Inside the palace, Luo Feng was seated with his legs crossed, and the light radiating from his body was flashing wildly. His aura was fluctuating drastically, and his expression was also constantly changing, as if he were undergoing some type of trial.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared beside him without any warning.

Luo Feng's aura was fluctuating more and more violently, and droplets of sweat were beginning to bead up on his forehead and his cheeks. At the same time, he seemed to be losing control over his own emotions.

The five-colored sea of light around the palace was also trembling in an unstable manner, and rays of light would occasionally shoot out in random directions, smashing huge craters into the ground around the palace, much to the alarm and panic of the surrounding bystanders, who quickly fled into the distance.

Han Li flicked a finger through the air upon seeing this, and a burst of gentle translucent light shot out before entering Luo Feng's glabella.

Luo Feng's expression instantly eased slightly, and the wild flashing of the light around him subsided, while the five-colored sea of light outside the palace was also stabilized.

As more and more spiritual qi surged down from the heavens, the five-colored sea of light around the palace also gradually transformed into a massive cocoon of light.

Time slowly passed by, and after an indeterminate period of time, the cocoon of light suddenly shuddered, following which a peculiar fragrant aroma wafted out from within.

A faint crack rang out as a small rift appeared on the cocoon of light, and a burst of golden light escaped from within, then transformed into a series of golden flowers, while a burst of heavenly music rang out.

All of the members of the Luo Clan gathered near the palace were ecstatic to see this, and a collective thunderous cheer rang out.

Inside the palace, light was revolving around Luo Feng's body, and his skin had turned as fair as jade. Furthermore, he had also taken on a slightly more youthful appearance.

He slowly opened his eyes, and an excited look appeared on his face.

This Grand Ascension Stage breakthrough was not one that he had much confidence in, and he was almost unable to transcend the tribulation of inner demons. However, a burst of external power had suddenly entered his body, fortifying his mind and ensuring a safe breakthrough.

Luo Feng was just about to rise to his feet when he spotted Han Li standing beside him.

He faltered momentarily at the sight of Han Li, then immediately realized what had to have happened, and he extended a deep bow toward Han Li. "Thank you for your assistance, Senior Liu."

"It's nothing, don't mention it. I didn't expect you to reach the Grand Ascension Stage so soon. This is truly worthy of celebration!" Han Li replied with a slight nod.

"It's all thanks to those cultivation resources that you bestowed upon me that I was able to take this step," Luo Feng replied in a respectful voice, and his heart was full of gratitude.

"As long as you serve me to the best of your abilities, there will be more where those resources came from," Han Li replied with a wave of his hand.

As a Body Integration cultivator, Luo Feng's usefulness had been limited, but now that he had reached the Grand Ascension Stage, he could be entrusted with more important tasks.

Chapter 133: The Three Paramount Laws

"Rest assured, Senior. Our Luo Clan owes everything to you, and we'll be sure to serve you with absolute diligence and loyalty," Luo Feng declared with a solemn expression.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he was just about to say something else when his expression suddenly changed slightly.

"You're far too kind, Chief Luo. Your breakthrough to the Grand Ascension Stage is something for the entire island to celebrate, so you should go and meet your clansmen," Han Li said, then immediately vanished from the spot.

Luo Feng was already accustomed to Han Li's elusive and enigmatic ways, so he extended a bow at the spot where Han Li had just disappeared, then took a moment to adjust his robes before making his way outside.

At the same time, Han Li appeared back in his courtyard, then immediately made his way into the secret chamber.

As he did so, he pulled out and put on his azure mask, upon which a speck of white light was flashing incessantly.

Han Li pointed a finger forward, and a streak of white light flew out of the mask before transforming into a buzzing white vortex in front of him.

A projection of another masked figure appeared, and all that could made out of their facial features was a pair of blue eyes.

Han Li wasted no time, cutting straight to the chase as he asked, "You accepted my missions, so I presume you must know what that one-eyed giant is, right, Fellow Daoist?"

"I just so happen to have some knowledge in various types of exotic beasts, and if I'm not mistaken, the one-eyed giant you're asking about should be a rare type of earth-attribute spirit beast. However, the description provided in the mission isn't very detailed, so I can't be absolutely certain. If you could provide me with some more details, I'll be able to make a more informed judgment," the figure replied.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he provided some more details to the masked figure. "It does indeed sound like you're quite the expert. The appearance of the beast..."

The fact that the masked figure was able to determine that it was an earth-attribute spirit beast just from Han Li's rough description alone indicated that they were very knowledgeable, and perhaps they really did know what this beast was.

"It seems my guess was correct. The one-eyed giant that you're referring to is a beast by the name of the Primordial Fei Beast," the figure confirmed after hearing Han Li's more detailed description.

"Can you enlighten me on this creature?" Han Li asked.

"This is a type of extremely rare spirit beast, and I've never seen it myself. All I've heard about it is that it's born from chaos and possesses innate earth law powers, allowing it to manipulate the earth as it pleases. Upon reaching adulthood, these beasts will attain powers equivalent to those of a True Immortal," the masked figure explained.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, then asked, "I see. Is there anything special about such a beast?"

"The only special thing I can think of about this beast is that its lone eye will occasionally mutate, giving rise to a wisp of time law powers, which is extremely sought-after among all immortals.

“However, these mutated Primordial Fei Beasts are exceedingly rare, with only roughly one in 10,000 such beasts undergoing this mutation. On top of that, wherever a mutated Primordial Fei Beast appears, a period of extreme unrest is sure to follow in that area," the masked figure replied.

"The laws of time..." Han Li murmured to himself, and even though his expression remained calm, his calm facade belied his actual emotions.

He had previously suspected that the abilities unleashed by the Primordial Fei Beast had something to do with the laws of time, so there was an extremely high possibility that the one-eyed giant had been a mutated Primordial Fei Beast.

"That's right. As bearers of one of the three paramount laws, it's not wonder that mutated Primordial Fei Beasts always stir up so much trouble wherever they appear," the masked figure said.

"What are the three paramount laws?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

A strange look appeared in the masked figure's eyes upon hearing this question, and they seemed to have been rather taken aback. "You don't even know about the three paramount laws?"

"Forgive me for my embarrassing lack of knowledge, and please enlighten me," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"This is a piece of general knowledge, so there's hardly any enlightening to be done. The three paramount laws refer to the laws of time, space, and reincarnation. It's said that those three laws are the root of all laws, and the other 3,000 Great Dao laws were all born from those three paramount laws.

“The paramount laws are also the rarest and most mysterious laws in the Immortal Realm, and even among the Holy Ancestors, not many have been able to master such laws. As for immortals below the Holy Ancestors, even coming into contact with the three paramount laws is nothing more than a pipe dream," the masked figure said with a hint of longing in their voice.

"The 3,000 Great Dao laws..." Han Li repeated to himself with a thoughtful expression.

"It's said that each type of law represents a Great Dao, and each Great Dao can ultimately lead one to the pinnacle of the True Immortal Realm. There are 3,000 types of known laws in the Immortal Realm, so that's why it's said that there are 3,000 Great Dao laws," the masked figure explained, still with a hint of longing in their voice voice.

"I see," Han Li murmured in a contemplative voice.

"Materials that contain the three paramount laws are priceless treasures in the Immortal Realm, and it's impossible to obtain them through conventional means. I've heard that people have even begun offering large rewards on information pertaining to the whereabouts of Primordial Fei Beasts.

“If you have some information, I suggest you sell it in the guild. I'm sure many people would be willing to pay a handsome price for such information," the masked figure said in a meaningful voice.

"I don't have any information on the whereabouts of any Primordial Fei Beasts. I just so happened to see some records describing such a beast recently, and I was curious about what they were," Han Li replied in a nonchalant manner.

"I must admit, I was also very intrigued when I first saw a description of this beast," the masked figure chuckled.

"Thank you for answering my questions. I have no further questions, and I'll issue your reward to you in a moment," Han Li said.

The projection of the masked figure nodded in response, then promptly vanished from the spot.

With a wave of his hand, Han Li summoned the promised reward, then placed it onto the array plate's transmission site, and it vanished amid a flash of light.

After that, Han Li removed the azure mask, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

He wasn't smiling about the eye of the Primordial Fei Beast. Instead, he was thinking about that crystal that the Heaven Controlling Vial had created after devouring so much of the immortal spiritual power in his body.

Even though he hadn't made any further attempts, he presumed that just like with the manifestation of the spirit liquid, the vial was capable of creating this crystal more than just once.

If that were the case, then theoretically, he would be able to secure an infinite supply of this material that contained one of the rarest powers of laws in existence.

Now that he thought about it, this vial was able to speed up the maturation of spirit medicines, so it wasn't much of a surprise that the crystals formed by the spirit liquid contained the laws of wood or the laws of time.

A solemn look then appeared on his face, and he decided that he had to keep this matter a secret, given how precious materials that contained the laws of time were.

If for some reason, he was forced to exchange the crystal for other items, he had to ensure that his identity remained confidential to the other party.

After all, given his current paltry cultivation base, revealing such a precious treasure in his possession would've been no different from courting death.

With that in mind, another thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and a grim look appeared on his face.

Could it be that this crystal had something to do with the centuries of memories that he had lost?

He immediately rose to his feet as this thought sprang into his mind, and as he paced back and forth in his secret chamber, this notion was becoming more and more likely in his mind. He pulled out the crystal once again, then sat back down with his legs crossed and began to carefully inspect it with his spiritual sense.

However, even after an extensive and thorough inspection, he still wasn't able to find anything useful.

Han Li pointed a finger at his own glabella, and his Law Destruction Eye appeared amid a flash of black light, following which a beam of black shot out from within.

At the same time, two bursts of blue light shot out of his eyes, and the three bursts of light fused as one.

At the same time, Han Li chanted an incantation while making a hand seal, and an enormous burst of spiritual sense surged out of his glabella amid a flash of translucent light, then also fused together with the three bursts of light.

As a result, the three bursts of light gradually transformed into a huge black and blue eye that began to scrutinize the crystal.

This was a secret technique that combined his Law Destruction Eye and Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

A burst of black and blue light shot out of the eye to envelop the crystal, immediately following which a hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face.

At the center of the crystal was a faint golden thread that was barely visible, and it would've been impossible for him to find it if not for the use of this secret technique.

Half a month later, a certain area of the sea near Dark Veil Island was churning incessantly, while an enormous vortex was slowly revolving.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on a reef island, contemplating something meticulously with the crystal pressed against his forehead.

According to the scriptures that he had recently consulted, it was virtually impossible to try and master the power of laws purely through inspecting a material that contained that power of laws. However, if he were to use a cultivation art related to the laws of time, then this was definitely going to be a beneficial experience.

It was a bit like discussing cultivation insights and experiences with other cultivators. As for exactly how this was beneficial and how much one could benefit from such discussions, that was up to them.

Time was one of the three paramount laws, so he naturally didn't want to pass up any opportunity to try and examine it.

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li opened his eyes before removing the crystal from his forehead, then shook his head with a slightly disappointed expression.

Even after so many days and experimenting with all types of methods to try and detect the laws of time within the crystal, his efforts had proven to be completely futile, but that really wasn't much of a surprise.

He continued to fiddle absentmindedly with the crystal in his hand, but his gaze was piercing through the sea as he observed his Earthly Deity Avatar on the seabed in a contemplative silence.

The crystal in his hand didn't seem to have been changing at all, but in reality, the laws of time within it were getting weaker by the day, and the golden thread was gradually becoming shorter and shorter.

At this rate, it was only going to take about half a month before the laws of time in the crystal completely faded, and that was a rather disappointing prospect to Han Li.

As a result of this, it seemed that his idea to sell the crystal to others in exchange for resources simply wasn't feasible.

He withdrew his gaze as he turned his attention to the crystal in his hand once again.

"Nevertheless, I have to give it an actual try. After all, I can wield some power of water laws now," Han Li murmured to himself as he raised a hand before making a beckoning motion.

The massive vortex in the sea up ahead churned violently for a moment before gradually subsiding, immediately following which a blue shadow emerged from within in a flash. The blue shadow quickly descended beside Han Li, following which the blue light radiating from its body faded to reveal the Earthly Deity Avatar.

Han Li tossed the crystal at his Earthly Deity Avatar, and the latter caught it as black light flashed from its body, following which the thread of laws on top of its head slowly burrowed its way into the crystal.

In order to examine the power of laws within the crystal, it only made sense that the power of laws had to be used. However, the laws of time within the crystal was one of the three paramount laws, so there was an element of risk to what Han LI was doing.

However, he naturally wouldn't be willing to give up on this idea without attempting it, and he could only hope that this wouldn't have much of an impact on his Earthly Deity Avatar.

As these thoughts were going through his mind, the thread of water laws had already entered the crystal in a flash.

All of a sudden, the crystal began to glow with scintillating golden light.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, but before he had a chance to do anything, an unexpected turn of events suddenly unfolded.

Chapter 134: Extraordinary Spirit Artifact

A resounding boom rang out as the crystal abruptly exploded, and the nearby space was instantly filled with countless fine ripples. Faint shadows, both bright and dark, then quickly proliferated throughout the surrounding area.

The explosion had taken place without any warning, and Han Li was too close to crystal, so he didn't have sufficient time to take evasive measures. All he could do was manifest a layer of True Extreme Membrane over his body before he was struck by a burst of tremendous force.

He was immediately sent flying back like a cannon, and the energy in his body surged violently as he threw up a mouthful of blood.

After steadying himself several thousand feet away, he turned to find that the reef island beneath his Earthly Deity Avatar was already nowhere to be seen, and the surrounding seawater had also been dispersed by a burst of tremendous force. As a result, a completely empty region with a radius of several thousand feet was formed, and it took a long time for that area of the sea to return to normal.

Even though his avatar was able to form a protective light barrier using its laws of water, its right arm and close to half of its body was still destroyed in the explosion, giving it a rather pitiful appearance, but thankfully, its foundation remained unharmed.-

All of a sudden, something caught Han Li's attention, and he turned his gaze to the law thread hovering above his avatar's head.

It was originally a light blue water-attribute law thread, but not only had it become a little thicker than before, there was some faint golden light flashing inside, giving off a similar aura to the laws of time.

Han Li suppressed his bewilderment as he summoned his avatar to him, and at the same time, he opened his mouth to release a burst of nascent flames, which quickly enveloped the avatar. At the same time, he brought out an array of spirit materials with a sweep of his sleeve, and they gradually began to melt and change shape in the nascent flames.

A day and a night later.

On the seabed, Han Li was inspecting his Earthly Deity Avatar, which had already returned to normal, and the avatar immediately sat down with its legs crossed at his behest.

It then encircled its arms in front of its own chest, and the law thread above its head began to quiver slightly white radiating blue light that was far brighter than before.

The entire surface of the sea began to surge and churn, and enormous waves were raised, while a vortex that was even more massive than the previous one began to take shape. The giant waves that were swept up surged all the way to Dark Veil Island thousands of kilometers away, and the entire island began to tremble as if an earthquake were taking place.

All of the islands inhabitants were quite alarmed by this, and many cultivators at or above the Spatial Tempering Stage hurriedly flew into the sky to see what was causing this phenomenon.

However, moments later, all of the cultivators returned the same way they had come in silence, as if they had all simultaneously received some type of instruction. At the same time, the island became encompassed under a series of light barriers, and the disturbance gradually subsided soon thereafter.

Meanwhile, Han Li was standing on the seabed with an astonished look on his face.

In front of him, his Earthly Deity Avatar's eyes were tightly shut, and at the center of its encircled arms, a tiny ball of heavy water was rapidly revolving on the spot while expanding at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Soon, it had become the size of a bean, then swelled to the size of a finger...

After no more than two hours, an egg-sized ball of heavy water had appeared before Han Li, and it was still steadily expanding along with the surging water currents in the surrounding sea.

Han Li took a deep breath, and the astonishment on his face turned to elation.

However, as he shifted his gaze slightly upward, a peculiar look appeared in his eyes.

Just like the golden thread in the crystal, the hint of golden light within the law thread hovering above his avatar's head was slowly fading.

Could it be...

A thought sprang into his mind upon seeing this.

Time quickly flew by, and half a month went by in a flash.

On the seabed, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and at this point, the golden light within the law thread above his Earthly Deity Avatar's head had already become extremely dim.

Even so, the rate at which his Earthly Deity Avatar was deriving heavy water didn't slow down in the slightest.

All of a sudden, the law thread shuddered, and the golden light within completely faded.

In the same instant, the churning seawater in the surrounding area also became far more tranquil, while the huge vortex on the surface of the sea rapidly shrank down to only several hundred kilometers in size.

Simultaneously, the speed at which the avatar was deriving heavy water was also reverted back to the initial rate.

Han Li was inspecting the large ball of heavy water in front of his avatar with a contemplative look on his face.

Somehow, the power of time laws imbued within the crystal had managed to fuse with his avatar's law thread, and it rapidly enhanced the rate at which his avatar was able to derive heavy water. However, the fusion wasn't very stable, and the power of time laws continued to constantly seep away during this process. Once it completely disappeared, the rate of heavy water derivation naturally returned to normal.

In any case, Han Li had finally managed to find a use for these crystals. Given the original rate a at which his avatar was deriving heavy water, Han Li estimated that it would've taken around 1,500 years to derive this much.

Hence, the crystal was an extraordinary artifact, and it was no wonder that it had almost sucked him dry.

With that in mind, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce his True Water Pouch, which he stored the heavy water into.

After stowing the True Water Pouch away, he didn't linger on the seabed any longer. Instead, he flew out of the water as a streak of azure light, then made his way back to Dark Veil Island, while his Earthly Deity Avatar was left behind to continue deriving heavy water.

Half a month later.

A series of rather complex and profound spirit patterns had been engraved onto a plot of empty land on a lone island that was quite far away from Dark Veil Island. Around the plot of land stood nine silver stone pillars, which were also riddled with spirit patterns, as well as many star-like specks of silver light.

It was a profound array, and Han Li was seated at its center with his legs crossed and his eyes closed.

Beside him were around a dozen jade vials, wooden boxes, and other containers for pills. Even though the containers were all tightly sealed, there were still faint medicinal aromas escaping from within.

Moments later, he gently exhaled as he opened his eyes, then flipped a hand over to summon his Heaven Controlling Vial.

Azure light began to glow from his body, and his immortal spiritual power surged into the vial along his arm.

The dark green floral patterns on the surface of the vial lit up one after another, quickly becoming so bright that it appeared that Han Li was holding a ball of dazzling green light in his hand.

Shortly thereafter, the small vial flew out of his grasp before hovering in mid-air.

As Han Li flicked his fingers through the air, streaks of azure light were released before vanishing into the vial in a flash, and the surrounding world's origin qi began to ripple, while a drop of green liquid began to slowly flow out of the vial.

Shortly thereafter, the silver eyes and silver mouth surfaced once again one the vial, releasing silver flames that enveloped and scorched the drop of green liquid. The world's origin qi that was converging from the surrounding area also formed a massive pillar of light around the vial.

All of a sudden, Han Li shuddered as the immortal spiritual power in his body began to surge out in an uncontrollable fashion before being absorbed by the drop of spirit liquid.

However, instead of being alarmed, he was ecstatic, and he heaved an internal sigh of relief before pointing a finger forward.

A streak of azure light shot out before landing on the array around him.

The array immediately began to operate, and the spirit patterns on the ground lit up one after another, radiating dazzling white light and forming a white ball that was over 100 feet in size. The white ball encompassed his entire body before beginning to revolve on the spot.

The world's origin qi that was converging from all directions also flowed into the white ball, and they immediately began to surge through the white ball in a haphazard fashion as streaks of spiritual light.

The concentration of spiritual qi inside the ball was rapidly rising, quickly reaching several times the concentration outside the ball, and this spiritual qi was constantly replenishing the immortal spiritual power that was rapidly surging out of Han Li's body.

At the same time, he picked up an azure jade vial from behind him, then tipped out a green pill that was around the size of a longan.

The pill was called the Azure Flower Pill, and it was currently the best energy recovery pill that he could procure.

Even though there was still plenty of immortal spiritual power left in his body, he still devoured the pill without any hesitation before focusing on refining it.

At the same time, he cast several incantations seals in succession, all of which fell upon the surrounding nine stone pillars. Vast expanses of silver light instantly began to radiate from the stone pillars, and countless star runes emerged, drawing starpower down from the night sky, forming seven pillars of starlight that injected their power into Han Li's body...

Five days later, Han Li's expression had turned rather grim.

Even though he had prepared the best pills and a spirit gathering array, his efforts were proving to be rather ineffective.

His immortal spiritual power had run out once again, and he could only use that same secret technique from before to convert his blood essence into immortal spiritual power for the vial to absorb.

Several more days passed, and he was once again reduced to a sack of skin and bones, and overall, he only appeared to be in slightly better condition than last time.

Thankfully, the drop of spirit liquid had solidified into another semi-transparent crystal.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he inspected the crystal, but there was a hint of elation in his eyes.

Several days later.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on a giant rock in the sea near Dark Veil Island. His body was protected by several spirit treasures, and the crystal was hovering in a still manner in front of him.

His Earthly Deity Avatar was also seated with its legs cross across from him, and it was protected by several spirit treasures as well.

After taking a moment to brace himself, Han Li made a beckoning motion with his hand, and the law thread hovering above his avatar's head drifted over to him before slowly entering the crystal.

This time, he wanted to experience the laws of time for himself.

This was one of the three paramount laws, and seeing as his avatar was able to use it to speed up its derivation of heavy water, perhaps it would also trigger some type of unexpected change in him.

However, to his surprise, after the law thread entered the crystal, no explosion took place.

Why isn't it working?

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

This crystal was no different from the last one, and it also contained the power of time laws. However, for some reason, he was unable to control the water law thread to fuse with the laws of time inside the crystal.

Han Li was unwilling to give up, and he tried the same thing four or five more times, all with the same outcome.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and after some contemplation, he sent the water law thread back to the top of his avatar's head with a wave of his hand. He then tossed the crystal at the avatar as well.

The Earthly Deity Avatar caught the crystal, then injected its water law thread into it, and sure enough, the crystal exploded, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping in all directions.

However, this time, Han Li had ensured that both he and his avatar were sufficiently protected, so both of them remained unharmed, and the water law thread was once again tinged with a hint of gold.

"Looks like this thing can only be used by my avatar, but is beyond my reach," Han Li murmured to himself as a wry smile appeared on his face.

Chapter 135: Bonded Eight Spirits Vat

Even though Han Li was feeling a little disappointed, he quickly told himself to be content with what he already had.

It was already incredibly fortunate that these crystals were able to significantly enhance the rate at which he could derive heavy water. If he expected anything more than that, then he would simply be asking for too much.

Of course, if he could somehow glean the secrets of the laws of time someday, there was a chance that he would be able to use these crystals for himself, and just the mere thought of this sent a flash of excitement surging through his heart.

However, at this point, that was only a distant dream.

For the vast majority of itinerant cultivators, just mastering one of the 3,000 Great Dao laws to become a True Immortal was already a very difficult task, let alone master one of the three paramount laws.

Furthermore, even though he had already recovered his cultivation base, the true crisis still hadn't been completely averted yet.

Hence, his top priority at the moment was to attain more power as quickly as possible, as well as to recover his lost memories and treasures, lest he suffer the same inexplicable fate that had caused him to end up in the Spirit Domain Realm.

Even though the Black Wind Sea was quite secluded and safe, it was not a place that he could remain at for long. If his enemies were to somehow find him, then he would be in a world of trouble. Perhaps someone had already detected his approximate location prior to the seal on his nascent soul being undone.

As for how to recover his lost memories, at the moment, there were only two leads available to him.

The first one was naturally to return to the Ascension Platform where he had first completed his ascension. He would then try to track down Gao Sheng, who had served as his guide at the time, and ask him what had happened after they left the platform.

However, the Northern Glacial Immortal Region was extremely vast, so he had no idea how he was supposed to track down Gao Sheng, and even if he could find him, there was no guarantee that Gao Sheng's words would be credible.

Furthermore, Gao Sheng was a late-True Immortal cultivator, so it was definitely not a good idea for Han Li to approach him on a whim without being able to ensure his own safety.

The second lead was the wanted notice that had been passed down from the Immortal Realm, and mysterious length of dark azure chain that he had sealed into a white jade box.

For some reason, he couldn't shake the feeling that the two things were somehow connected, and he was convinced that if he could find the person who had released the wanted notice or the owner of the chain, then he would be able to find an important lead relating to his lost memories.

Of course, regardless of which one of those leads he chose to pursue, he required more power to ensure his safety.

Looks like the best way to enhance my powers in a short time would be to recover my lost treasures, as well as Jin Tong and Daoist Xie. [1]

Aside from that, there was another way to get stronger, which was to get his avatar to derive large volumes of heavy water as quickly as possible.

According to the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome, even if it were only heavy water of the first level, as long as one possessed sufficient quantity, it would still suffice as a trump card to be used in battle.

However, even with an endless supply of crystals that contained the power of time laws, it was still going to take quite some time to accumulate a substantial amount of heavy water.

One morning, roughly a month later.

Han Li was standing in the open-air area of his courtyard, a rusty and antiquated-looking octagonal copper vat had appeared before him.

A different exotic beast was engraved onto each of the vat's eight faces, including a Qilin, a Taotie, and a Kui, all of which were extremely menacing to behold. [2]

A series of strange ring-shaped patterns had been engraved onto the vat around the beasts, and there were also an ancient rune inscribed in gold-plated text beneath each beast, with each rune around the size of a human head.

On the bluestone slab beneath the copper vat was a sector-shaped array that had been engraved using a sharp object, and looking down at it from above, it resembled a flower in full bloom.

The vat was filled with clear water, which was as still as a mirror without even the slightest ripple running over the surface.

At this moment, Han Li was standing beside the vat with one hand resting on its edge, gently rubbing along the vat's surface.

This vat was called the Bonded Eight Spirits Vat, and it was a treasure that he had obtained from the Transient Guild's trade array plate at quite a heavy price.

This wasn't a treasure that could help him in battle of inr his cultivation. Instead, it was something that was specifically used to find certain people or objects.

In contrast with other similar treasures, this vat could only be used to search for people or objects that had a bloodline or spiritual connection with the user.

Han Li had exchanged for the vat despite the heavy asking price as he wanted to use it to find his bonded flying swords, the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch, and other important things.

He raised his head to look at the sunlight that was filtering over the wall of his courtyard, and with a flick of his wrist, several longan-sized top-grade spirit stones appeared on his palm, all of which were giving off watery blue radiance or an earthy yellow glow.

He walked a lap around the vat, embedding the water and earth-attribute spirit stones in his hands into the mouths of the eight beasts engraved onto the vat's surface.

After that, he returned to his original spot before beginning to chant an incantation, and a hint of excitement gradually began to appear in his eyes.

As the first ray of morning sunlight shone over the wall and down onto the vat, the surface of the water in the vat was immediately tinged with a faint golden glow.

Han Li placed both hands onto the edge of the vat upon seeing this, then switched to another incantation, one that was very profound and difficult to understand.

As he did this, the sector-shaped array beneath the vat began to glow with azure light, and eight ancient runes on the vat also began to shine brightly.

At the same time, the still surface of the water in the vat began to ripple, and the mouths of the beasts engraved onto the vat also lit up in unison.

Blue and yellow light began to shine into the vat from its walls, illuminating the water inside the vat to form a blue and yellow yin yang diagram.

A serious look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he raised a hand before extending it over the surface of the water.

A faint burst of light flashed over his index finger, and drop of golden blood essence slowly appeared before dripping down.

A dull thud immediately rang out, seemingly from directly within Han Li's consciousness.

He stared intently into the water, and he saw that after the drop of blood essence fell into the water, not only did it not display any signs of dissolving, it began to rapidly revolve like a spinning top instead.

As a result, all of the water in the entire vat was quickly stirred up, and the originally clearly divided yellow and blue light were also mixed together somehow, forming a series of strange lines that resembled mountains and rivers.

Han Li began to chant another incantation upon seeing this, and the drop of blood essence instantly stopped spinning, as if it had just received an instruction.

It then warped and changed shape to form a miniature golden sword, which was completely identical in shape to Han Li's bonded flying swords, his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

"Go!" Han Li instructed, and the tiny golden sword immediately began to vibrate at a high speed on the surface of the water, then abruptly changed turned to the east before quickly hurtling away in that direction.

The sword was moving very quickly, and the area within the vat was quite limited, so it should've struck the wall of the vat in an instant, but as it turned out, the tip of the sword continued to maintain a distance of around a foot away from the wall of the vat, keeping them separated.

However, upon closer inspection, one would discover that the mountain and river patters on the surface of the water in the vat was rapidly receding, making it appear as if the sword were traveling over a vast distance.

Only after around 15 minutes had passed did the mountain and river patterns on the surface of the water gradually draw to a halt, and the golden sword was suspended over a set of blurry and indistinct patterns.

Han Li couldn't clearly see the terrain being displayed by the patterns. All he could tell was that the swords were definitely outside of the Black Wind Sea, and they were extremely far away in the east.

After looking at the surface of the water for a moment longer, he pointed a finger at the miniature golden sword, trying to get a clearer sense of the current situation that his bonded flying swords were in.

However, in the instant that his finger came into contact with the golden sword, his consciousness suddenly rippled slightly, and a faint hint of familiarity rose up in his soul.

Could it be...

Han Li immediately closed his eyes and focused on examining this sensation, and moments later, his eyes abruptly sprang back open, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he exclaimed, "There's no mistaking it! That's Daoist Xie's aura!"

However, a perplexed look then quickly appeared on his face. Did this mean that Daoist Xie and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were together, or did they just so happen to be situated not far away from one another?

With that in mind, another thought occurred to him, and he murmured to himself, "I wonder if Jin Tong is with them as well."

To follow up on that thought, he began to chant another incantation, then gently swept the palm of his hand over the surface of the water.

The tiny golden sword in the water instantly reverted back to a drop of blood essence, and after completing his incantation, Han Li instructed once again, "Go!"

The drop of blood essence shuddered slightly, then began to dart around haphazardly through the water like a headless fly.

Moments later, it abruptly sank straight down to the bottom of the vat, where it vanished without a trace.

With the disappearance of that drop of blood essence, the spirit stones embedded into the vat were also completely spent, and the glow that they were radiating gradually faded. As a result, the water inside the vat also reverted back to its original state.

Han Li couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh upon seeing this.

He didn't know whether it was because the subject was too far away, or if there were some other reason at play, but the drop of blood essence was unable to determine the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch's location. In fact, it wasn't even able to determine the direction that it was in.

If it weren't for the fact that Han Li could still feel an extremely faint spiritual connection to the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch, he would've perhaps been inclined to believe that it had already perished.

Thankfully, he had received some leads on the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and Daoist Xie. Even though it was only a rough direction, it was still certainly better than nothing.

He was confident that if he were to set off in search of them according to the direction provided by the vat, he would be able to track them down with his spiritual connection to them once he was close enough.

With that in mind, Han Li was struck by the impulsive urge to set off right away, but he knew that even if he were to set off on such a journey, he had to take care of some matters on Dark Veil Island first.

[1]. As a quick reminder, Jin Tong is the name of the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch.

[Back]

[2]. All three of these are beasts from Chinese mythology.

[Back]

Chapter 136: Arrangements

Close to a month later.

In a secluded area of the Black Wind Sea, there were over 100 small gray islands littered across the region.

These islands were all of different sizes, but they were all smaller than 10,000 kilometers in area, and they resembled a string of pearls embdeed onto a wall of jade.

Vegetations on the islands were very sparse, as was the spiritual qi. Not only was there not a single animal to be seen on the island, there weren't even any seabirds in the area, presenting a rather bleak and desolate sight to behold.

In reality, these islands had all been encompassed under a near-transparent light barrier, and if one were outside the light barrier, they would only be able to see a vast stretch of empty ocean. In fact, even if the average True Immortal cultivator were to scour the area with their spiritual sense, they wouldn't be able to discover anything amiss.

At this moment, two figures, one male and one female, were seated on either side of a round stone table in a secret chamber constructed in the belly of a mountain on a certain island.

One of them was a man with an imposing physique and a hollow helmet on his face, and it was none other than Ancestral God Han Qiu of the Cold Crystal Race, and the woman with him was Mistress Gu Gu, with whom he had targeted Han Li on multiple occasions.

"Are you sure he won't be able to find us here, Fellow Daoist Han Qiu?" Mistress Gu Gu asked as she gripped tightly onto the teacup in his hand, within which the tea had gone cold long ago.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Gu Gu. I had to spend almost all of my belongings to exchange for this illusory array from Master Illusory Light, even a Late-True Immortal cultivator wouldn't be able to find us here. That man is only a Profound Immortal, so there's no chance he'll discover us.

“Even if he does stumble into this area, he won't be able to see the true landscape as long as he doesn't break the core of the array," Han Qiu replied, but despite what he was saying, there was a rather uncertain look in his eyes.

"I should've never allowed myself to get involved in this mess! Not only has my avatar been destroyed, I can't even return to my home! If I hadn't taken part in this, I would still be doing whatever I please on my Worry Bone Island!" Mistress Gu Gu sighed.

"What's the point of saying that now? As Earthly Immortals, we're envied by countless people, but even in the Black Wind Sea, we are only bottom-dwellers. Risk and reward come hand in hand, and unless we're blessed with immense fortune, our situation most likely won't change even over the course of the next 100,000 years. How is an existence like this different from being dead? I made an error in judgment this time, but as long as we can weather the storm here and refine new avatars, we can definitely rise again someday!" Han Qiu said.

"You make it sound so easy to refine new avatars. If you ask me, we should find a way to leave the Black Wind Sea," Mistress Gu Gu said as she released her teacup.

"That's preposterous! Setting aside the fact that we don't have a way out, even if we somehow manage to leave the Black Wind Sea, we'll lose the protection of our law powers, and we wouldn't even be able to match the average itinerant cultivator in battle! How would that be a better option to staying here?" Han Qiu harrumphed coldly.

A dejected look appeared on Mistress Gu Gu's face upon hearing this, and she didn't say anything further.

Right at this moment, Han Qiu abruptly sprang up from his chair as if he had been pricked in the bottom, and he yelled, "Impossible!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of earth-shattering rumbling rang out, and all of the islands in the entire area shuddered in unison, along with the transparent light barrier above them.

Enormous plumes of dust rose up into the sky as a series of bottomless rifts appeared on all of the islands. Countless rock fragments erupted forth in all directions before falling onto the surface of the sea like rain, churning up its surface into a frenzy.

Massive waves swept through the area, and one island after another began to crumble away before sinking to the bottom of the sea.

Two figures emerged from the smoke and debris, and they didn't linger for even a single moment as they flew westward as quickly as they could.

However, they were only able to flee for a few hundred kilometers before a streak of light arrived directly in front of them.

Grim looks appeared on Han Qiu and Gu Gu's faces as they looked at the figure they were being confronted by.

Han Qiu swallowed his pride and extended a slight bow as he asked, "Senior Liu, is there really no way that you would spare us?"

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response.

Han Qiu also fell silent for a moment, then continued in a careful voice, "If you spare our lives, we're willing to offer up everything in our respective races in gratitude."

Meanwhile, his hands were concealed up his sleeves, and he was tightly gripping an azure jade tablet in one hand, while making a hand seal with the other.

Mistress Gu Gu hadn't said anything, but she had also subtly withdrawn her hands up her sleeves.

Right at this moment, a layer of azure light appeared over Han Li's body, and he took a step toward the two Ancestral Gods.

Both of the Ancestral Gods immediately sprang into action upon seeing this, and a burst of radiant azure light appeared from one of each of their sleeves before connecting together to envelop the two.

In the blink of an eye, the two of them vanished from the spot.

Mere moments later, a flash of light appeared in the sky tens of thousands of kilometers away, and the two of them reappeared.

"Thank heavens we prepared this pair of Divine Travel Pendants in advance. Even as Profound Immortal, I'm sure he won't be able to catch up to us anytime soon," Han Qiu said as he inspected his surroundings with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"These Divine Travel Pendants are indeed quite extraordinary. The only drawbacks are that they take too long to activate and require both of us to activate them at once. We almost didn't make it out in time back there. This place isn't safe, either, so we should continue on our way," Mistress Gu Gu said in a concerned manner.

Han Qiu was just about to respond when a voice suddenly rang out from the faraway distance.

"You two got away a bit faster than your avatars did."

Han Qiu and Gu Gu were horrified by the sound of the voice, and they immediately tried to activate their Divine Travel Pendants once again, only for Han Li to descend right before them in a flash.

"How is he this fast?" Mistress Gu Gu wailed in a despairing voice.

Han Qiu's eyes were also filled with shock and horror.

With a flick of his wrist, Han Li summoned a black longsword into his grasp, and it was none other than the one that Mistress Gu Gu's had used.

He pointed the tip of the sword upward, and a massive sword projection that resembled an enormous mountain appeared, piercing a hole straight through the clouds up above.

Han Qiu and Mistress Gu Gu were in complete despair, but they still mustered up their final shreds of courage to summon their most powerful treasures.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a translucent wheel of ice appeared in front of Han Qiu. The wheel was riddled with countless ice spikes that were giving off white glacial qi.

Meanwhile, Gu Gu swept her hands through the air, and a gray puppet appeared out of thin air, then vanished into her body amid a flash of light.

Han Li could see what they were doing, but he paid it no heed as he abruptly turned his wrist downward.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the mountainous sword projection was instantly tipped upside-down before crashing down upon the two Ancestral Gods.

Han Qiu immediately opened his mouth upon seeing this, expelling a mouthful of blood essence from under his visor, and the blood essence vanished into the white wheel of ice in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, it was as if the ice wheel had sprung to life, and it began to rapidly revolve on the spot before transforming into a huge ice phoenix that flew directly toward the oncoming sword projection.

Meanwhile, a cloud of dense mist began to surge out of Mistress Gu Gu's body, sending a powerful corrosive aura surging through the air.

In the next instant, the black sword protection swelled even further in size, completely obscuring the heavens.

The gray mist was instantly dispelled, while the ice phoenix was decapitated, and the bodies of the two Ancestral Gods were completely destroyed by the sword projection.

……

Meanwhile, Han Li's Earthly Deity Avatar had arrived on the island of the Cold Crystal Race along with Luo Feng.

First, they slew several elders and the chief of the opposing race, then smashed all of the statues of Han Qiu on the island. Only after that did they declare that Han Qiu was already dead, and that Cold Crystal Island now belonged to Dark Veil Island.

The Cold Crystal beings naturally refused to believe this initially, but Han Qiu remained absent, and they had also lost the protective light membranes granted to them by their Ancestral God, so they had no choice but to surrender.

After that, the two of them traveled to Worry Bone Island and repeated the same process.

During the following month, Dark Veil Island's new Ancestral God, Liu Shi, quickly became a name that everyone in the nearby region was aware of. The Ancestral Gods that had targeted him in the past were so horrified that they all fled their islands, not daring to return.

As for the nearby Ancestral Gods who were yet to make contact with Han Li, all of them hurriedly traveled to Dark Veil Island to try and appease him.

There were even two itinerant cultivators that joined Dark Veil Island to become guest elders, and they were sent to preside over Cold Crystal Island and Worry Bone Island in his stead.

All of a sudden, Dark Veil Island had become a dominant force in the region.

However, all Han Li did was slay Han Qiu and Gu Gu, and he left everything else to Luo Feng and his avatar.

Several months later, in the secret chamber of Han Li's courtyard.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on a cushion , while Luo Feng was standing before him with a serious look on his face.

"I have to go into seclusion soon, and I'll most likely be in seclusion for a very long time. My avatar is also busy cultivating, so you'll be solely responsible for overseeing matters on the island," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, Senior Liu, I'll be sure to look after the island diligently in your stead," Luo Feng hurriedly replied.

"I'm going to be setting up an array around this courtyard soon, and no one is permitted to approach this place. If you encounter something that you can't take care of, don't come to me, just seek out my avatar," Han Li instructed.

"Yes, Senior Liu," Luo Feng immediately replied.

Following Luo Feng's departure, a streak of blue light abruptly flew out of Han Li's body, then transformed into a humanoid figure, revealing itself to be none other than his Earthly Deity Avatar.

Han Li rose to his feet, then flipped a hand over to produce a pair of identical black array plates, one of which he handed to his Earthly Deity Avatar.

The array plates were similar in size and shape to go boards, and their surfaces were riddled with countless small white dots, while a nine palace grid and the 16 directions were engraved onto the edge of the plate, presenting a rather intriguing sight to behold.

The plates were called Twin Starshift Plates, and they were capable of teleporting treasures from one plate to another. This was another treasure that he had exchanged from the Transient Guild at a very steep cost.

One night, around half a month later, a figure with an extremely well-disguised aura left Dark Veil Island in a stealthy fashion.

Only upon arriving in an area of open sea several dozen kilometers away from the island did the figure abruptly transform into a streak of azure light, hurtling rapidly toward the center of the Black Wind Sea.

Chapter 137: Black Wind City

As the center of the entire Black Wind Sea, Black Wind Island boasted an extremely vast territory, and it was more appropriate to call it a continent than an island.

Aside from the main Black Wind Island, there were also dozens of islands littered throughout the nearby area.

Black Wind Island had an abundance of spirit veins and world's origin qi, and its massive territory was laden with resources, far more so than other islands. Furthermore, it had the only teleportation array that led to the outside world.

Every day, there were countless immortals, mortals, and resources converging to Black Wind Island from all parts of the Black Wind Sea. Similarly, there were also countless rare materials that were exchanged here before spreading to all parts of the Black Wind Sea, making this an extremely thriving central hub.

There were even some who proclaimed that half of the Black Wind Sea's most precious resources were concentrated on Black Wind Island.

On the southern coast of Black Wind Island was an enormous city that resembled a gargantuan beast laying sprawled out on the ground. The city walls alone were thousands of feet tall, resembling vast mountains.

The city was filled with an array of imposing and majestic buildings, as well as wide and pristine streets that were teeming with pedestrians.

There were also buildings hovering in the air above, and streaks of light were traversing back and forth through the air.

This city was Black Wind City, the largest city on Black Wind Island, and it was also home to the teleportation array that led to the outside world.

Even before first light, the entire city had already been teeming with activity for quite some time.

As a coastal city, Black Wind City had an abundance of all types of piers and docks. Countless boats and ships of different sizes were constantly traveling over the sea to reach Black Wind City, and the vast majority of them belonged to mortals.

There was a particularly large pier on an area of the coast close to 10 kilometers away from Black Wind City. The pier was thousands of feet long and around 200 to 300 feet wide. It was entirely constructed from white jade, and there were countless faintly glowing runes engraved onto its surface.

The white jade pier stood far taller than the surface of the sea down below, resembling the resting arm of a giant.

At this moment, the pier was packed with people, all of whom were staring expectantly into the distance, as if they were waiting for something.

There was a completely unremarkable-looking young man standing in the crowd. He appeared to be around 17 to 18 years of age and had a slightly dark complexion.

Mu Xue gently exhaled, and he was immediately greeted by the unique fishy and salty aroma of the sea breeze, which caused his brows to furrow slightly.

Having come from an inland region, even though he had already been on Black Wind Sea for two years, he still wasn't used to the smell of the sea.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out nearby. "You've come pretty early today as well, Brother Mu."

Mu Xue turned to discover a man with an imposing figure making his way toward him. The man had a thick and coarse beard, and his facial features were rather menacing to behold.

Surely you jest, Brother Zhao. When have I ever arrived earlier than you?" Mu Xue chuckled.

The man's name was Zhao Hu, and despite his intimidating appearance, he actually had quite an easy-going personality. Just like Mu Xue, both of them were foreign itinerant cultivators who had come to Black Wind City to make a living, and the two of them had established a close friendship.

The two began to make small talk with one another, and Zhao Hu lowered his voice as he asked, "How have things gone for you this month, Brother Mu?"

As it turned out, luck hadn't been on Mu Xue's side recently, and his brows furrowed slightly as he shook his head in response. "Things haven't been great recently. I haven't received many jobs at all in the past few days. What about you, Brother Zhao?"

"I received a job from an important client yesterday and managed to make some money," Zhao Hu replied with a pleased expression, but he wasn't gloating to Mu Xue.

"I'm going to make an extra effort and strive to earn enough spirit stones to buy a vial of Nascent Formation Elixir by the end of the year," Zhao Hu continued with a hint of excitement in his eyes.

"I must offer you my congratulations in advance then, Brother. Given your spiritual roots and cultivation aptitude, you'll definitely be able to manifest a nascent soul with the assistance of some Nascent Formation Elixir. Once that happens, you'll be able to venture out into the sea with hunting parties to hunt for sea beasts, and you'll be able to earn spirit stones far more quickly than you are now!" Mu Xue said with a hint of envy on his face.

He had only just reached the Core Formation Stage, so he was still far away from the Nascent Soul Stage.

Zhao Hu's smile grew even more pronounced upon hearing this, and he patted Mu Xue on the shoulder as he said, "You're still a young man, Brother Mu. The only advantage that I have over you is my age. By the time you get to my age, you'll have left me far behind."

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling rang out from the distant horizon.

Mu Xue and Zhao Hu immediately ceased their conversation as they turned their attention to the horizon.

Several clouds were drifting apart in the sky amid the rumbling, and an enormous white shadow appeared in the distance.

It was traveling extremely quickly, arriving near the pier in just a few seconds to reveal itself to be a gargantuan white louchuan.

The vessel was over 10,000 feet in length and close to 1,000 feet tall, hovering in mid-air like a majestic white mountain.

The louchuan had somewhere between 20 to 30 levels, and every single level was divided up into countless square grids, which were the windows of the rooms on the ship.

The louchuan rapidly decelerated as it arrived at the pier, quickly drawing to a halt in mid-air.

All of a sudden, the spirit patterns on the pier began to radiate spiritual light of various colors, which converged to form a thick pillar of light that erupted straight into the heavens, coming into direct contact with the giant vessel.

In response, countless spirit patterns appeared on the underside of the vessel as well, forming a series of arrays, and the pillar of light instantly injected itself into the spirit patterns.

The pillar of light resembled a giant chain that connected the pier and the louchuan together.

Under the guidance of the pillar of light, the giant white vessel slowly descended, coming to a rest in front of the pier.

The louchuan was called the Skydrift Cloud Ark, and it was vastly renowned throughout the Black Wind Sea.

Even though the Black Wind Sea was only considered to be an insignificant rural area in the context of the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, its area was incredibly vast in the eyes of all of the cultivators here.

Even for a True Immortal, it would've taken them countless years to fly across the entire Black Wind Sea.

The islands in the Black Wind Sea were very dispersed, and all types of demon beasts were residing in the sea, making it a very perilous region. Hence, it was extremely inconvenient for cultivators to travel to different islands unless they were at the True Immortal Stage.

The number one trading house on Black Wind Island had identified this as a business opportunity, expending a huge amount of resources to construct this Skydrift Cloud Ark, which was capable of transporting tens of thousands of people to all parts of the Black Wind Sea.

Thanks to the special refinement methods used, the Skydrift Cloud Ark was extremely fast, far more so than the average True Immortal cultivator.

Even though traveling on the ship was quite expensive, it was still a very popular form of transport among the cultivators of the Black Wind Sea for its speed and safety.

All of a sudden, a vast expanse of white light began to radiate from the Skydrift Cloud Ark, and the white radiance formed a long passageway that was projected to the pier.

A series of cultivators then flew out from the passageway before arriving on the pier.

Mu Xue and Zhao Hu immediately approached those cultivators with smiles on their faces.

"May I ask if you're traveling to Black Wind City, esteemed senior? I reside permanently in the city, so I know it like the back of my hand. If you want to go somewhere or do something in the city, I'll definitely be able to help you," Mu Xue said to a black-robed man in a welcoming voice.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hu had approached someone else and was doing the same thing, as was everyone on the pier around them.

The black-robed man paid no heed to Mu Xue and flew directly toward Black Wind City himself.

However, Mu Xue wasn't disheartened in the slightest, and he immediately turned to the next person with a welcoming smile. However, that person also ignored him and flew away on their own.

Before long, over half of the louchuan's passengers had already disembarked, but up to this point, no one was willing to hire Mu Xue.

"Yes! Rest assured, Senior, you can count on me!"

Meanwhile, Zhao Hu had already received a client.

It was a Body Integration cultivator, who swept a hand through the air to release a burst of blue light that enveloped Zhao Hu's body, following which both of them flew toward Black Wind City.

A hint of frustration flashed through Mu Xue's eyes upon seeing this. Perhaps it was because he was still too young and perceived to be lacking in maturity, but business had always been quite lackluster for him.

Right at this moment, an azure-robed man drifted down from the louchuan, but instead of immediately setting off for Black Wind City, he began to inspect his surroundings as if he were appreciating the scenery.

"Is this your first time coming to Black Wind Island, Senior? If you're going to Black Wind City, then you'll most likely require a guide. Black Wind City is extremely massive, and not only is the layout of its streets very complex, there are restrictions in the city that limit the use of one's spiritual sense.

“If you don't have a capable guide, it'll be quite troublesome to find things. I grew up my entire life in Black Wind City, so I'll definitely be able to help you get to where you want to go," Mu Xue greeted.

"So you're a guide?" the azure-robed man asked.

"That's right. I've already been working as a guide here for about four or five years, and I only charge five mid-grade spirit stones for my services."

Mu Xue could tell that Han Li was interested, and he was ecstatic. In order to ensure that this client didn't slip through his hands, he charged a slightly lower price than normal.

"This is indeed my first time visiting Black Wind City, so I will be needing a guide," the azure-robed man replied with a nod, then swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light, which carried both of them toward Black Wind City.

"What's your name?" the azure-robed man asked as he took a glance at Mu Xue.

"My name is Mu Xue," Mu Xue hurriedly replied.

"Mu Xue? That sounds like a girl's name," the azure-robed man remarked with a faint smile.

"My name was given to me by my mother," Mu Xue replied as he scratched his head in a slightly embarrassed manner.

"You just told me that you grew up your entire life in Black Wind City. Those who live by the sea are constantly exposed to the sea breeze, which will result in a dark complexion, but also some red coloration of the skin, and you don't seem to fit that bill. I'm assuming you actually grew up in a mountainous area, right?" the azure-robed man asked with a hint of a smile on his face.

Mu Xue's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and he lowered his head as he replied, "Your wisdom is truly unmatched, Senior. I did indeed grow up in a mountain village, and I offer you my sincerest apologies for lying to you. As an outsider, I have no choice but to tell some lies in order to make a living in Black Wind City."

"It's fine, that doesn't matter to me. All that matters is that you serve as a good guide," the azure-robed man replied with a dismissive wave of his hand, and a reminiscent look had appeared in his eyes.

The azure-robed man was none other than Han Li, and it had taken him around two months aboard the Skydrift Cloud Ark to arrive at Black Wind City.

As he took in the city before him, a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

The city was so massive that even with his exceptional eyesight, he was unable to see its boundaries. The entire city was encompassed under an enormous array, which was giving off immense spiritual power fluctuations.

The two of them quickly arrived near Black Wind City, where they were greeted by dozens of different gates on the city wall.

"These gates are meant to split up the different types of visitors to the city. Local residents or cultivators generally don't need to pay an entrance fee, whereas mortals or merchant parties have to pay in silver. You're a cultivator who's visiting the city for the first, so you'll need to go through that gate," Mu Xue introduced as he pointed to a certain gate on the left.

Chapter 138: Immortal Origin Stones and Earthly Pill Masters

Han Li merely nodded in response and flew directly toward the gate that Mu Xue was gesturing toward.

A long line had already taken shape in front of the gate designated for foreign cultivators, and there were several black-robed cultivators stationed at the gate, accepting entrance fees from all those entering the city.

These people appeared to be no different from human cultivator, but in reality, they were all Dao Warriors.

There were several lines of large text engraved onto one side of the city gate, displaying the different fees that had to be submitted by visitors of different cultivation bases. However, the highest tier was only for Spatial Tempering cultivators, and no fees were specified for those at or above the Body Integration Stage.

"Why does it only go up to Spatial Tempering cultivators? Does this mean those at or above the Body Integration Stage don't need to pay an entrance fee?" Han Li asked.

"That is indeed the case, Senior. Cultivators at or above the Body Integration Stage are considered to be esteemed guest that don't need to pay," Mu Xue replied with a smile.

"I see," Han Li replied with a smile.

Before long, the two of them had already arrived at the city gate, and Han Li made his way into the city with his hands clasped behind his back without summoning any spirit stones.

Spiritual light flashed from the hands of the two Dao Warriors stationed at the gate, and the light flashed over Han Li's body before he was granted passage.

A hint of surprise appeared on Mu Xue's face upon seeing this. He handed one of the Dao Warriors a pair of low-grade spirit stones before hurriedly following along behind Han Li, and the awe and veneration in his eyes had only become more pronounced.

Beyond the city gate was a road that was around 70 to 80 feet wide, and it was paved with azure jade in a clean and orderly fashion.

The street was extremely lively and bustling, and cultivators were an extremely common sight, many of whom were quite advanced in their cultivation bases.

The street was lined with rows of well-organized shops that were all very clean and orderly, most of which old cultivation materials of a very high quality.

There were no strict flight restrictions in the city, so as long as one didn't fly too high, they would be allowed to do as they pleased.

Hence, Han Li rose up into the air to inspect his surroundings.

He wasn't able to see much from outside, but now that he had entered the city, he was greeted by the sight of one bustling street after another, stretching as far as his eyes could see. These streets were all teeming with pedestrians, as well as countless shops of all descriptions.

He couldn't help but be stunned by the sight of such a thriving city.

"Esteemed senior, have you come to Black Wind City to buy something, or is there something else on your agenda?" Mu Xue asked in a careful voice as he arrived beside Han Li.

"I heard that the teleportation array leading out of the Black Wind Sea is in this city, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"It is. The teleportation array is in the Heavenly Star Pagoda at the center of the city. Could it be that you wish to leave the Black Wind Sea, Senior?" Mu Xue asked.

Han Li merely nodded in response.

"I don't mean to be rude, Senior, but every year, there are many people who come to Black Wind City with the intention of leaving the Black Wind Sea, but almost all of them end up failing. It's a very difficult task to be granted access to that teleportation array," Mu Xue said with a wry smile.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he asked, "Oh? And why is that?"

"The teleportation array connected to the outside world is an ancient teleportation array controlled by the island master, and it's only activated once every century. There's only a set number of people teleported each time, and the island master decides who gets to fill those spots. Not only will you have to claim one of those spots, using the array incurs an extremely steep cost that even many immortals can afford," Mu Xue explained.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "Do you know when the array is set to be activated next?"

"It shouldn't be too far away. The array is always activated after the grand auction, which also takes place once every century. The grand auction is happening soon, and that's why the city is more lively than usual," Mu Xue replied.

Han Li was rather relieved to hear this, and he asked, "So how do I secure one of those spots from the island master?"

Mu Xue's expression stiffened slightly, and he scratched his head sheepishly as he replied, "Well... This is a rather confidential matter, and my cultivation base is too low, so I'm afraid I don't know..."

Han Li didn't blame Mu Xue for his lack of knowledge on this subject, and he asked, "You also just mentioned that the cost to use the array is very expensive. How many spirit stones will it require?"

"The island master asks for immortal origin stones rather than spirit stones, and five are required per person," Mu Xue replied.

"Immortal origin stones? What're those?" Han Li asked.

"From what I've heard, immortal origin stones are a type of special currency used by immortals, and their creation requires an immortal to inject their energy into a certain type of special crystal," Mu Xue replied.

This was the first time that Han Li had ever heard of immortal origin stones, and after a moment of contemplation, he asked, "How much are these stones worth? If they're a type of currency, then surely they can be exchanged for with spirit stones, right?"

"Immortal origin stones aren't just an ordinary type of currency. Apparently, they're extremely precious even to immortals, and generally speaking, no one would put them up for trade. I've already been in Black Wind City for many years, and I've only ever heard of one occasion several decades ago when a trading house managed to exchange for an immortal origin stone from an immortal.

“At the time, the trading house had to sell several of its shops on the island to gather enough spirit stones for the transaction," Mu Xue replied.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, and he was rather intrigued by the concept of these stones.

He didn't ask any further questions, nor had he expected leaving the Black Wind Sea to be a simple matter.

In any case, he was very curious about Black Wind City, so there was no hurry for him to pursue this matter.

With that in mind, he made his way deeper into the city, while Mu Xue trailed along behind him, providing him with tidbits of information on the city.

The two of them explored the city for close to half a day, and it was a very eye-opening experience for Han Li.

What was particularly of interest to him was the central area of the city, which boasted countless pill shops, material shops, and treasure shops of all descriptions, presenting an almost dizzying sight to behold.

However, according to Mu Xue, they had only explored less than 10% of the city, and upon hearing that, Han Li was thoroughly convinced that this was indeed the largest city in the entire Black Wind Sea.

All of a sudden, he drew to a halt and turned his gaze to a large shop on the side of the street.

This was a five-story shop with a wide entrance, and the decor was lavish, but not excessively so. Instead, it gave off quite a grand and majestic aura, and it was a huge pill shop.

"This Thousand Medicine House is arguably the best pill shop in all of Black Wind City, and it's said that the shop even has some ties with the island master. They sell all types of precious pills at fair prices, and they've always maintained a spotless reputation," Mu Xue introduced.

Han Li nodded in response, then made his way into the shop.

He didn't have many energy recovery pills left, and he was in even shorter supply of other restorative pills. He was going to have to leave the Black Wind Sea and travel eastward in search of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, among other things, so he had to prepare a good stash of pills in case of emergencies.

Mu Xue followed him into the shop.

The shop was filled with wide counters, of which there were dozens in total. The counters were laden with all types of pills, as well as a whole host of pill refinement ingredients.

At this moment, there were quite a few customers browsing through the wares sold in the shop.

Han Li and Mu Xue were immediately welcomed by a yellow-robed attendant upon entering the shop. "Welcome to our Thousand Medicine House. May I ask what type of pills you need?"

Han Li took a glance at the counters around him, following which his brows furrowed slightly.

The pills on these counters were all quite good, but they weren't of a sufficient standard to be of use to him.

"Are these all the pills that you have here? Do you have any better pills?" Han Li asked.

The attendant took a closer look at Han Li upon seeing this, seemingly trying to gauge Han Li's status, then replied, "Our shop is the best pill shop in all of Black Wind City, so we naturally have better pills than this, but the price will also..."

All of a sudden, a yellow-robed elderly man hurriedly approached them, and he yelled, "Shut your mouth, you insolent cur! I'll attend to this senior!"

It was clear from his attire that he was also working at the shop, seemingly in a managerial position.

The attendant immediately realized that he had made a mistake, and he extended an apologetic bow toward Han Li before backing away with his head lowered.

"He has no clue what he's talking about, please don't take offense, Senior," the yellow-robed elderly man said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

Han Li was completely unbothered, and he replied, "It's alright. Where are your best pills? Take me to them."

"Please come with me," the yellow-robed elderly man said as he made an inviting hand gesture, also treating Mu Xue with a great deal of respect by extension.

Mu Xue hurriedly returned the salute.

"I am the manager here at the Thousand Medicine House, and my name is Lu Ping. May I ask your name, Senior?" the yellow-robed elderly man asked.

"Liu Shi."

"Welcome, Senior Liu. The pills sold on the first few floors of our Thousand Medicine House are all ordinary pills refined by Temporal Pill Masters, so it's no surprise that they haven't managed to catch your eye. If you visit our shop again, please head straight to the top floor. All of the pills there are refined by Master Hao, and I'm sure they'll be of use to you, Senior Liu," Manager Lu explained in a warm and hospitable voice.

In order to keep a low profile, Han Li had restricted his own cultivation base to the Grand Ascension Stage. Lu Ping was an early-Body Integration cultivator, so he was already able to get a rough sense of Han Li's aura.

"Master Hao is one of the Black Wind Sea's top three pill refinement masters, and it's said that his skills are already on par with those of a B-grade Earthly Pill Master," Mu Xue explained to Han Li in a quiet voice.

As he was speaking, the three of them had already arrived on the fifth floor.

There were only counters here, only intricately crafted wooden shelves. There were only three such shelves with several attendants standing next to each shelf, but there wasn't a single customer on the level aside from Han Li.

"Our Thousand Medicine House has very close ties with Master Hao, and most of the pills refined by him are sold in our shop. This shelf contains pills to enhance one's cultivation base, all of these restorative pills, and over here are the pills that have regenerative, antidotal, and other effects," Manager Lu introduced.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of these pills.

As expected of the best pill shop in Black Wind City, all of the pills here appeared to be of quite a high quality, not inferior in the slightest to the ones that he had exchanged from the Transient Guild. In fact, there were even a few that were clearly of a higher quality.

Judging from the prior conversation, it seemed that only those capable of refining pills useful to immortals or those close to ascending to become immortals could be referred to as Earthly Pill Masters. In contrast, those who refined pills for ordinary cultivators were Temporal Pill Masters. At the very least, that was the assumption that Han Li was making.

As for whether this was actually the case, he would have to find a chance to clarify the matter.

Chapter 139: Pill Masters of the Immortal Realm

Han Li didn't pay any attention to the pills used for cultivation base enhancement or restoration. Instead, he made his way straight to the shelf that carried energy recovery pills.

Beneath each pill on the shelf was a detailed description of the pill's effects, as well as its price.

His gaze slowly roamed over the shelf, and he quickly spotted a type of pill called the Origin Return Pill.

This pill had an immense energy recovery effect. Every time he manifested a crystal that contained the laws of time, he would be left in desperately short supply of energy, so this pill was perfect for shortening his recovery time.

"I'll take five vials of Origin Return Pills," Han Li declared.

Each vial only contained three pills, but it cost 30 top-grade spirit stones. Thankfully, Han Li had obtained quite a few top-grade spirit stones from the Earthly Immortals and itinerant cultivators that he had previously slain, so the price wasn't too steep for him to afford.

"Yes, Senior!" An elated look appeared on Lu Ping's face as he pulled out a badge.

A burst of white light shot out of the badge before landing on the protective barrier around the shelf, and an opening appeared, following which one of the attendants immediately crouched down and pulled out five green jade vials.

After some more searching, Han Li picked out some Origin Watch Pills, which allowed the consumer to accelerate their absorption of the world's origin qi for a short time, as well as some Bone Alteration Pill, which was a pill that could provide a disguise that could fool even the spiritual sense of late-True Immortal cultivator.

These two types of pills weren't cheap, either, and he had spent the majority of his top-grade spirit stones here.

However, he was willing to make this investment if it meant that he could better deal with the potentially perilous journey ahead.

Manager Lu was naturally very pleased, seeing as this was quite a big sale for him.

Right as he was about to introduce some other pills to Han Li, the sound of footsteps rang out, and two more figures arrived on the fifth floor.

One of them was a young woman who appeared to be around 18 to 19 years of age. Her robes were as pristine as snow, and she resembled a pure celestial maiden who had descended from the palace on the moon.

Beside the young woman was a blue-robed young man who appeared to be in his twenties. He was also quite handsome in appearance, but the arrogant look on his face made for a negative first impression.

The blue-robed young man took a glance at Han Li out of the corner of his eye, then interjected in a rude manner, "Lu Ping, are the spirit ingredients I asked you to prepare last time ready?"

"Please pardon me for not coming out to greet you sooner, Master Fang. The spirit ingredients that you asked for have been prepared well in advance, I'll go fetch them now."

Manager Lu hurriedly made his way toward the duo, shooting Han Li an apologetic glance as he was speaking.

Han Li took a glance at the blue-robed young man, and his gaze settled onto a small crimson cauldron design emblazoned onto his collar.

"That's a symbol that can only be worn by pill masters. That man is an A-grade Temporal Pill Master," Mu Xue introduced in a quiet voice.

Han Li nodded in a contemplative manner upon hearing this, then withdrew his gaze as he continued to browse through the other pills on the shelves on his own.

Meanwhile, Lu Ping called over a couple of attendants to accompany the Master Fang and the young woman, while he quickly made his way downstairs.

The white-robed young woman had a concerned look on her face as she made her way over to the wooden shelf that carried all types of restorative and antidotal pills.

"Given Brother Mo's powers, I'd say he's most likely just fallen into some type of special space or restriction that severed his connection with his Origin Soul Lamp. There are examples of this happening in the past, so don't be too concerned," the blue-robed young man consoled in a gentle voice as he trailed along behind the young woman.

"I'm also confident in his abilities, but I have to find him no matter what," the young woman replied with a nod, and her voice was as crisp and pleasant as the call of an oriole.

Han Li paid no heed to the two of them as he quickly scanned through all of the pills on the fifth floor, but didn't find anything else that caught his fancy.

"Let's go," he said to Mu Xue, then turned to make his way back downstairs.

After leaving the Thousand Medicine House, Han Li took a glance at the throngs of people on the streets, then turned to Mu Xue as he asked, "Are there any cave abodes on Black Wind Island available for temporary accommodation?"

"Around 250 kilometers away from the city is a mountain by the name of Mount Youyang, and it was developed by the island master to serve as temporary accommodation for cultivators. I've taken a few people there in the past, so I'm very familiar with its whereabouts, and I can take you there as well if you need, Senior," Mu Xue replied.

"No need. Just tell me the rough location, and I'll go there on my own," Han Li said.

Mu Xue was slightly dejected to hear this, but he immediately did as he was told. "Just take the main road at the center of the city out of the northern gate and keep traveling northward to get to Mount Younyang."

With a flick of his wrist, Han Li casually tossed out a longan-sized azure rock, which fell toward Mu Xue.

Mu Xue hurriedly caught the object to find that it was a high-grade spirit stone, and an elated look immediately appeared on his face, but he then offered the spirit stone back to Han Li with both hands in a slightly fearful manner as he said, "This is too much, Senior. Five mid-grade spirit stones will suffice."

"Just take it. I'm not giving this spirit stone to you for free. There's something that I need you to find out for me," Han Li said with a smile.

Mu Xue faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't immediately withdraw the spirit stone as he asked, "What is it, Senior?"

Han Li was quite pleased with Mu Xue's reaction, and he replied, "I want you to help me find out how I can claim one of the spots to leave the Black Wind Sea. If you can find out information that's useful to me, I'll be sure to reward you."

"Rest assured, Senior, you can count on me!" Mu Xue assured with a nod as an elated look appeared on his face.

With that, the two of them parted ways, departing in different directions.

Han Li slowly made his way along the main road at the center of the city while looking at the shops around him, and he was in no hurry as he casually strolled out of the city.

After emerging from the city, he walked for a while longer before abruptly springing up from the ground and vanishing in a flash.

250 kilometers was a distance that Han Li could cover in the blink of an eye, and he quickly descended in front of an elegant mountain that was several thousand feet tall.

He looked up to find that the mountain wasn't very tall, but it was extremely lush, and there was a ring of cloud and mist halfway up the mountain, giving it the appearance of an immortal abode.

He also noticed a layer of faint and peculiar spiritual power fluctuations that encompassed the entire mountain like an enormous, invisible net.

After observing the mountain for a moment, he withdrew his gaze, then made his way toward a grand hall situated at the entrance to the mountain.

Upon entering the hall, he was greeted by a sight of a massive screen, upon which the entirety of Mount Younyang was embroidered in golden thread, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

In front of the screen was a large wooden table that was of a reddish-purple color. Its surface was as smooth as a mirror, and a beast-head incense burner was sitting on the corner of the table, out of which incense smoke was billowing incessantly.

Behind the cloud of smoke was an elderly man in a scholarly azure robe, and he was reading an ancient book with keen interest, seemingly not having detected Han Li's arrival at all.

Han Li looked around to find that there was no one else in the hall, so he approached the table before clearing his throat to catch the elderly man's attention.

Only then did the elderly man raise his head to look at Han Li, and a hint of displeasure flashed through his eyes.

"Are you here to rent a cave abode?" the elderly man asked.

"Do you have any cave abodes that are more quiet and secluded in location?" Han Li asked.

The elderly man gave him a disgruntled glance as he replied, "I've heard this request so many times that my ears are about to develop callouses! Everyone who comes here asks for the same thing. Do you all regard yourselves as True Immortals?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of spiritual pressure that was far superior to the Grand Ascension Stage erupted out of Han Li's body, and the elderly man almost fell out of his chair in shock and horror.

He hurriedly stood up from his chair with a fearful expression, extending a deep bow as he implored, "Please forgive me for my insolence, Senior."

Han Li had no intention of pursuing the matter, and he withdrew his aura as he tossed a small pouch of spirit stones at the elderly man, then said, "Find me a quiet cave abode, and keep the change."

The elderly man accepted the pouch of spirit stones, and a hint of elation flashed through his eyes as he pointed at the giant screen behind him and said, "This cave abode here is situated on the edge of the Sun Watch Cliff on the mountain summit, and it's always been the most peaceful of the few A-grade cave abodes on the mountain. Will this one suffice for your needs?"

Han Li turned to find that a speck of light had appeared on the summit of the mountain embroidered on the screen, and it was indeed quite a peaceful and secluded location that was far away from all of the other cave abodes.

"Alright, I'll take that one," Han Li replied with a nod.

The elderly man immediately stowed the spirit stones away, then handed a round black badge to Han Li.

Moments later, outside the hall.

Han Li injected a wisp of magic power into the round badge, and a layer of faint dark golden light instantly appeared on its surface.

According to the elderly man, not only did this badge serve as the key to opening the cave abode, it was also the token that would allow him to enter Mount Youyang's mountain protection array.

As long as he had this badge in his possession, he would be able to fly anywhere on Mount Youyang. Otherwise, he would trigger the array and be targeted as a trespasser.

Han Li looked up at the sun, which was gradually setting in the west, and he flew up toward the mountain summit in a flash.

Before long, he had already arrived in a relatively spacious cave abode.

Even though restrictions had already been set up here, Han Li still set up several more restrictions of his own for peace of mind.

After that, he arrived in the secret chamber and sat down with his legs crossed, where he stared absentmindedly at the space before him with different emotions flashing through his eyes.

He had seen and heard many things in Black Wind City on this day that had left a deep impression on him.

After a brief silence, Han Li suddenly called out, "Mo Guang."

His shadow immediately swayed and warped for a moment, following which a shadowy figure emerged. It was none other than Mo Guang, and its expression was still as wooden as ever.

"Do you know how pill masters are ranked in the Immortal Realm, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang?" Han Li asked.

"According to my knowledge, pill masters of the Immortal Realm are primarily split up into three categories, namely Temporal, Earthly, and Heavenly," Mo Guang replied.

Chapter 140: Dao Pill

Han Li nodded with a contemplative look in his eyes, then said, "I see, so there really are Heavenly Pill Masters above Earthly ones. If I'm not mistaken, I presume Temporal Pill Masters can only refine pills useful to normal cultivators, while Earthly Pill Masters are capable of refining pills useful to immortals. So what sets a Heavenly Pill Master apart from those two?"

"You're largely correct on the classification of Temporal and Earthly Pill Master. As for Heavenly Pill Master, they're also known as Dao Pill Masters, and they're the loftiest pill refinement masters of the Immortal Realm. The one thing that separates them from other pill masters is their ability to refine dao pills," Mo Guang explained.

"How are dao pills different from other pills?" Han Li asked.

"Dao pills are pills that contain the power of laws," Mo Guang replied.

A thought seemed to have occurred to Han Li upon hearing this, and he asked, "Does that mean that consuming such pills will allow one to directly perceive the power of laws?"

"In the Immortal Realm, there are two main paths that immortals take to master the power of laws in order to become True Immortals, the first of which is through the use of cultivation methods, cultivating for vast spans of time for the slim chance of being able to attain the power of laws.

“The second path is to refine some type of spirit material that contains a certain type of power of laws into a pill, then taking that pill to directly perceive the power of laws contained within," Mo Guang explained.

Han Li was astonished to hear this, but he took a deep breath to compose himself, then asked, "Is that really true? Doesn't that mean that taking a single dao pill would save tens of thousands, perhaps even hundreds of thousands of years of cultivation?"

"That's not the case. Even if one does manage to obtain a dao pill, there's still only a very slim chance that they'll be able to attain the power of laws contained in the pill. However, even so, these pills are still immensely beneficial to perceiving the power of laws," Mo Guang explained.

"The probability of being able to attain the power of laws through the consumption of dao pills must be related to the quality of the dao pill, right?" Han Li asked.

"Of course. Generally speaking, dao pills will definitely contain the power of laws, but not all pills that contain the power of laws are dao pills. The exact way to tell whether a pill is a dao pill or not is to see if there are dao patterns present on its surface following refinement, and the quality of a dao pill can be determined based on how many dao patterns it has," Mo Guang explained.

"Dao patterns, eh? Do you how many dao patterns the highest grade dao pills will carry?" Han Li asked.

"The most number of dao patterns a pill can have is nine, and those are referred to as ninth-tier dao pills, but they exist almost only in legends. Even first-tier dao pills are extremely rare and precious in the Immortal Realm," Mo Guang replied.

"I see... No wonder Heavenly Pill Masters are so revered in the Immortal Realm," Han Li mused.

"I'm aware that back in the Spirit Realm, you were already quite a capable pill refinement master, so I'm assuming you're asking these questions because you have aspirations of becoming a Heavenly Pill Master yourself.

“However, according to my knowledge, perhaps one in every 1,000 pill masters could become an Earthly Pill Master, but even among 100,000 Earthly Pill Master, perhaps not even a single one would go on to become a Dao Pill Master. As for Heavenly Pill Masters capable of refining high-grade dao pills, those are even rarer," Mo Guang said.

"Pill refinement is something that requires experience. Spirit materials that contain the power of laws are extremely rare, so there simply isn't enough of those materials to practice on," Han Li said with a smile, seemingly completely unsurprised by how rare Heavenly Pill Masters were.

"That is indeed an important reason. The other reason is that dao pill recipes are just are rare, and they're virtually all in the possession of the Immortal Realm's most powerful entities. Just like pill refinement masters of the Spirit Realm, most Heavenly Pill Masters serve those powerful entities, and its extremely rare to see an independent Heavenly Pill Master," Mo Guang explained.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Also, there's a rumor about dao pills, which is that the recipe for each type of dao pill can only be mastered by a set number of Heavenly Pill Masters. Once this quota is filled, no one else will be able to master the refinement method for that type of dao pill," Mo Guang added.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this. "Really? That sounds a little far-fetched."

"No one has been able to verify the authenticity of this rumor, but everyone would rather believe that it's true than renounce the claim. Hence, generally speaking, unless it's absolutely necessary to do so, no one is willing to share their dao pill recipe with others," Mo Guang said.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this. This was completely understable to him as he would do the exact same thing in that position.

"That's all I know about dao pills and Heavenly Pill Masters, I hope this information was helpful to you," Mo Guang concluded, then prepared to return to Han Li's shadow.

However, another thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he called out, "Please hold on for a moment, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, I have something else to ask you."

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"I'd like to know more about immortal origin stones," Han Li said.

"Immortal origin stones are fantastic things that can quickly replenish one's immortal spiritual power during battle, and can also be used to enhance one's rate of cultivation, so they're extremely rare and sought-after everywhere in the Immortal Realm," Mo Guang said.

"I see, no wonder it can be used as a type of currency. How long does it take to create an immortal origin stone?" Han Li asked.

"That differs from person to person. Generally speaking, a late-True Immortal cultivator would be able to create one in a year, while a mid-True Immortal cultivator would take a decade, and it would take over a century for an early-True Immortal cultivator," Mo Guang replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Five immortal origin stones were required to use the teleportation array, and in Han Li's mind, if these immortal origin stones didn't take very long to create, then he would've done so himself, but it seemed that this wasn't a feasible option.

"The timeframes that I just laid out apply only to low-grade immortal origin stones. Just like spirit stones, immortal origin stones are also split up into four grades, namely low-grade, mid-grade, high-grade, and top-grade. Generally speaking, only high-grade immortals will be able to create high-grade and top grade immortal origin stones," Mo Guang continued.

"Aside from the constant injection of immortal spiritual power, are there any other requirements to creating such stones?" Han Li asked.

"During the creation of an immortal origin stone, the creator will be unable to cultivate. No immortal is willing to deal with such a damning limitation, and that's why immortal origin stones of all grades are extremely rare in the Immortal Realm," Mo Guang replied.

Han Li nodded in response, and a disappointed look surfaced in his eyes.

It seemed that his chances of being able to exchange for immortal origin stones were also extremely slim.

Seeing as Han Li had fallen silent, Mo Guang knew that his services were no longer required, and it vanished into Han Li's shadow in a flash.

……

That night.

A streak of light abruptly rose up from the summit of Mount Youyang, then vanished in the blink of an eye like a flash of lightning.

Shortly thereafter, a figure appeared in a secluded region of the sea tens of thousand of kilometers away, hovering above the surface of the water.

It was none other than Han Li, and his eyes were as bright as stars as he made a grabbing motion in front of his own chest, then tossed something high up into the air before beginning to chant an incantation.

As he did this, the small vial that was hovering in mid-air began to tremble violently, and all of the world's origin qi within the surrounding area also began to display signs of unrest.

A spherical azure light barrier began to slowly expand outward in all directions, and the waves on the surface of the sea began to surge and churn.

Seven days and seven nights passed by in the blink of an eye.

A small crystal slowly descended out of the sky, alongside the small vial, which had become virtually completely transparent, and the sea had returned to a calm and tranquil state.

Han Li had taken an Origin Return Pill in advance, so he wasn't left in an emaciated condition as he had been in the past. However, he was still looking rather feeble and weary, and after catching the crystal and the vial, he immediately flipped a hand over to produce a green jade vial, out of which he poured another Origin Return Pill that he promptly devoured.

A cool and refreshing sensation began to spread through his throat, and as the pill entered his stomach, the cool sensation quickly turned into a surge of warmth, which flowed throughout his body before finally entering his dantian.

He felt a slightly warm sensation in his dantian, following which the rate at which he was absorbing the world's origin qi increased drastically, thereby significantly enhancing his rate of immortal spiritual power recovery.

Manager Lu had told him about how exceptionally efficacious high-grade pills were, and at the time, Han Li hadn't taken it to heart, but only after taking these Origin Return pills did he come to realize just how different they were from the pills he had taken in the past.

This was a pill that could drastically enhance the rate of immortal spiritual power recovery for a short time. Furthermore, it could also be taken to enhance the rate of creation of immortal origin stones, so it was no wonder that they cost such a steep price.

After resting on the spot for a moment, Han Li flew back toward Black Wind City as a streak of azure light.

As soon as Han Li reappeared in the Thousand Medicine House, he was immediately spotted by Manager Lu, who was attending to another customer. He was rather taken aback to see Han Li back so soon, but he quickly excused himself, then approached Han Li with a warm smile.

"Welcome, Senior. To what do I owe this honor?" he asked as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

"The pills that I purchased from here last time were quite good, so I decided to come back and have another look," Han Li replied with a smile.

Manager Lu's smile widened even further upon hearing this, and he quickly led Han Li upstairs as he said, "You are most welcome to visit our shop at anytime, Senior. Please come with me."

Just like during Han Li's last visit, the fifth floor was very quiet, with not a single customer present.

"Have you come to purchase more Origin Return Pills, or would you like to try some other types of pills?" Manager Lu asked.

"Before I decide what pills I want to buy, I have some questions I'd like to ask you," Han Li said in a calm manner.

Manager Lu faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response. "Please go ahead, Senior."

"Not only are the pills sold in your shop very fast-acting, they're extremely efficacious as well, and I presume that must be directly related to the quality of the spirit ingredients used and the skills of the pill refinement master, right?" Han Li asked.

"That is indeed the case. It sounds like you're an expert in the art of pill refinement, Senior," Manager Lu said with a smile.

"I wouldn't call myself an expert, I'm only dabbled a little in pill refinement myself in the past as well," Han Li replied.

Manager Lu seemed to have been rather taken aback to hear this, and he hurriedly asked, "May I ask what tier pill refinement master you are, Senior?"

Han Li put on an embarrassed expression as he replied, "Truth be told, I've been residing in a secluded area for a long time prior to coming here, and I've never had a chance to have my pill refinement skills evaluated. One of the reasons I came today is to have my skills evaluated by a pill refinement master of your shop so I can determine what level I'm at."

Chapter 141: Pill Refinement Examination

Manager Lu's brows furrowed ever so slightly upon hearing this, but his expression then quickly returned to normal.

"Rest assured, Manager Lu, I'm willing to cover all expenses for the examination," Han Li added.

Manager Lu didn't hesitate any longer upon hearing this, and he replied, "In that case, it would be downright rude of our Thousand Medicine House to turn you down. Please come with me, Senior."

With that, he promptly made his way out of the room, leading Han Li back downstairs, then emerged from the rear hall on the first floor before traveling along a path that led to the backyard.

Deep in the backyard was a circular archway that separated it from the front yard.

Even before arriving at the archway, Han Li detected a transparent light barrier present in the air within the archway, and judging from the spatial fluctuations emanating from it, it seemed to have been a teleportation array.

Upon arriving at the archway, Manager Lu stopped in his tracks, then turned back to Han Li aske said, "Please wait here for me while I make our presence known, Senior."

He then flipped a hand over to produce a purple badge, which he waved at the archway up ahead, and a burst of bright light immediately appeared within the archway.

Upon stepping into the archway, Manager Lu instantly vanished.

Han Li inspected his surroundings for a moment, following which the archway lit up again, and Manager Lu's voice rang out from within.

"Please come in, Senior."

Han Li did as he was told, stepping into the archway.

As soon as he did so, he immediately arrived in a hot environment with a rich and complex medicinal aroma in the air.

He looked around to discovered that they seemed to be in a hall that resembled an underground palace, and there were several wide paths leading in all directions.

On the walls on either side of the path were a series of copper doors, each of which was around 10 feet tall, and the light of flames could just barely be made out beyond them.

Before Han Li had a chance to take a good look at his surroundings, Manager Lu led him down one of the paths, which led to a spacious guest hall.

Inside the room sat a red-haired elderly man with a medium build, wearing a short dark purple robe. He was holding a teacup with one hand and the lid of the teacup in the other.

Han Li was immediately able to sense from the man's aura that he was a Grand Ascension cultivator.

Upon seeing the arrival of Han Li's duo, the elderly man set down his teacup and rose to his feet.

Manager Lu turned to Han Li as he introduced, "This is Master Zhu, an A-grade Temporal Pill Master, and he's agreed to conduct your examination."

"You have my thanks, Master Zhu," Han Li said as he extended a salute.

The red-haired elderly man could sense that Han Li's cultivation base wasn't inferior to his own, so he didn't dare to show any disrespect and returned Han Li's salute as he said, "If you want to examine your pill refinement skills, then I suggest we each refine a Sunray Pill, and by comparing the quality of our pills, we'll be able to determine your skill level."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "Sunray Pill? I'm afraid I don't know the refinement method for this pill. Is this something sold by your pill shop?"

"Oh?"

The red-haired elderly man was rather taken aback to hear this, seemingly rather surprised by Han Li's lack of knowledge, and he was beginning to look down on Han Li a little.

"There's no need to purchase the recipe. Sunray Pills are considered to be quite valuable among temporal pills, but its recipe is quite readily available in this area, so it's not worth much, and I'm happy to give it to you as a gift."

The red-haired elderly man swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, sending a white jade slip flying toward Han Li.

Han Li caught the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and he couldn't help but feel a little dismayed by what he saw.

The pill recipe was free, but all of the medicinal ingredients listed were quite expensive, and he had to pay for two batches, so this was quite a steep price to pay.

The red-haired elderly man then began to elaborate on some things that had to be kept in mind during the refinement of Sunray Pills.

Han Li listened carefully to his instructions, committing everything to memory. At the same time, he was pondering the steps that he was going to take and how he was going to control the temperature of his flame based on his past pill refinement experience.

A few minutes later, the two of them each accepted a storage pouch from Manager Lu, within which contained all of the ingredients required to refine Sunray Pills, following which each of them made their way into a pill refinement chamber.

A loud clang rang out as the heavy bronze gate was shut, and Han Li inspected hi surroundings to find that the pill refinement chambers here were rather different from the ones he had seen in the Spirit Realm.

There was barely anything in the chamber, with only a purple copper pill refinement furnace positioned at the center of the room. There was no firepit on the ground, nor were there any fire-starting runes on the furnace.

Complex runes had been engraved onto the walls and the ground, seemingly forming some type of restriction that was capable of condensing and sealing the spiritual qi within the chamber.

After taking a moment to familiarize himself with his surroundings, he began to focus on the task at hand.

He raised a hand before snapping his fingers, and a silver flame flew into the pill furnace like a bird.

Scorching silver flames instantly rose up within the furnace, and only after about 15 minutes had passed, once the furnace had reached a sufficient temperature, did Han Li gradually begin to add medicinal ingredients to it.

As one spirit ingredient after another flew into the furnace, a medicinal aroma began to waft through the entire pill refinement chamber.

Around two hours later, a faint sound rang out from within the pill furnace, and Han Li caught sight of a cloud of faint purple mist beginning to rise up out of the gap on the top of the furnace. It lingered above the furnace without dispersing, presenting an intriguing sight to behold.

According to the red-haired elderly man's instructions, this was the point when he should've been adding the Cloudform Herb.

However, as Han Li picked up the Cloudform Herb, a hesitant look appeared in his eyes.

He had refined countless pills in the past, and there was a hierarchy of importance that applied to all ingredients used in pill refinement. The purposes served by the ingredients differed depending on their level of importance.

The Cloudform Herb wasn't a spirit ingredient that was unique to the Immortal Realm. Instead, it was something that he had used back in the Spirit Realm, so he knew that it properties were quite mild, and it was normally used to balance out the medicinal effects of the other ingredient. In the case of the Sunray Pill, it served that same purpose.

At this point, the purple mist had only just begun to rise up from the furnace, which meant that the other ingredients had only just begun to release their medicinal effects, and there was no need to balance them out yet. Hence, this was definitely not the best time to be adding in the Cloudform Herb, and that was the reason for his hesitance.

However, he quickly made a decision, sticking by his gut instinct.

Around another hour passed, and the purple mist billowing out of the pill furnace had become a lot denser. Only then did Han Li lift the furnace lid before tossing in the Cloudform Herb.

As a strong medicinal aroma wafted into his nostrils, a hint of elation appeared in his eyes.

Right at this moment, the surrounding walls suddenly began to glow, and the array patterns engraved upon them were activated of their own accord.

A small vortex instantly took shape in the entire pill refinement chamber, sweeping up the spirit power that was escaping from the pill before directing it back to the pill furnace.

……

Around four hours later, the red-haired elderly man had already emerged from his pill refinement chamber, and he was waiting together with Manager Lu outside Han Li's pill refinement chamber.

Around another 15 minutes passed, and the door of Han Li's pill refinement chamber also swung open, following which he emerged with a white vial in his hand.

Manager Lu smiled as he said, "Looks like you've successfully refined the Sunray Pill as well, Senior. Congratulations."

"I don't know how well I was able to refine the pill, so I'll have to trouble the two of you to appraise it for me," Han Li said as he offered them the vial.

Manager Lu accepted the vial before pulling out the stopper, and a rich medicinal aroma immediately wafted out from within.

The red-haired elderly man expression instantly changed slightly upon catching a whiff of the aroma, and he unconsciously sidled up closer to Manager Lu to take a closer look at Han Li's pill.

Placed on Manager Lu's hands were the two batches of three Sunray Pills that Han Li and the red-haired elderly man had refined. On the surface, they didn't look very different, with the only notable disparity being that Han Li's pills appeared a little smaller.

Han Li turned his gaze to the red-haired elderly man, and he was just about to ask for his opinion when the latter heaved a faint sigh before departing without a word.

Manager Lu made no effort to stop him. Only after he had completely disappeared out of view did he turn to Han Li with a peculiar look on his face as he explained, "Please don't take it to heart, Senior. Master Zhu is not trying to be rude, he's just feeling a little... defeated."

Han Li immediately understood what Manager Lu was trying to say, and he waved a hand with a smile as he said, "In that case, I'll have to trouble you to appraise these pills, Manager Lu."

Manager Lu wasn't a pill refinement master, but he was a very skilled pill appraiser, and he said, "If what you said earlier is true, and you really haven't come into contact with any high-grade pills of the Immortal Realm prior to this, then I can only say that you have immense talent for pill refinement.

“Your control over temperature is incredibly precise, allowing you to eradicate all of the impurities in these Sunray Pills while also completely preserving the medicinal effect. The quality of these pills exceeds that of the ones refined by Master Zhu."

"So where would I rank as a pill refinement master in the Immortal Realm?" Han Li asked as a faint smile appeared on his face.

"Even though you only refined the Sunray Pill on this occasion, judging from the quality of the pill, you are undoubtedly already an A-grade Temporal Pill Master," Manager Lu replied with a serious expression.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

Even though he didn't have to display the full extent of his skills in the refinement of a pill of this caliber, the level of complexity and difficulty of refining this pill was not inferior to that of the top-tier pills of the Spirit Realm.

With that in mind, his past pill refinement skills would've most likely only landed him the rank of C-grade Temporal Pill Master in the Immortal Realm.

Manager Lu could see that Han Li didn't seem particularly excited about this appraisal, and he added, "Given your current pill refinement skills, there's definitely a chance that you could become an Earthly Pill Master in the future."

"Thank you for kind words, Fellow Daoist Lu," Han Li replied, and right there and then, he made up his mind, resolving himself to become a Heavenly Pill Master.

Once he reached that level, all he would need to do would be to find a suitable pill recipe, and he would be able to refine those mysterious crystals produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial into dao pills.

He had a unique advantage over others in that it was far easier for him to obtain spirit materials that contained the power of laws.

After a brief hesitation, Manager Lu asked, "May I ask if you're planning to settle permanently in Black Wind City, or are you just visiting on a temporary basis?"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and Manager Lu hurriedly explained, "Please don't misunderstand, Senior, I only wanted to invite you to join our Thousand Medicine House as a guest pill master. Given your skills, I'm sure you'll be ranked second only to Master Hao in no time, and once you get there..."

Han Li waved a hand to cut off Manager Lu as he said, "I'm only stopping by in this city for a short time, but I appreciate the kind offer."

Manager Lu could tell that Han Li didn't seem to be lying, so he could only heave a forlorn sigh and drop the subject.

After that, Han Li purchased some more Origin Return Pills, then paid for them along with the cost of the Sunray Pills before promptly departing.

Of course, the six Sunray pills refined by himself and the red-haired elderly man had also been taken by him.

Chapter 142: Best of Both Worlds

After leaving the Thousand Medicine House, Han Li didn't immediately return to his cave abode on Mount Youyang. Instead, he began to explore some of the larger shops nearby.

The pills that he had purchased up to this point had almost completely exhausted his stash of spirit stones, and he was definitely going to need spending money, so he was planning to sell some of his materials and treasures for top-grade spirit stones.

After walking for a while, he made his way onto a crowded main street, and he spotted a tall building that occupied the best spot on the entire street.

The building was three stories tall, and it was entirely constructed from fire clay bricks. There was a pair of gold-plated pillars in front of the entrance, supporting a hexagonal eave, atop which were glazed green tiles and golden rooftop beasts, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Above the entrance was a large red plaque with a golden border, upon which was inscribed the words "Exotic Treasure House" in majestic gold-plated text.

Han Li took a glance at the plaque, then made his way up the stone steps before striding over the doorstep to enter the shop.

There were quite a few customers in the shop, gathered together in small groups in front of a series of redwood counters, examining and pointing at the treasures and materials placed on the shelves behind the counters.

Each group was accompanied by an azure-robed attendant, who were either offering descriptions and explanations of the shop's wares, or pulling down items from the shelves so the customers could examine them more closely.

Han Li took a brief glance at his surroundings, and he discovered that even though the treasures and materials on the shelves weren't of a particularly high caliber, with even the best ones among them only suitable to be used by Deity Transformation cultivators, they were all of an extremely high quality.

Right at this moment, he was spotted by an azure-robed attendant, who quickly excused himself, then approached Han Li with a smile as he asked, "What are you looking for? Do you require my assistance with anything?"

"I'm not here to buy, I'm here to sell," Han Li replied with a smile.

The azure-robed attendant was rather taken aback to hear this, then said, "I see. In that case, please come with me. Master Hai and Master Hu have always been the ones overseeing the purchase of items in our Exotic Treasure House, so I'll take you to see them."

Han Li merely nodded in response.

He was led by the attendant up a spiral wooden staircase straight to the third floor.

The layout of the third floor was completely different from that of the first floor. Rather than a shop, it bore a much closer resemblance to a tea room, and there was a series of separate rooms here.

The attendant made his way to the door of one of the rooms, then called out, "Master Hai, Master Hu, I've brought a customer."

The door of the room swung open, and Han Li was greeted by the sight of two people seated across from one another with a go board placed on the table between them, upon which were dozens of black and white stones.

The two of them looked up at Han Li, and upon sensing his aura, they immediately rose to their feet before extending a salute to him.

Among them was a scholarly azure-robed middle-aged man, and he waved a hand to dismiss the attendant, then said, "My name is Hai Wuliang, and this here is my colleague, Hu Dayou. May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist?"

The short-haired elderly man's attention was still on the game, and his gaze remained on the go board. He merely put on a faint smile and nodded at Han Li in an absent-minded manner.

"You can call me Liu Shi," Han Li replied.

"The two of us have always been responsible for the appraisal and purchase of items here in the Exotic Treasure House. The fact that you've been brought here must mean that you have something to sell to us, right?" the scholarly man asked with a warm smile.

"That's right. I have a water spirit bell here that I would like to have appraised," Han Li replied with a smile.

He flipped a hand over as he spoke, and a small blue bell appeared on the palm of his hand, The bell was glittering and translucent, with complex runes inscribed on its surface, and there were also several streaks of light that resembled roaming dragons swirling around it.

Hai Wuliang's eyes instantly lit up at the sight of the bell, and the short-haired elderly man also finally shifted his gaze away from the go board.

The two of them carefully accepted the water spirit bell, and after some close examination, they exchanged a glance with one another, following which one of them said, "This is a treasure of a very high caliber, and it can only be used by cultivators who are at least at the Grand Ascension Stage. However, it appears to not be an offensive or defensive treasure. Instead, it can only be used to seal all of the spiritual qi in an area."

This was a treasure that Han Li had secured from Han Qiu's storage bracelet, and just as the short-haired elderly man said, it was a rather niche treasure.

Hence, this was the first treasure that Han Li wanted to sell.

"You are indeed correct, Fellow Daoist. However, this is an exceptional treasure for those who are using water-attribute cultivation arts or want to conceal certain water-attribute spirit items. I'm sure you'll give me a fair price," Han Li said with a smile.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Hu Dayou asked, "I can do three top-grade spirit stones. What do you think Fellow Daoist?"

Han Li thought about this offer for a moment, and he felt it to be a fair price, so he nodded in response.

After that, he flipped his hand over once again to summon a white bead, which was giving off glacial qi that was visible even to the naked eye.

As soon as the bead appeared, the temperature of the room instantly plummeted, and a burst of faint crackling rang out from the teacups placed beside the go board. As it turned out, the tea inside had been instantly frozen solid.

The eyes of the two appraisers lit up once again, and they began to carefully examine the bead...

Around an hour later, Han Li slowly emerged from the Exotic Treasure House. Hai Wuliang and Hu Dayou had insisted on accompanying him down to the first floor and out of the shop.

Prior to his departure, they had invited him repeatedly to come back if he had any more treasures that he wanted to sell, and they assured him that they would give him good prices.

Han Li thanked them with a smile, then turned to depart, and the two appraisers watched him until he was completely out of sight before returning to the Exotic Treasure House, much to the bewilderment of all of the shop's attendants and customers.

They had purchased five treasures and a spirit material from Han Li, and they were ecstatic, thinking that they had made a massive haul.

However, in reality, they had only purchased around a tenth of everything that Han Li wanted to sell.

After leaving the Exotic Treasure House, Han Li visited the largest few shops in the city one by one, and only as night began to descend did he leave Black Wind City and return to his temporary cave abode on Mount Youyang.

After activating all of the restrictions in the cave abode, he went straight into his secret chamber.

Inside, he flipped a hand over to summon his azure cow mask, then placed it onto his face.

He then tapped his index and middle fingers against his glabella while chanting an incantation, and a burst of azure light flew out of the mask to form a giant array plate on the wall.

His gaze roamed over the right side of the array plate for a moment, following which he began flicking his fingers through the air.

One streak of light flew forth after another, and they all contained treasures that landed on the azure array plate.

Even though Han Li had altered his appearance several times and sold his stash of treasures and spirit materials in several batches, he still kept several of the most valuable treasures in his collection, including that black metal spike he had obtained from Wyrm 16.

These remaining treasures were virtually all scavenged from the bodies of the deceased Transient Guild members during his last trip to Red Moon Island, and most of them were signature treasures of theirs, so revealing them in Black Wind City could spell trouble for him.

Hence, he had decided to sell them all in the Transient Guild.

After that, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he turned his gaze to the left side of the array plate before writing something in the air.

As one glowing azure character flew into the array plate after another, a mission that was requesting leads for dao pill recipes quickly took shape.

After doing all of that, he stowed away his mask and closed his eyes to meditate.

……

Several days passed by in the blink of an eye, and Han Li thought that it was going to be a very long time until he heard back about his dao pill recipe mission, but to his surprise, that was the first thing that he received a response on.

However, he hadn't been given any dao pill recipes. Instead, he was informed that what he was requesting was too precious, and such a thing generally wouldn't appear in normal trades.

Only higher-level core members of the Transient Guild could occasionally encounter someone willing to put a dao pill recipe up for trade, but even then, the trade conditions were always extremely rigorous and virtually impossible to satisfy.

Han Li was also informed that if he could obtain the title of Heavenly Pill Master and a piece of suitable collateral, then it would be far easier to obtain dao pill recipes.

In fact, if he could satisfy those two conditions, then he wouldn't even have to actively seek out dao pill recipes on his own. Instead, other guild members would supply him with recipes and ingredients so that he could refine the pills for them.

After that, Han Li inquired about some matters related to the three paramount laws, and he was told that there were many scriptures that claimed to be able to allow one to cultivate the paramount laws, but most of them were under the ownership of powerful entities in the Immortal Realm, and they were generally kept secret from outsiders.

As for some that were circulating in the outside world, they were either incomplete or flawed and unreliable, so no one would dare to cultivate them.

Furthermore, during the past few days, all of the treasures that Han Li had put up for sale in the Transient Guild were sold one after another.

In addition to the spirit stones he had obtained from selling treasures and materials in Black Wind City, he had made a small fortune of over 600 top-grade spirit stones.

This was an astronomical sum of wealth for the average cultivator, but in Han Li's eyes, it was nowhere near enough for the grand auction that was coming up in three years and the steep cost that would be required to leave the Black Wind Sea.

However, he wasn't overly concerned, and he released another mission to the Transient Guild, this one to search for Soulbirth Flower seeds.

According to his estimates, with the assistance of the Heaven Controlling Vial, he would definitely be able to nurture a Soulbirth Flower above 10,000 years old prior to the commencement of the grand auction.

With such a precious item up his sleeve, he was confident that he would be able to exchange it for whatever he required.

However, if he were to use the spirit liquid to accelerate the maturation of a Soulbirth Flower, then the rate at which his Earthly Deity Avatar was deriving heavy water would undoubtedly be negatively impacted.

However, this was unavoidable, and it was impossible to get the best of both worlds.

Chapter 143: Missing Person

Several days later.

Han Li was cultivating in his secret chamber when his eyes suddenly sprang open, and he emerged from the room before releasing an incantation seal with a sweep of his sleeve.

The gate of his cave abode was opened, and Mu Xue was revealed standing outside.

Mu Xue hurriedly extended a respectful bow toward Han Li as he said, "Senior Liu, I've managed to find out some information on the matter that you entrusted to me last time."

"Come in," Han Li replied with a nod, gesturing fro Mu Xue to enter the cave abode.

After entering the cave abode, Mu Xue jumped straight to the topic without wasting any time. "According to the information I've been able to gather up to this point, there are two official ways through which one can obtain a teleportation spot."

"What are they?" Han Li asked.

"The first way requires one to be at the True Immortal Stage or above and serve as a guest elder at the island master's manor, doing his bidding for 100 years, and at the end of that period, they would be given a spot. The second way is to complete some of the missions occasionally released by the island master's manor, and these missions will occasionally grant a teleportation spot as its reward," Mu Xue said.

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this.

The first of those two methods was naturally not one that he was going to consider.

The wanted notice from the Ubiquitous Pavilion and the person who had sealed his nascent soul were like a pair of swords constantly hanging over his head, and that was one of the main reasons he was in such a hurry to leave the Black Wind Sea. 100 years was simply far too long, and he had no idea what could happen during that time.

As for the second method, any missions that could grant a teleportation spot as a reward were definitely going to be quite difficult to complete, but it was definitely more feasible than the first method, so this was something that he could keep an eye on.

After a brief silence, Mu Xue lowered his voice slightly as he continued, "Aside from these two official methods, I heard that these teleportation spots have been traded in the black market as well, but the price is always... very steep."

"How much does it usually cost for a spot?"

"Five immortal origin stones at the very least, and even then, I've heard they're very difficult to purchase."

Han Li shook his head upon hearing this. In addition to the required teleportation fee, that would amount to a total of 10 immortal origin stones.

For an early-True Immortal cultivator, even if they didn't cultivate at all, it would still take 1,000 years to refine 10 immortal origin stones.

He had inquired about immortal origin stones in the Transient Guild earlier, and he was told that it was occasionally possible to find immortal origin stones up for trade, but the asking price for each one was generally around 100 top-grade spirit stones, and as soon as one appeared, it would immediately be traded.

Given the current circumstances, it was clear that the master of Black Wind City wasn't very keen on the idea of allowing people to leave the Black Wind Sea.

"Alright, thanks for your hard work."

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a high-grade spirit stone as he spoke, then tossed it at Mu Xue.

Mu Xue was ecstatic, and he said in a grateful manner, "Thank you, Senior Liu! If you require my services for anything else, please feel free to tell me."

Han Li merely smiled and waved a hand to dismiss Mu Xue.

Following Mu Xue's departure, Han Li began to pace back and forth in his cave abode with his hands clasped behind his back, seemingly pondering something. Moments later, he left his cave abode altogether before flying toward a certain direction.

At the center of Black Wind City was a series of connected black buildings.

In stark contrast with their surroundings, these black buildings were entirely constructed from extremely high quality building materials, and they took up a vast area. The buildings had clearly also been arranged in a meticulous fashion, with countless pavilions, gardens, and bodies of flowing water inside. This was an enormous manor.

The entire manor was emanating a burst of faint black qi, making it appear as if it were enshrouded under a layer of black mist.

All of the passersby gave the manor a wide berth and were walking very quickly, not daring to approach the manor.

This was the island master's manor, which belonged to Island Master Lu Jun.

At the entrance of the manor was a huge plaza, at the edge of which stood a tall black palace. Above the entrance of the palace was a plaque that read "Talisman Letter Palace."

This was quite a lively and bustling place with many people frequently entering and exiting the palace. All of the visitors were at least at the Body Integration Stage, and the occasional Grand Ascension cultivator could be seen as well.

A streak of azure light shot forth from afar, then landed outside the palace to reveal Han Li.

He took a glance at the palace before him, then made his way inside.

The palace was rather empty, with only a bluestone wall that was over 100 feet tall standing at its very center, upon which was inscribed some lines of text.

A pair of black-robed men were standing on either side of the palace, and judging from their attire, they seemed to be serving the island master's manor.

At this moment, there were around a dozen cultivators littered throughout the palace, looking up at the stone wall, and there were also some familiar acquaintances among them discussing the missions on the wall.

Han Li drew to a halt near the stone wall before looking up at it to find that it was laden with around 20 to 30 missions, all of which were accompanied by clear descriptions and rewards.

Han Li immediately began searching for missions that granted teleportation spots as their reward, and he quickly found two, one of which was to search for a spirit material known as Azure Radiance Jade, while the other required one to be at or above the True Immortal Stage and oversee an island for 100 years.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

He had read about Azure Radiance Jade in scriptures on Dark Veil Island, so he knew that it was a spirit material that was said to contain the power of laws, so that definitely wasn't going to be easy to find.

Even if he could track down this spirit material, he would have to ponder whether it was worth exchanging it for a teleportation spot.

As for the other mission, that required 100 years to complete, so it was definitely not something that he was going to consider.

Right as a hint of disappointment appeared in his eyes, he suddenly spotted something that caught his attention.

There was a rather special mission at the very top of the stone wall, and it required one to search for a missing person, but the identity of the missing person wasn't specified.

The reward for this mission was massive, and anyone who completed it would be able to state a request to the island master to be fulfilled, as long as it was within reason.

The mission had only been released not long ago, and there was a note attached to it, stating that only those at or above the True Immortal Stage could take on the mission.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes.

This was a rather mysterious mission, and it didn't look like it was going to be easy to complete, but it was definitely more feasible than the other two missions.

After some contemplation, he began to approach the stone wall.

One of the black-robed men extended a salute toward Han Li, then asked in a respectful voice, "Would you like to take on a mission, Senior?"

"I'll take on this mission. Are there any more details available?" Han Li asked as he pointed at the mission.

Everyone around him immediately turned their attention to him with different looks on their faces.

The black-robed man's eyes immediately lit up, and he began to make his way out of the palace while gesturing for Han Li to follow along. "Please come with me, Senior."

"Does that mean he's a True Immortal cultivator?"

"That should be obvious! The fact that he dares to take on this mission clearly indicates that he's a True Immortal."

"I've never seen him before, so he's most likely not from the city."

As Han Li and the black-robed man made their way out of the palace, everyone erupted into spirited discussion.

There were countless cultivators gathered on Black Wind Island, but True Immortals were still exceedingly rare in the Black Wind Sea, and no one had expected such an unremarkable-looking young man to be a True Immortal.

Han Li paid no heed to the chatter behind him as he followed the black-robed man toward the island master's manor.

The guards at the entrance of the manor granted them free passage, and after passing through a series of winding corridors, they arrived in a large hall.

At this point, there were already around a dozen people gathered in the hall.

Upon hearing the sound of footsteps, most of them turned to glance at Han Li for a moment, then averted their eyes again.

All of these people were giving off enormous auras, clearly indicating that they were True Immortals as well.

Han Li didn't display any outward reaction to this, but internally, he was rather taken aback to discover that there were so many True Immortals on Black Wind Island.

"Please take a seat and wait here, Senior, someone will be here to deliver a debriefing on the mission soon," the black-robed man said.

Han Li nodded in response, then found a place to sit in the hall.

An azure-robed attendant approached him before offering him a cup of spirit tea that was giving off a delectable aroma.

Han Li raised the teacup to his lips, taking the opportunity to size up the other people in the room.

It was clear that they had taken on the same mission as him, and their cultivation bases were also all quite similar to his. Most of them were seated on their own with no verbal communication taking place, and some had even already closed their eyes to meditate.

However, not everyone was on their own.

There were three people seated next to one another in a rather conspicuous spot in the hall, and the trio consisted of a burly and imposing man, a young woman with a black veil over her face, and a thing young man, all of whom were chatting amicably with one another.

"Greetings, Fellow Daoist, my name is Guan Yong."

While Han Li was observing the people around him, a voice rang out beside him, and as it turned out, he had been approached by a chubby young man with a smile on his round face.

"My name is Liu Shi. It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Guan," Han Li replied with a nod as he set down his teacup.

"I don't recognize you, Brother Liu. Could it be that you only recently came to Black Wind Island?"

Guan Yong clearly had a very naturally outgoing personality, and he was already referring to Han Li as brother.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he replied, "Indeed, I only arrived at Black Wind Island just a few days ago. How did you know that?"

"I have a very outgoing personality and like to make friends, and there aren't many True Immortal cultivators in Black Wind City, so I know almost everyone," Guan Yong explained with a smile.

"I see. Your ability to make friends is very admirable," Han Li said with a nod.

Guan Yong was a rather chatty man, and Han Li had nothing better to do anyway, so he engaged in a casual conversation with Guan Yong.

He asked Guan Yong about some of the other people present, and he was able to learn quite a bit from the conversation.

Close to half a day passed by, during which time two more True Immortals had arrived in the hall.

At the stroke of noon, the sound of footsteps rang out from behind the hall, and an authoritative-looking middle-aged man wearing a black brocade robe emerged.

As soon as he arrived, the entire room instantly fell silent, and even the trio that had been chatting amicably with one another had stopped their conversation.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly at the sight of the man standing before him.

He felt as if he were looking at a tall mountain, and the aura emanating from the man's body was making his heart shudder with apprehension.

"Island Master!" Guan Yong was the first to rise to his feet before extending a salute toward the middle-aged man.

Han Li and the others also extended salutes of their own as he carefully sized up the most powerful figure in the entire Black Wind Sea.

Chapter 144: The Island Master's Missing Daughter

"There's no need for such formalities. Please take a seat, everyone."

The brocade-robed man's expression was calm and tranquil, but there was a barely detectable hint of agitation concealed deep within his eyes.

Han Li and everyone else in the room did as they were told, returning to their seats.

"I'm not going to waste any time here. The missing person that I'm searching for is none other than my daughter, Yuqing. Two days ago, she suddenly disappeared along with several companions, and these are some leads that I've managed to gather following her disappearance. If any of you can help me find my daughter, I'll be sure to reward you handsomely."

Lu Jun swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, releasing around a dozen jade slips at once, all of which landed on the tea tables beside the cultivators in the room.

Han Li picked up the jade slip, then pressed it against his forehead before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The jade slip contained a visage of Lu Yuqing, and she was a young woman dressed in white who appeared to have been around 18 to 19 years of age.

He was rather taken aback to discover that Lu Yuqing was none other than the white-robed young woman he had run into at the Thousand Medicine House not long ago.

Following her visage were the visages of several more people. These were the companions that had gone missing with Lu Yuqing, and their identities were clearly stated as well.

The first one was the blue-robed young man who had accompanied Lu Yuqing on her visit to the Thousand Medicine House, and his name was Fang Leng.

He was a Temporal Pill Master, and he was the disciple of a renowned Earthly Pill Master in the Black Wind Sea.

As for the others, they were all guards that had been assigned to Lu Yuqing.

All of them had left Black Wind Island using a teleportation array two or three days ago, and they had been missing since then.

The jade slip also contained a list of places that Lu Yuqing often frequented.

There wasn't much information in the jade slip, so Han Li was able to read through everything quite quickly, following which a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"Island Master, do you have any idea of why Young Mistress Yuqing may have suddenly disappeared?"

The question had been raised by the burly man in the trio, and everyone immediately turned their attention to him upon hearing this.

Han Li's gaze also fell upon the burly man. According to Guan Yong, these three had come from a place known as Splendid Mountain Island, and they referred to themselves as the Three Scourges of Splendid Mountain.

No one knew their names, and to outsiders, they were merely known as the First Scourge, the Second Scourge, and the Third Scourge, with the burly man being the First Scourge.

All three of them were itinerant immortals who had no set residence. Furthermore, they always worked together and had a reputation for being ruthless, so they were quite renowned in the Black Wind Sea, and no one dared to mess with them.

A hint of sorrow flashed through Lu Jun's eyes upon hearing this question, but he quickly composed himself as he replied, "My son, Lu Mo, left on a journey several years ago, but not only has not returned, his Origin Soul Lamp has also been snuffed out. To this day, I still have no idea what's happened to him.

“Yuqing has always been very close to her brother, and she had always wanted to go and find out the cause of his death, but I've never allowed her to go. I presume her sudden appearance may have something to do with this."

Everyone fell silent upon hearing this.

Han Li thought back to Lu Yuqing's conversation with Fang Leng back at the Thousand Medicine House on that day with a contemplative look in his eyes, and he recalled that they were indeed discussing something about Lu Yuqing's brother.

The First Scourge exchanged a glance with his companions, then said, "In that case, would it be possible for us to have a copy of Young Master Lu Mo's information as well? I'm sure that would help us in our search for Young Mistress Yuqing."

"That's a good idea," Lu Jun replied with a nod, then pulled out a jade slip along with around a dozen blank jade slips.

After making copies of the initial jade slip, each person in the room was given a copy.

Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip to find a rather messy and disorganized collection of information on Lu Mo.

All of a sudden, he caught sight of a rather surprising piece of information.

It was a visage of a blue tiger mask, but it wasn't very clear.

The mask was very similar to the ones worn by Transient Guild members, and it was rather familiar to Han Li.

That mask belongs to Wyrm 16

Han Li quickly recalled that Wyrm 16, with whom he had carried out a mission on Red Moon Island, had been wearing a blue tiger mask.

Could it be that Lu Mo is Wyrm 16?

Han Li couldn't be sure.

Right at this moment, Lu Jun swept his sleeve through the air once again, and around a dozen black badges were released before landing beside everyone in the room.

"These are Black Wind Badges. With these badges, you'll be able to use all of the teleportation arrays on Black Wind Island while carrying out your mission," Lu Jun explained.

Everyone immediately extended collective words of gratitude toward Lu Jun.

There were many teleportation arrays on Black Wind Island that were connected to other islands in the Black Wind Sea. Due to far all of the islands were away from one another, it would've normally been very expensive to travel to those islands through teleportation arrays, so these Black Wind Badges would save everyone a lot of spirit stones.

All of a sudden, a cold and forbidding look appeared on Lu Jun's face as he continued, "One more thing: none of you are to tell anyone about this mission. Otherwise, don't blame me for turning on you. If I want to have someone in the Black Wind Sea killed, they won't be able to get away no matter where they hide!"

"Rest assured, Island Master, our lips are sealed!" everyone in the room hurriedly assured.

Lu Jun's expression reverted back to normal as he said, "If any of you manage to bring back my daughter safely, I'll be sure to follow through on my promise and grant you one request."

"In that case, we'll begin our search right away. We'll be taking our leave now."

The First Scourge cupped his fist in a parting salute toward Lu Jun, then departed with the other two scourges.

Han Li and the others quickly departed as well, and before long, Lu Jun was the only one left in the room.

Right at this moment, a black-robed elderly man abruptly appeared beside him in a wraith-like manner. His hair and beard were all completely white, but his face was as delicate as an infant's. His aura was enormous, indicating that he was a mid-True Immortal cultivator.

"Can we really count on those people to save Yuqing? You should send me instead, Island Master," the black-robed elderly man said.

Lu Jun immediately shook his head as he sighed, "No. There's recently been a lot of activity taking place on Azure Feather Island, and it seems like they're about to make a big move, so none of us can leave Black Wind Island at a time like this. I'll simply have to count on those people to find Yuqing. I've promised them quite a handsome reward, so I'm sure they'll do everything in their power to find her."

"But..." The black-robed elderly man wanted to protest the matter further, but Lu Jun raised a hand to cut him off.

"We must keep our priorities in check. Unfortunately, there are more important things for us to worry about right now than Yuqing," Lu Jun said with a hint of weariness in his voice.

The black-robed elderly man heaved a resigned sigh upon hearing this. "I can't believe Yuqing would choose to run off at a time like this."

"She does whatever she wants because I've spoiled her rotten! Once she comes back, I'm going to teach her a good lesson!" Lu Jun harrumphed coldly.

"Yuqing is not entirely to blame. It's already been so many years, yet we still haven't been able to find out the cause of Mo'er's death, so it's no wonder that she would grow impatient," the black-robed elderly man sighed.

Lu Jun rose to his feet with an agitated expression, clasping his hands behind his back as he paced back and forth in the room.

He then drew to an abrupt halt as he said, "If this is just a simple disappearance, then that wouldn't be a cause for concern. What I'm most worried about is that she's inadvertently exposed her own identity and fallen into the hands of cultivators from Azure Feather Island. If that's the case, then we'll all be in a terrible situation."

The black-robed elderly man's brows furrowed slightly as he said, "Yuqing is a little sheltered, but she's a very bright and intelligent girl. On top of that, she's carrying several powerful spirit treasures, so I'm sure she'll be fine."

"I certainly hope so," Lu Jun sighed.

……

After departing from the island master's manor, Han Li and the others all flew toward the same place in silence.

Moments later, everyone had arrived in front of a huge rhomboid brick building in the city.

On the first floor of the building were around a dozen teleportation arrays of different sizes, all of which were giving off glowing white radiance, and a destination island was marked out beside each array.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this.

He had already been on Black Wind Island for several days, and during this time, he had learned extensively about Black Wind Island and the nearby region.

The islands that were marked out in the teleportation hall were all technically subsidiaries of Black Wind Island.

Unlike a small and rural island like Dark Veil Island, Black Wind Island was situated at the center of the Black Wind Sea, and it wasn't the only powerful island in the region. Hence, the smaller islands near the most prominent islands in the area would form alliances with those larger islands for protection.

Due to the fact that Black Wind Island had a teleportation array that led to the outside world, it had a unique advantage, and that was why it was such a thriving city.

However, it was also exactly because of this that it was attracting a great deal of envy from nearby island alliances. As a result, it had many enemies, and there were conflicts constantly taking place.

Thankfully, Lu Jun was a late-True Immortal cultivator, and he had many powerful guest elders at his beck and call, so he was able to keep all of the nearby forces in check, thereby ensuring the peace of Black Wind Island and also contributing to the peace of the entire Black Wind Sea to a certain extent.

However, none of these conflicts had anything to do with Han Li. All he had to do was find Lu Yuqing, and he would be able to leave the Black Wind Sea.

None of the other people had any idea where Lu Yuqing could be, but he already had a good guess of her location.

With that in mind, a faint smile appeared on his face, and he directed his gaze toward the teleportation arrays in the hall.

At this moment, the hall was completely empty aside from the cultivators in charge of overseeing the teleportation arrays.

Han Li's gaze fell upon one of the teleportation arrays, and he began to make his way toward it.

This was one of the islands that had been mentioned in the jade slip. Its name was Assembly Island, and according to the jade slip, Lu Yuqing had previously left Black Wind Island using this teleportation array.

Hence, if he wanted to find her, then Assembly Island was naturally the first place to visit.

Everyone else was thinking the same thing, and after a brief pause, all of them made their way toward that teleportation array.

A gray-haired elderly man beside the teleportation array was rather taken aback to see such a large group of people approaching him, and he hurriedly asked in a respectful voice, "Are you all here to take the teleportation arrays, esteemed seniors?"

"Why else would we come here? Hurry up and stop wasting our time! I'm in a hurry!" the First Scourge harrumphed coldly, then flashed his Black Wind Badge at the elderly man before stepping onto the array.

Everyone else also brought out their Black Wind Badges before stepping onto the array as well.

"Yes, my apologies, Senior."

The gray-haired elderly man didn't dare to delay, and he immediately cast a series of incantation seals, following which Han Li and everyone else vanished from the array amid a flash of radiant white light.

Chapter 145: Search

All Han Li saw was a burst of blinding white light, and in the next instant, he found himself in an azure stone hall, standing atop a teleportation array.

As soon as everyone emerged from the teleportation array, several people immediately flew out of the hall, including the three scourges.

Only one person could complete this mission, so the competition was very fierce.

Han Li and the rest of the cultivators exchanged a few glances, then made their way out of the hall in silence.

The hall was situated on a plot of elevated land, and one could see a complex system of streets and roads down below, as well as countless humanoid figures that were as tiny as sesame seeds.

It was clear that this was also a city, and it appeared to have been quite a large and bustling city as well, but it naturally couldn't compare with Black Wind City.

"You seem very confident, Brother Liu. Could it be that you already have an idea of where to begin your search?" Guan Yong asked with a smile.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he replied, "I'm afraid not, Brother Guan. I'm currently racking my brains, trying to think of where Young Mistress Lu could be. What about you? Have you thought of anything?"

"I'm just as lost as you are. Looks like all we can do is search for her by brute force," Guan Yong sighed.

The two of them chatted for a short while before parting ways, and at this point, everyone else had also already left.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, which contained a detailed map of the Black Wind Sea. He then injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip and quickly tracked down the location of Assembly Island.

Looks like I was right.

A contemplative look appeared in his eyes, and he rose up as a streak of azure light before hurtling away into the distance. Before long, he had already flown out of Assembly Island, and he flew around the nearby sea for a while to ensure that he wasn't being followed.

He then made a hand seal, and countless arcs of silver lightning erupted out of his body, instantly forming a round lightning array with a diameter in excess of 100 feet.

There were countless silver runes flashing within the array, and the array abruptly vanished amid a resounding thunderclap, leaving behind only several arcs of silver lightning that also quickly dissipated.

Several days later.

A flash of lightning appeared somewhere on the Black Wind Sea, and a silver array appeared out of thin air before quickly vanishing to reveal Han Li, who was looking a little weary.

He took a glance at his surroundings, and he spotted a black dot on the horizon, which seemed to have been an island.

"Finally," he murmured to himself, and instead of continuing to use his lightning teleportation array, he flew toward the island as a streak of azure light.

Given his current speed, it didn't take him very long at all to arrive at the island.

The earth on the island before him had a peculiar red hue, and the same applied to all of the vegetation on the island as well. This was none other than Red Moon Island, the island that he had previously visited on his mission for the Transient Guild.

Assembly Island was the closest of Black Wind Island's subsidiary islands to Red Moon Island, and in addition to that, Han Li was aware that there was a very good chance that Lu Mo was Wyrm 16, so he knew that it was very likely that Lu Yuqing had also gathered sufficient leads to find out that Lu Mo had perished on Red Moon Island.

Even though this was all just speculation from Han Li, he had no other leads, so there was no other direction for him to pursue.

He cast his gaze toward Red Moon Island, and his brows furrowed slightly.

The island was too massive, so even with his spiritual sense, it would take an extremely long time to scour the entire island.

After a moment of contemplation, he shot forth as a streak of azure light once again, flying toward the Red Moon City in the Kun Province, where Wyrm 16 had met his demise.

At the same time, his spiritual sense was fully activated to inspect his surroundings.

He couldn't search the entire island, so he could only pick out the likeliest locations.

It took him no more than half a day to cover close to half of the journey to his destination Red Moon Island, but he hadn't been able to find any further leads along the way thus far.

All of a sudden, he seemed to have noticed something, and he drew to an abrupt halt before descending onto the ground.

Down below was a lush forest, and there was a long trench in the ground that was thousands of feet in length. The soil on the edge of the trench had been completely charred black, as if it had been incinerated.

"These signs of battle are very recent, so the battle seems to have taken place not long ago," Han Li murmured to himself.

There was still some heat emanating from the charred soil, and judging from the damage caused, the person responsible had to have been at least a Grand Ascension cultivator.

Han Li didn't linger here any longer as he rose up into the air once again and continued to fly onward.

He made sure to be extra vigilant, and sure enough, he discovered many more similar signs of battle along the way.

Close to an hour later, Han Li had descended onto a grassland.

The ground up ahead was completely charred black and riddled with countless craters that were thousands of feet deep, clearly indicating that a fierce battle had recently taken place here.

He spread his spiritual sense through the area, then beckoned toward a certain direction, and the soil in one of the large craters up ahead stirred slightly, following which a piece of black cloth flew out from within and into Han Li's grasp.

Looking at the piece of black cloth, Han Li was reminded of the black attire worn by the cultivators serving the island master's manor on Black Wind Island. The material was identical.

With that in mind, he immediately rose up into the air once again as a streak of azure light, vanishing into the distance in a flash.

A short while later, silver lightning flashed above the giant crater, and he returned to the same spot.

There weren't any further signs of battle up ahead.

He didn't know who Lu Yuqing's enemies were, but it was clear that she and her companions had been defeated here, and it was unclear whether she was dead or alive.

All of a sudden, bright blue light began to glow from Han Li's eyes, and at the same time, his Law Destruction Eye appeared on his glabella amid a flash of black light.

The three bursts of light, one black and two blue, converged in front of him to form a huge black and blue eye, which was releasing waves of black and blue light that proliferated outward in all directions.

All of the world's origin qi in the surrounding area instantly appeared in his mind with exceptional clarity, resembling countless specks of light that were moving around in all directions in a chaotic fashion.

Even though there seemed to be no rhyme or reason to these chaotic specks of light, he was able to spot a trail of crimson light that seemed to have been drifting in a certain direction.

He immediately set off toward that direction, flying as quickly as he could, vanishing into the distant horizon in a flash.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li drew to an abrupt halt, then flew in another direction.

The person who had left the aura behind had changed directions here.

Only after several more directional changes did the lingering aura finally follow a single direction, and Han Li was able to truly commence his pursuit.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as countless arcs of silver lightning erupted out of his body, and another loud thunderclap rang out as he vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he reappeared hundreds of kilometers away, then disappeared once again amid another flash of lightning.

He didn't dare to teleport too long a distance each time for fear that his target would change directions again, but even so, he was still traveling at an extraordinary speed.

The lingering aura in the air was becoming clearer and clearer, indicating that he was closing in on his target.

In a region of the sea somewhere near Red Moon Island, a streak of bright red light was hurtling through the air at an incredible speed, containing a fiery red flying ark.

Atop the flying ark stood three figures, two of which were a square-faced middle-aged man and an elderly man with a white beard. Both of them were wearing azure robes with an azure feather design emblazoned on the sleeve.

The two of them were standing beside a gorgeous white-robed young woman, whose entire body had been bound by a chain of red light, and she was glowering at the two men with intense fury and resentment in her eyes.

"Speed up a bit more," the elderly man urged as he inspected his surroundings with tightly furrowed brows.

"This is already as fast as this Dragon Feather Ark can go, Brother Qi. Any faster than this and the ark's spiritual nature will be harmed. Besides, we've already killed all of those Black Wind Island cultivators and changed directions multiple times, surely no one will be able to track us down," the square-faced man said in a nonchalant manner.

"We can't afford to grow complacent before we return to Azure Feather Island. Keep accelerating, I'll cover the costs to repair any damage to your ark," the elderly man urged.

"Fine."

The square-faced man gave a slightly exasperated shrug, then released a series of incantation seals.

Countless crimson runes instantly appeared around the flying ark, resembling an undulating wave.

The ark immediately sped up by about 30%, hurtling along so quickly that the surrounding scenery had turned into a complete blur.

The elderly man's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and a flipped a hand over to produce an array plate.

However, right as he was about to activate the array plate, his expression changed drastically, and he swung around to look behind the ark.

"What is it, Brother Qi?" the square-faced man asked with a perplexed expression.

"Someone's chasing after us!" the elderly man exclaimed with a grim expression.

The square-faced man immediately turned to look behind the ark as well, and a surprised look appeared on his face.

Sure enough, a speck of silver lightning had appeared on the horizon, and it was flashing incessantly.

Furthermore, with each flash, the silver lightning would become a little larger, indicating that whoever was chasing after them was quickly closing in.

"What incredible speed!" the elderly man exclaimed with a stunned expression, while a hint of elation appeared in Lu Yuqing's eyes.

"Shit!"

The square-faced man gritted his teeth, then expelled a mouthful of blood essence, and he made a rapid series of hand seals while the blood essence transformed into a ball of crimson light that vanished into the flying ark.

Streaks of fiery red light instantly erupted out of the ark, and it was as if the entire ark had been set alight. As a result, it sped up by twofold and began hurtling through the air as a red blur.

Even though the flying ark had accelerated even further, its speed was still clearly inferior to its pursuer, and the distance between them was still slowly diminishing. Before long, the pursuer was only several dozen kilometers away.

A dark look appeared on the elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he was just about to spring into action when another flash of silver lightning appeared behind him before vanishing in a flash.

In the next instant, a rumbling thunderclap rang out directly above them, and a ball of silver lightning appeared, followed by another resounding thunderclap as a bolt of silver lightning that was as thick as a water tank came crashing down with devastating power.

Chapter 146: The Two Azure Feather Island Cultivators

The elderly man immediately raised a hand upon seeing this, releasing a burst of black light that contained a small black flag.

The small flag instantly unfurled and began to glow with dazzling black light, which formed a menacing ghostly head that chomped down onto the bolt of silver lightning.

A layer of silver runes appeared on the surface of the silver lightning, and it abruptly accelerated, vanishing into the ghostly head's mouth in a flash.

The elderly man's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, the ghostly head exploded violently amid a resounding boom.

The bolt of lightning emerged from the other side, having shrunk down significantly, then struck the flying ark with tremendous force, causing it to explode into pieces.

Before the ark was destroyed, the two azure-robed cultivators had already taken Lu Yuqing and fled to several thousand feet away.

Meanwhile, the silver lightning in the sky flashed a few times before dissipating to reveal Han Li. His gaze roamed over the pair of azure-robed cultivators before settling on Lu Yuqing, and he was very relieved to see that even though she was bound, she was largely unharmed.

The elderly man's face had paled slightly, and he yelled, "Who are you? I'd advise you not to meddle in the business of our Azure Feather Island unless you have a death wish!"

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and his gaze fell upon the azure feather design on the elderly man's sleeve.

Azure Feather Island was a vastly renowned island in the Black Wind Sea, and it was one of the most powerful islands aside from Black Wind Island. Its island master, Daoist Master Azure Feather, was no less renowned than Lu Jun, having already reached the pinnacle of the mid-True Immortal Stage countless years ago, and it was anyone's guess whether he had progressed to the late-True Immortal Stage.

At the moment, Azure Feather Island was also Black Wind Island's most formidable enemy.

In particular, Azure Feather Island had been constantly recruiting other nearby powers under its wing, and it was beginning to pose a serious threat to Black Wind Island.

However, this wasn't the time to be considering such matters, and in the next instant, Han Li vanished on the spot once again amid a flash of silver lightning, not bothering to answer the elderly man's question.

In the next instant, he appeared behind the pair of azure-robed cultivators in a wraith-like manner, and silver lightning flashed all over his body as he made a grabbing motion.

A giant hand formed by silver lightning instantly appeared above the pair of cultivators before swooping down with tremendous force.

Even before the giant hand arrived, a burst of terrifying power had already come crashing down like a mountain.

All of a sudden, a series of purple devilish patterns appeared over the elderly man's exposed skin, and two balls of purplish-black devilish flames appeared before intertwining with one another, rising up to form a pillar of flames that enveloped his entire body.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as the giant silver hand grabbed onto the fiery pillar, resulting in an eruption of silver and purple light, as well as a burst of shockwaves that swept through the air in all directions.

Ultimately, the giant lightning hand seemed to have been kept at bay.

Right at this moment, crimson light flashed from the square-faced man's body, and the 13 short crimson blades that he had already summoned rapidly swelled to over 100 feet in length, with crimson flames surging over them.

The 13 huge fiery blades shot forth through the air, striking the giant lightning hand with tremendous force and piercing deep into it.

The giant hand instantly exploded into countless arcs of silver lightning that erupted in all directions, transforming the entire surrounding area into a sea of silver lightning that was several hundred feet in size.

The pair of azure-robed cultivators were caught off guard by the shockwaves resulting from the explosion, and they involuntarily stumbled back a few steps.

However, the silver lightning and the shockwaves left Lu Yuqing completely unharmed, parting down the middle and surging past her body right as they were about to strike her.

Lu Yuqing had been so terrified that she had closed her eyes in fear, but her expression eased slightly as she realized that she hadn't been harmed.

Immediately thereafter, the chaotic arcs of lightning abruptly drew to a halt, then rapidly converged to form a silver lightning array around Lu Yuqing in the blink of an eye.

"Stop him!" the square-faced man exclaimed in an alarmed voice, and he swept a sleeve through the air to send a burst of crimson swordlight hurtling directly toward the lightning array.

At the same time, a burst of black and purple devilish flames shot forth from the other side, sweeping toward the lightning array as well.

However, it was already too late. Silver lightning flashed within the array, and Lu Yuqing vanished into thin air, only to instantly reappear beside Han Li with the chains of light binding her body completely gone.

The square-faced man's expression stiffened upon seeing this, while the pillar of purplish-black flames receded to reveal the elderly man.

The devilish patterns on his body made it impossible to glean his expression, but the fury in his eyes was very apparent.

Lu Yuqing was ecstatic, and a grateful look appeared on her face as she said, "Thank you for saving me! May I know your name?"

"My name is Liu Shi, and I've come to save you under instructions from your father," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

Lu Yuqing faltered slightly upon hearing this. "My father..."

Before she had a chance to say anything else, Han Li suddenly swept a sleeve through the air, and a silver lightning array instantly took shape around the two of them, following which they vanished from the spot amid a flash of lightning.

In the next instant, several giant fiery blades descended out of the sky, striking the spot where the two of them had just been standing.

The fiery blades naturally missed their target, and they plunged into the sea down below, causing the entire surface of the sea to boil and churn, raising a series of ferocious waves.

Han Li and Lu Yuqing were standing in mid-air not far away, and the latter had a look of lingering fear in her eyes, having only just realized what had just taken place.

"Get back," Han Li instructed.

Lu Yuqing immediately did as she was told, hurriedly flying away into the distance.

Meanwhile, the giant fiery blades arrived once again, hurtling toward Han Li from all directions to ensure that he had no course for retreat.

In response, Han Li raised both of his arms, and several thick bolts of silver lightning shot out of his palms. Countless silver lightning runes were flashing over the surfaces of the bolts of lightning, and they instantly transformed into several huge balls of silver lightning to meet the giant fiery blades.

Countless silver runes were flashing over the balls of lightning, and this was none other than the Lightningwield Technique that he had mastered back in the Spirit Realm.

Now that he possessed immortal spiritual power, he was able to unleash all types of secret techniques with a far higher degree of speed and proficiency than before.

The balls of lightning clashed with the fiery blades, resulting in an eruption of scintillating silver radiance amid a string of earth-shattering booms, and a series of rifts had appeared in the nearby space.

Immediately thereafter, several short fiery blades shot back out of the epicenter of the explosion. The spiritual light radiating from the blades had dimmed significantly, clearly indicating that they had been severely damaged, and the square-faced man stumbled back in an unsteady manner before throwing up a mouthful of blood.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and in the meantime, the purple devilish patterns on the elderly man's body had begun glowing brightly. Furthermore, a giant purplish-black devilish shadow with three heads and six arms had appeared behind him. It was impossible to make out the shadow's facial features, and the only features clearly visible were its six sinister purple eyes.

The devilish shadow threw its head back and let loose a thunderous roar, then thrust its six giant palms forward at once.

A burst of rumbling instantly rang out from the space around Han Li, following which the entire space began to collapse. Six giant inky-black vortexes then appeared out of thin air, surrounding him from all directions to ensure that he couldn't escape.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and silver lightning flashed from his body once again as he attempted to create another lightning teleportation array.

However, right at this moment, countless streaks of black light rapidly shot out of the black vortexes, then wound themselves tightly around Han Li's body.

In the face of the streaks of black light, all of the silver lightning and the protective spiritual light around Han Li's body completely faded, and even the circulation of immortal spiritual power within his body had become very slow and sluggish.

"This is what you get for meddling with Azure Feather Island!"

A cold gleam flashed through the elderly man's eyes as he made a string of hand seals, and a huge pillar of purplish-black devilish flames erupted out of the mouth of the giant devilish shadow, then transformed into a purplish-black spear of fire.

The spear shot through the air like lightning before plunging viciously into Han Li's, then exploded violently amid an eruption of dazzling light and scorching flames.

A concerned look appeared on Lu Yuqing's face as she saw this from afar, but she chose not to flee the scene.

In contrast, both of the azure-robed cultivators were quite relieved to see that the attack had landed, but in the next instant, both of their expressions changed drastically.

As the dust settled, it was revealed that Han Li's chest remained completely unharmed, and his entire body was encompassed within a faint membrane of light that kept the black light at bay.

An incredulous look appeared on the elderly man's face, and he was able to immediately identify what this light membrane was, much to his horror and dismay.

"Run! We're no match for him!" the square-faced man yelled in a panicked voice.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as a seven-star constellation appeared on his lower abdomen, and a burst of terrifying power erupted out of his body, causing the nearby space to rumble and shudder.

The streaks of black light around him were instantly snapped, and the six black vortexes vanished as well.

The elderly man had only just turned around to flee when the six arms of his devilish projection abruptly exploded without any warning, and the devilish projection itself also quickly dissipated moments later.

An unnatural flush appeared on the elderly man's face, and he gave a muffled groan as he stumbled unsteadily almost losing his footing in the process.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared directly behind him before throwing a vicious punch.

A suit of black devilish armor appeared over the elderly man's body amid a flash of black light, and a layer of complex array patterns was engraved onto the surface of the suit of armor, which was giving off a faint metallic sheen.

At the same time, a burst of black light appeared in his hand, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, a cold harrumph suddenly rang out beside his ears.

He immediately felt as if a sharp spike had been driven viciously into his consciousness, and he let loose an agonized howl as the black light in his hand instantly faded.

Meanwhile, Han Li's fist sped through the air before striking the suit of black devilish armor, tearing through it with ease before emerging on the other side straight through the elderly man's chest.

The elderly man's body instantly exploded into a vast cloud of blood mist amid a dull thump, and not even his nascent soul was able to escape before it was destroyed by a burst of tremendous power.

Chapter 147: Intercepting the Spoils

At the same time, a streak of azure light was flying rapidly into the distance, vanishing in the blink of an eye.

Inside the streak of light was the square-faced man, who was fleeing with a panicked look on his face.

Han Li hadn't even withdrawn his fist before he vanished on the spot amid a flash of silver lightning.

Several resounding booms rang out from the horizon, and dazzling silver light flashed several times in the distance before peace and quiet returned. The streak of crimson light had also vanished, indicating that the square-faced man had been disposed of as well.

Meanwhile, Lu Yuqing was looking on with her eyes wide with shock, seemingly still yet to comprehend just how quickly and drastically the situation had turned.

A few seconds later, a streak of azure light returned, then faded to reveal Han Li.

Lu Yuqing cast her gaze toward the rather unremarkable-looking Han Li with a complex look on her face, and it seemed that she didn't know what to say.

"Let's go, Young Mistress Lu. Your father is waiting for you," Han Li said.

Lu Yuqing turned her gaze to Red Moon Island in silence, and it seemed that she was still a little reluctant to leave.

"Those two may not be the only Azure Feather Island cultivators in this area. As for the matter regarding your brother, I'm sure your father will look into it," Han Li said.

"How do you know about that?" Lu Yuqing asked with a surprised expression.

"Your father already told us everything before we set off to search for you," Han Li explained.

"We?" Lu Yuqing asked.

"Aside from myself, there are around a dozen other fellow daoists searching for you. I was just lucky that I happened to be nearby. Your father has gone to great lengths to ensure your safe return," Han Li explained.

"Alright, I'll go back with you," Lu Yuqing sighed in a slightly dejected manner.

……

In the sky above the boundless sea, two streaks of light were flying through the air alongside one another at an incredible speed, covering hundreds of kilometers in an instant.

Within the two streaks of light were a man and a woman, and they were none other than Han Li and Lu Yuqing.

Lu Yuqing's face was slightly pale, and she took a glance at Han Li, who was flying slightly ahead of her, seemingly wanting to say something.

Han Li's gaze remained fixed on the sky ahead, but he consoled, "Rest assured, we'll be reaching One Pine Island soon, and there's a teleportation array on the island that'll take us to a place near Black Wind Island."

"Thank you, Brother Liu," Lu Yuqing replied with a nod.

She had sustained some injuries earlier, and even though she had taken some pills to improve her condition, the past few days of rigorous travel had taken a toll on her.

Han Li merely waved a hand in response and didn't say anything.

He didn't have any suitable flying treasures that could carry both of them, so he had been traveling below his top speed this entire time in order to ensure that Lu Yaqing could keep up.

A short while later, right as the two of them were flying over a cluster of islands, Han Li's brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he drew to a halt as he said, "Hold on a second."

Lu Yuqing was rather taken aback by this sudden stop, and she was just about to ask a question when she spotted three streaks of light hurtling rapidly toward them from the distant sky.

An alarmed look appeared on her face, but she could see that Han Li was still quite calm and composed, and that instilled within her a sense of confidence and security.

The three streaks of light drew to a halt several thousand feet away, then faded to reveal two men and a woman.

The trio was led by a burly man, followed by a young woman with a black veil over her face, and a thin young man.

It was none other than the Three Scourges of Splendid Mountain.

An elated look appeared on the First Scourge's face at the sight of Lu Yuqing, and he smiled as he said, "Thanks for your hard work, Fellow Daoist. You can hand over Young Mistress Lu to us now, and we'll make sure to keep her safe the rest of the way back to Black Wind Island."

"What's the meaning of this?" Han Li asked.

"If you know what's good for you, then you won't ask any questions. While we're still in a good and merciful mood, piss off!" the thin young man chuckled.

"I understand that the reward for the mission is very alluring, but it won't do you any good if you're dead," the young woman said in a meaningful voice.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and he said in a cold voice, "I am the one who found Young Mistress Lu. Don't you think you're going too far here?"

A cold look appeared on the First Scourge's face, and he chuckled, "Now that you mention it, you're right. In that case, you can stay here, and we'll send you on your way."

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but Lu Yuqing decided to step forward after a moment of hesitation.

"There's no need to escalate this into a physical conflict. There may still be unforeseen danger on the rest of the way back to Black Wind City, so why don't you all work together? Once we get back, I'll be sure to ask my father to reward all of you equally," Lu Yuqing said.

A hesitant look appeared on the First Scourge's face upon hearing this, and he seemed to be considering this option.

The veiled young woman remained silent, and it was impossible to tell what she was thinking.

Right as Lu Yaqing thought that a peaceful resolution could be reached, a sly look suddenly appeared on the thin young man's face as he said, "The promised reward is quite a handsome one, but it's still a finite reward, so the fewer people we have to share it with, the better."

A hint of killing intent flashed through the First Scourge's eyes upon hearing this.

Han Li stroked his chin with a contemplative look on his face.

Right at this moment, Lu Yuqing's voice rang out in Han Li's mind. "Brother Liu, it seems like the safest course of action for you is to leave for now. Once I return to Black Wind Island, I'll inform my father of what happened."

"The mission released by Island Master Lu only requires your safe return, there's no requirement on who takes you back to him, so even if they kill me and take you back to Black Wind Island, they'll have completed the mission. Besides, your father isn't going to punish them for the sake of a stranger like me," Han Li said as he turned to Lu Yuqing with a faint smile.

Lu Yuqing was stumped upon hearing this, and it was clear that she hadn't considered this.

"Besides, they never intended to let me go to begin with, isn't that right?" Han Li asked as he turned to the three scourges.

The First Scourge did away with his hesitant facade upon hearing this, and he admitted, "We didn't want to get violent in front of Young Mistress Lu, but it looks like it can't be helped."

A cold look appeared on Lu Yuqing's face upon hearing this, and she took a step forward, placing herself in front of Han Li as she declared, "I owe Brother Liu my life, so if you want to kill him, then you'll have to get through me first."

The three scourges were rather surprised to hear this, and Han Li was also slightly moved by her courageous gesture.

"I appreciate the gesture, but I don't have a habit of hiding behind women," Han Li said as he gently laid a hand onto her shoulder and stepped around from behind her.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, a burst of silver lightning erupted behind the thin young man, followed by a resounding explosion.

A net of silver lightning that was over 1,000 feet wide instantly unfurled. Countless thin arcs of lightning shot forth in all directions, while a blurry azure shadow flew out from within.

An agonized howl rang out from within the lightning, and a humanoid figure that was completely encased in black ice crystals fell out of the silver light toward the First Scourge.

The burly man and the veiled young woman were both quite alarmed to see this, clearly not expecting Han Li to be so fast and strike so decisively.

In the blink of an eye, he had already struck down the thin young man.

Lu Yuqing was greatly startled by this abrupt turn of events, and she was completely rooted to the spot. However, she then thought of the power that Han Li had displayed earlier, and she was feeling a bit more reassured.

The sound of cracking ice crystals rang out, and the thin young man reappeared. His robes were in tatters, his skin had been charred black, and there was black smoke rising up from the top of his head, presenting a very sorry sight to behold.

The man quickly swallowed a pill as he spat through gritted teeth, "Make sure you don't kill him too easily! I'm going to peel off his skin and use it for a new drum!"

He then swept a hand through the air, and a large black drum appeared in front of him amid a flash of black light.

It was a flat cylindrical drum with a layer of waxy yellow skin draped over the outside, and at first glance, there didn't appear to be anything remarkable about it, but upon closer inspection, one would discover some harrowing details.

As it turned out, there was an old and wizened face on the side of the drum. Its mouth and eye sockets were all empty, and it resembled a complete set of facial skin that had been peeled straight off someone's body.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce a black longsword, which he held in his grasp before slashing it at the thin young man.

Hundreds of dizzying black sword projections instantly appeared in the air before surging toward the thing young man like a series of crashing waves.

Right at this moment, a crisp clang rang out, and a burst of ripples that were invisible to the naked eye began to spread through the air, releasing bursts of gentle force that shattered the black sword projections one after another.

The First Scourge had positioned himself in front of the thin young man, and he was holding an antiquated black pot in one hand and a copper pestle with a strange beast head engraved on it in the other.

Meanwhile, the veiled young woman had also pulled out a white bone lute, and her fingers were gently gliding over the lute's black strings.

Chapter 148: Battling the Three Scourges

"This is not an opponent to be underestimated, so we should use that technique right away," the First Scourge said as his brows furrowed slightly.

Before the other two had a chance to reply, a burst of urgent and insistent tapping rang out, and the huge waves instantly rose up on the surface of the sea amid gusts of ferocious wind.

The clouds in the sky quickly converged, forming an inky-black cloud that cast a dark shadow over a huge area with a radius of several hundred kilometers, making it appear as if dusk had suddenly arrived.

The veiled young woman began to play her lute, and two bursts of white light suddenly appeared within the dark cloud, resembling a pair of giant pagodas that were projecting through the cloud.

Han Li looked up to find that the cloud was surging and tumbling incessantly, as if there were a gargantuan creature wreaking havoc inside.

He then turned back to take a glance at Lu Yuqing, who was also looking up at the sky with a stunned look on her face, and after a moment of contemplation, he suddenly swept a sleeve toward her, releasing a burst of azure energy that enveloped her entire body.

Before she had a chance to react, she had already been carried thousands of kilometers away by the burst of energy.

Now that Han Li didn't have to worry about Lu Yuqing, he was able to focus on the battle at hand, and he tightened his grip around the hilt of his sword before springing up into the heavens, charging directly at the three scourges.

Another crisp clang rang out in the air, and the massive dark cloud in the sky abruptly parted to open up a massive rift, as if the gate leading to the heavens had suddenly opened up.

In the next instant, a white bone blade that was several thousand feet in length came crashing down out of the dark cloud amid a flash of white light.

There were near-transparent white flames burning along the entire length of the blade, and the flames were giving off scorching heat, as well as releasing a devastatingly destructive aura.

Han Li drew to a halt, and with a flick of his wrist, he raised his sword toward the heavens before slashing it upward.

A vast expanse of black sword projections instantly took shape, stacking on top of one another to resemble a black mountain that hurtled directly toward the bone blade.

Heaven and earth rumbled and swayed violently as the mountain of sword projections was destroyed and reduced to countless fragments, while countless specks of white flames came drifting down from the heavens.

The white bone blade shuddered violently before flying back into the dark cloud, and the three scourges, who had summoned the bone blade, gave a collective muffled groan.

Meanwhile, Han Li was descending rapidly through the air, and only after falling for close to 1,000 feet was he able to steady himself.

Even after landing on the surface of the sea, the specks of white flames continued to burn resembling countless glowing white lotus flowers that basked the sea down below in a bright white radiance.

Han Li looked down at the black longsword in his hand to find that there were still white flames clinging to its blade, scorching it incessantly.

He gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and a layer of golden scales appeared over his hand before he gently rubbed his hand along the blade of the longsword.

All of the white flames were instantly wiped away like dirt and grime.

All of a sudden, the thunderous beating of a drum rang out in the air, immediately followed by the sound of a strumming lute and a tapping pot.

The dark cloud in the sky churned violently as a mountainous white bone foot descended out of the heavens, stomping down directly upon Han Li.

Han Li raised his sword while activating his Azure Essence Sword Arts, and his robes began to flap audibly around him despite the lack of wind.

He then stomped heavily down onto the air beneath him, and a burst of violent force was sent hurtling downward, causing a massive indentation that was several thousand feet in size to appear on the surface of the sea, while Han Li himself was launched into the heavens.

Gusts of ferocious wind swept through the air as a series of sword projections that resembled small mountains appeared in a radius of several kilometers around him, then began to rise up into the heavens alongside him.

Scorching white flames were burning over the giant bone foot, causing the air to crackle and pop incessantly, and the foot continued to stomp down from above, clashing violently against the rising sword projections.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the giant bone foot exploded violently, and a white bone giant that was over 10,000 feet tall stumbled out of the dark clouds before plunging into the sea, sending massive waves erupting in all directions.

The vast expanse of black sword projections was also all shattered, and they fell out of the sky alongside countless specks of white flames, causing the surrounding sea to bubble and boil, while clouds of water vapor rose up into the air.

Han Li emerged from the cloud of mist and water vapor in a flash, and the black longsword in his hand had already snapped in half, perhaps from being scorched by the white flames, or perhaps because it was unable to hold the handle the astonishing sword qi unleashed by his Azure Origin Sword Arts.

He heaved a faint sigh as he stowed the two pieces of the sword away, and he couldn't help but lament over the loss of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords again.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li suddenly opened his mouth to let loose a thunderous roar, and his muscles bulged as his body rapidly swelled in size, quickly transforming him into a giant golden ape that wasn't inferior in stature to the white bone giant.

The three scourges had already realized that Han Li was an extremely formidable opponent, and their expressions darkened even further upon seeing this. All three of them began to chant incantations, and the tempo at which they were playing their instruments had clearly sped up as well.

Under the trio's combined efforts, the bone giant swiveled around before striding over the surface of the sea, swinging a white bone saber directly at the giant golden ape.

The golden ape clenched its fists tightly and strode forward to meet the attack head-on.

The two massive figures clashed over and over again, sending countless enormous waves that were thousands of feet in height sweeping over the surface of the sea in all directions.

At this moment, Lu Yuqing was far away from the battlefield, and even though the shockwaves resulting from the clashes were too far away to reach her, she could still sense the violent surging of the world's origin qi in that direction, and she couldn't help but feel astonished.

All of a sudden, white light flashed within the eyes of the bone giant, and two incredibly thick pillars of white flames erupted forth like a pair of fiery dragons, twisting through the air as they swooped directly at the golden ape's face.

The giant ape let loose another thunderous roar as it slammed its fists down upon the pair of fiery dragons, and the latter exploded violently into a vast flurry of white flame that inundated half of the golden ape's entire body.

Despite the immense fire-resistant properties of the giant ape's fur and skin, plumes of white smoke began to rise up from its body along with a sharp and acrid charred smell.

However, the golden ape paid no heed to the white flames clinging to its body as it continued to barrel forward with ferocious might, springing high up into the air before raising its right fist and slamming it heavily down toward the bone giant's head.

The bone giant hurriedly lowered its center of gravity while raising its bone blade with both hands to shield itself, and a resounding crack rang out as the golden ape's fist struck the blade with tremendous force, snapping the blade and sending bone fragments flying in all directions.

The three scourges were controlling the bone giant collectively, and they immediately shuddered violently before throwing up a mouthful of blood in unison.

The giant ape continued to press its advantage, closing in on the bone giant while slamming its fists repeatedly into the giant's chest.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out as a series of massive cracks appeared on the bone giant's body. At the same time, bone fragments were constantly falling off its enormous frame, and it wasn't going to be able to withstand this ferocious assault for much longer.

"Activate the Heaven Incinerating Blood Flames! Hurry!" the First Scourge hurriedly yelled in an urgent voice.

He then brought a finger forcefully down onto the edge of his antiquated pot, and a section of his finger was severed before falling into the pot, which instantly began to glow red.

At the same time, the veiled young woman sliced her finger open with the string of her lute before rubbing her blood onto the lute, while the thin young man stuck a finger into the mouth of the human face on the side of his drum.

All three of them were feeding their blood essence to their respective treasures.

Right as the golden ape was about to smash open the bone giant's head, a burst of bright red light suddenly appeared behind the latter, and the bone giant's entire body took on a red hue.

The white flames that enveloped its enormous frame instantly turned red as well, as did the flames that were clinging to the giant ape's body.

A sharp burning pain spread over the golden ape's entire body, causing it to roar in agony as it reflexively stumbled back.

Layers of golden scales surfaced over its body, attempting to keep the red flames at bay, but to no avail, and the excruciating pain wasn't lessened in the slightest.

With the emergence of the red flames, the temperature in the area had been elevated to a terrifying degree, causing massive volumes of seawater to evaporate into water vapor, to the extent that the sea level in the area was falling at a discernible rate.

Right as the giant ape was overcome by the red flames, the bone giant's aura swelled drastically, and all of the cracks on its body began to heal at a rapid rate.

It extended a hand forward, and a crimson bone blade appeared out of thin air. The bone giant grabbed onto the blade, then lashed out with ferocious might.

A resounding boom rang out, and the golden ape felt as if it had been struck in the abdomen by a mountain, sending flying horizontally through the air, raising a trail of massive waves in its wake.

Before the golden ape had a chance to get up, the crimson bone giant sprang high up into the sky, then grabbed the hilt of its saber with both hands before plunging its tip directly down toward the ape's head.

The giant ape quickly rolled to the side to just barely evade the attack, then took a step back in retreat.

At the same time, a burst of radiant silver flames suddenly appeared on its shoulder, then rapidly spread over its entire body, and the silver flames completely inundated the crimson flames before beginning to devour it in a frenzy.

Immediately thereafter, the sharp cry of a bird rang out, and the silver flames around the golden ape transformed into a giant fire raven that slammed straight into the bone giant's chest with tremendous force.

Silver flames erupted in all directions, spreading over the bone giant's entire body, and before it had a chance to react, the silver flames had already formed a massive fiery cloak that enveloped its entire body.

The crimson flames on its body rapidly retreated in a desperate attempt to escape from the silver flames, but it was all in futility, and the silver flames quickly commenced their feast.

Chapter 149: The Grand Auction

"What the hell is that?"

The First Scourge's face had turned deathly pale at the sight of the silver flames, and the other two scourges were also horrified, looking as if they were about to turn and flee at any moment.

Meanwhile, the golden ape had many charred sections all over its body, but the ferocity in its eyes hadn't abated in the slightest, and seven specks of starlight appeared on its chest and abdomen as it launched a massive fist at the bone giant.

A huge golden fist projection was sent hurtling through the air before crashing into the bone giant's chest with devastating force.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as countless bone fragments were sent spraying through the air in all directions.

Only half of the bone giant's body remained, and after swaying for a moment, it collapsed into the sea in a limp and powerless manner before quickly disintegrating into nothingness.

At the same time, the instruments in the hands of the three scourges also exploded violently into three balls of white light. Powerful shockwaves that were visible to the naked eye swept through the air in all directions, causing the surrounding space to rumble and quiver incessantly.

The three scourges were throwing up blood uncontrollably as the shockwaves sent them flying back over 1,000 through the air.

Meanwhile, Han Li reverted back to his human form, and the silver fire raven flew back to him at his behest before vanishing up his sleeve in a flash.

Through their spiritual connection, Han Li could sense that the Essence Fire Raven was very excited after devouring those crimson flames, clearly having benefited immensely from the feast.

"Run!"

As soon as the First Scourge steadied himself in the air over 1,000 feet away, he immediately called out to his two companions, who flew to his side in a blind panic.

The three of them then each made a peculiar hand seal with one hand, and their other arms exploded in unison, forming a cloud of blood mist that enveloped them in an instant.

Within the cloud of blood mist, the three of them flew away as a streak of crimson light, displaying incredible speed as they did so.

Countless arcs of silver lightning instantly appeared over Han Li's entire body, and he vanished on the spot amid a rumbling thunderclap.

Close to 100,000 kilometers away, the three scourges drew to a halt, and their faces were deathly pale and still etched with shock and horror.

The three of them were just about to catch their breath and take some pills when a resounding thunderclap suddenly rang out overhead.

Thick bolts of silver lightning flashed through the, intertwining with one another to form a lightning array with a diameter in excess of 100 feet.

Han Li was standing at the center of the array with a cold look on his face.

He made a forward-grabbing motion with one hand, and the arcs of silver lightning that were lingering in the air around him instantly converged to form a silver ball of lightning over the palm of his hand, from within which thunderclaps were ringing out incessantly.

With a casual flick of his wrist, the ball of lightning descended from the heavens.

The three scourges were in complete despair as they felt the terrifying pressure descending upon them from afar.

They were severely injured and had completely depleted their energy reserves, so it was impossible for them to get away. Hence, all they could do was summon as many protective treasures as possible to try and keep the ball of lightning at bay.

A pillar of silver lightning that was as thick as a water tank came crashing down from above, swallowing up the three of them in the blink of an eye.

A thunderous explosion rang out alongside a string of bloodcurdling howls, and the Three Scourges of Splendid Mountain were completely destroyed in both body and soul in an instant.

Han Li took a glance at the spot where the three scourges had just vanished into thin air, then conjured up another lightning teleportation array and vanished from the spot.

……

Around half a month later.

A brocade-robed man with a powerful aura was seated on an ornate wooden chair in the island master's manor in Black Wind City, looking at the azure-robed man standing before him with undisguised praise glowing in his eyes.

"It's all thanks to you that my daughter was able to return safely to Black Wind Island, Fellow Daoist Liu. I promised you a reward, and it's time to deliver. What request would you like me to grant for you?" the man asked with a smile.

The azure-robed man in the room was naturally none other than Han Li, and he replied in a calm manner, "I took on this mission for the sole purpose of securing a teleportation spot that would allow me to leave the Black Wind Sea the next time the teleportation array is used."

"That's it?" Lu Jun asked as a look of disbelief appeared on his face.

"That's it," Han Li confirmed.

"Yuqing has already told me what happened while the two of you were on the back to Black Wind Island. As I'm sure you're aware, I like to surround myself with talented individuals, and I'd like you to stay here on Black Wind Island. I could even grant you one of the deputy island master positions," Lu Jun offered.

"Thank you for the kind offer, Island Master Lu, but there are certain reasons why I must leave the Black Wind Sea, so I'll have to turn down the offer," Han Li said with a hint of apology in his eyes.

Lu Jun could tell that Han Li wasn't lying, so he could only drop the matter.

"In that case, I won't force you to stay against your will. In addition to a teleportation spot, I have some other gifts that I'd like to present to you, and I hope you won't refuse this time."

He swept a hand through the air as he spoke, and a blue storage pouch flew out before coming to a rest in front of Han Li.

Han Li accepted the storage pouch, then expressed his gratitude before taking his leave.

Following his departure, Lu Yuqing emerged from the rear hall, having already changed into a set of clean clothes, and she made her way over to Lu Jun's side with a hint of disappointment in her eyes.

"Why didn't you make more of an effort to try and convince Brother Liu to stay, Father? Are you doubting my claims about his powers?" she asked.

"On the contrary, I have a feeling that he's even more powerful than what you described," Lu Jun replied with a serious look on his face.

"In that case, why did you..."

Before Lu Yuqing had a chance to finish, Lu Jun cut her off with a wave of his head.

"Someone of his power and talent is clearly unwilling to stay in our Black Wind Sea, and on top of that, I don't completely trust him, so it may not be a good thing to keep him here. Hence, this is the best outcome for all of us."

"But..."

Lu Yuqing still wanted to protest further, but she was cut off once again by Lu Jun as he said in a stern voice, "Yuqing, the current situation that our Black Wind Island is facing is far more complex than you can imagine. Your brother has already gone missing, do you know how catastrophic the consequences would've been had you not been saved by Liu Shi?"

"I'm sorry, Father," Lu Yuqing apologized in a dejected voice, and tears were beginning to well up in her eyes.

Lu Jun heaved a faint sigh as he embraced her and gently patted her should, unable to bear scolding her any further.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already flown out of Black Wind City and was returning to Mount Youyang.

Upon returning to his cave abode, he made his way straight to the backyard.

After deactivating several concealment arrays, a small medicine field was revealed.

At the very center of the medicine field was a dark purple seedling that was completely unremarkable in appearance, looking no different from the weeds that one would find on the side of the street.

However, in reality, this was actually a seedling that Han Li had painstakingly grown from the Soulbirth Flower seed that he had obtained from the Transient Guild prior to traveling to Black Wind Island.

The germination rate of the flower was very low, so even though he had purchased quite a few seeds, he was only able to sprout one of them after exhausting close to half his supply of seeds.

After checking on the flower to ensure that nothing was amiss, Han Li reactivated the concealment arrays before returning to the cave abode.

He pulled out the storage pouch that Lu Jun had given to him earlier, but instead of opening it right away, he carefully examined it with his spiritual sense.

Only after verifying that there was nothing amiss did he refine the storage pouch and remove its contents.

There were only two types of items in the storage pouch, namely a palm-sized black badge and a small pile of top-grade spirit stones.

Han Li counted the spirit stones to find that there were about 200 of them, which was a small fortune.

He casually stowed the spirit stones away, then began to carefully inspect the badge.

The badge was riddled with spirit patterns, and on one side was engraved the words "Black Wind" while the word "Teleportation" was inscribed on the other side.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this.

It had been quite a tumultuous journey, but he had finally achieved his objective.

The seasons passed by, and over three years flew past in the blink of an eye.

At this particular point in time, there was a particularly high number of cultivators in Black Wind City, particularly high-grade cultivators at or above the Body Integration Stage, and there were decorations put up all over the city, as if some type of celebration were taking place.

The centenary Black Wind Island grand auction was about to commence, and it was a major event.

All types of precious and exotic materials and ingredients, high-grade cultivation arts, and premium pills were always put up for sale during the grand auction, and there were even some special treasures that would only appear in the grand auction.

Almost all of the high-grade cultivators in the entire Black Wind Sea would gather here for the grand auction, and even some enemy islands of Black Wind Island would call a temporary truce and send people to participate in the auction.

On the summit of Mount Youyang, Han Li emerged from his cave abode, having adopted a disguise using his Transient Guild mask, transforming him into a burly man with a dark complexion and a coarse beard.

Even from his cave abode, he could clearly see the lively and bustling scenes in Black Wind City.

A faint smile appeared on his face, and he was also rather looking forward to this centenary auction.

With that in mind, he flew toward the city as a streak of azure light.

At the center of Black Wind City was a majestic golden palace that was hovering in mid-air.

The palace was roughly 1,000 feet tall, and it took up a huge area. It was entirely constructed from golden jade, and it was giving off a radiant golden glow, presenting a dazzling sight to behold.

Inscribed in majestic, flowing characters on the plaque above the main entrance of the palace were the words "Golden Cloud Pavilion".

Aside from the main entrance, each of the pavilion's other three sides also had an entrance.

Four massive golden staircases extended out of the palace, and there were occasionally streaks of light landing upon them before making their way into the Golden Cloud Pavilion.

This was the venue for the grand auction.

Chapter 150: Bidding

A streak of azure light descended onto one of the staircases outside the Golden Cloud Pavilion, then faded to reveal a burly man with a coarse beard, and it was none other than the disguised Han Li.

He took a glance at the majestic palace before him, then strode directly toward the entrance.

Many black-robed attendants were standing on either side of the entrance, tending to each and every arriving cultivator.

A black-robed attendant immediately approached Han Li with a smile as he asked, "Are you here for the grand auction, Senior?"

"What else could I possibly be here for?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly with displeasure.

"Please allow me to explain, Senior. This year's auction is a little different from the auctions of previous years," the black-robed attendant said.

"How so? Han Li asked."

"There are far more participants in this year's auction than previous years, so in order to restrict the numbers and keep out patrons who only intend to watch the auction with no intention of purchasing anything, it's been decided that each participant must issue a sum of spirit stones as an entrance fee. However, all you need to do is purchase any item during the auction, and the entrance fee will be returned to you," the black-robed attendant explained in a respectful voice.

"I see. How many spirit stones do I need to pay?" Han Li asked.

The black-robed attendant was just about to reply when a middle-aged man who appeared to have been a supervisor hurriedly arrived on the scene as he yelled, "How dare you be so insolent to this esteemed senior? Get out of here, I'll attend to this senior myself!"

Han Li took a glance at the middle-aged man to find that he was a Body Integration cultivator.

"Please don't take any offense, Senior, he's just an ignorant little brat that has no idea what he's doing. These rules only apply to regular patrons. For an esteemed True Immortal cultivator like yourself, you can go straight through the VIP passageway, and there's no need to submit an entrance fee. Please come with me, Senior," the middle-aged man said in a respectful voice.

Han Li was rather amused to hear this.

It seemed that power was paramount no matter where he went, and those with superior cultivation bases were always given preferential treatment.

Han Li gave the middle-aged man a slight nod, then made his way into the golden palace.

From the outside, the palace didn't appear to be all that remarkable, but only after stepping into the palace did he realize just how astonishingly massive it was.

The palace was split up into three levels, with the bottom one being a vast hall that resembled a giant plaza.

At the very front of the hall was an auction platform, which was still completely empty at this moment.

There were countless seats positioned around the hall, forming a series of tiered stands, and most of the seats were already occupied, giving the area a rather rowdy and and crowded atmosphere.

"These seat are prepared for the ordinary cultivators. Please come with me to the VIP area on the second floor, Senior," the middle-aged man said as he led Han Li up the staircase to the second floor.

There were several hundred wide and spacious seats on the second floor, with large gaps between the seats. There was a tea table beside each seat, upon which were placed some fruits and spirit tea.

Many of these seats had been occupied as well, and all of the people on the second floor were True Immortal cultivators, several of which Han Li recalled seeing at the island master's manor a few years ago.

Han Li was led to a seat by the middle-aged man, and there was a very good view from this position, allowing him to clearly see the auction platform down below, granting all those on the second floor a sense of superiority over those in the hall below.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned his gaze toward the third floor as he asked, "Who are the ones up there?"

On the third floor was a series of independent rooms that had restrictions placed upon them, making it impossible to see into the rooms from the outside, and it was clear that they were reserved for guests of even higher prestige than the ones on the second floor.

Han Li wasn't disgruntled by the fact that he hadn't been invited to the third floor, he was merely curious.

"The third floor is reserved for all of the island masters," the middle-aged man explained.

Han Li nodded in response, then withdrew his gaze and didn't say anything further.

The middle-aged man was rather busy, and he called over a beautiful female attendant to tend to Han Li before excusing himself.

Han Li wasn't bothered by this at all, and he sat in silence, waiting for the auction to begin.

Time slowly passed by, and it didn't take long before the hall on the first floor was at full capacity, and there were barely any available seats on the second floor, either.

Over two hours later, three loud gong strikes rang out, reverberating throughout the palace.

The rowdy venue immediately fell silent, and an elderly man with a white beard and a rosy complexion made his way onto the auction platform. It appeared that he was the auctioneer.

"That's Master Wen!"

A flurry of quiet chatter rang out within the hall, and Han Li's expression changed slightly as he realized that this elderly man was a guest elder of Black Wind Island and only one of three Earthly Pill Masters on the island.

"Thank you for attending our centenary grand auction. I am extremely honored to be serving as your auctioneer today," the elderly man declared in a boisterous voice that echoed throughout the entire venue.

As soon as he began speaking, all of the chatter immediately died down, and the venue became extremely quiet.

"There are lots of familiar faces here, and of course, there are also some friends who are only attending the auction for the first time, so I'll have to lay out some rules for the auction. All items are sold with top-grade spirit stones as the unit of currency, and if you don't have enough spirit stones, you can use immortal origin stones instead at an exchange rate of one immortal origin stone to 100 top-grade spirit stones.

“Alternatively, you can submit items in exchange for spirit stones, and the value of those items will be appraised by these three here," Wen Hua said.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a trio of cultivators drifted their way onto the auction platform, consisting of a white-haired elderly man in a gray robe, a muscular man in a short blue robe, and an elegant middle-aged woman, all of whom were at the True Immortal Stage.

The three of them made their way over to a long table beside the auction platform before taking a seat.

"I'm sure many of you recognize these three fellow daoists. As elders of the Eternal Prosperity Trading House, the Dark Moon Trading House, and the Taibai Trading House, they have a vast wealth of knowledge and experience, and they'll be sure to appraise all items without any bias, so you can all rest assured.

“In order to ensure the safety of our attendees, fighting is strictly prohibited in Black Wind City, and anyone caught engaging in battle will be punished. Alright, that's enough from me. Without further ado, let the auction begin!" Wen Hua declared as he swept a sleeve through the air.

A muscular man in black carried a giant pristine white box onto the platform, then opened it to reveal a red crystal that was around the size of a human head. There were flame-like patterns on the crystal's surface, and even from several thousand feet away, one could still sense the astonishing fire-attribute spiritual power fluctuations emanating from the crystal.

"This is a piece of high-grade Fire Pattern Bright Jade, an exceptional spirit material for refining top-tier spirit treasures. The base price is 20 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least one top-grade spirit stone," Wen Hua declared.

"20 top-grade spirit stones!"

"21!"

"25!"

……

As soon as the piece of Flame Pattern Bright Jade was revealed, many people's eyes instantly lit up, and a bidding war quickly began.

Han Li was seated in his chair, watching the unfolding scene down below with a calm expression.

Flame Pattern Bright Jade was indeed a great material, but it was still not enough to catch his eye.

The bidding war continued, and the price quickly rose to 50 top-grade spirit stones, upon which the bidding war finally ceased.

"Sold for 50 top-grade spirit stones!" Wen Hua declared with a wide smile.

He wasn't expecting the first auction item to be sold for such a high price, and this was a very good sign for things to come.

Shortly thereafter, the second auction item was also brought onto the platform, and it was a 30,000-year-old spirit herb, which also went on to sell for a high price.

Time slowly passed by, and one auction item was brought on after another, consisting of all types of precious materials, pills, and spirit treasures, but they had clearly all been prepared for the Body Integration and Grand Ascension cultivators on the first floor.

Han Li was looking on in a detached manner, and up to this point, very few of the True Immortal cultivators on the second floor had cast any bids.

Several hours quickly passed by, and the prices of the auction items were gradually rising. Some extremely precious treasures were beginning to appear, including Divine Spirit Treasures, pills and treasures to be used during tribulation transcendence, and some pills that aided one in breaking through bottlenecks. At this point, the True Immortal cultivators on the second floor were finally beginning to cast bids on a semi-regular basis.

Shortly thereafter, another auction item was carried onto the stage, and it was a huge piece of jade that was dark red in color, and a series of blood-red patterns could be seen on its surface, forming the image of a fire phoenix. Furthermore, the item was giving off potent fire law fluctuations.

Wen Hua's gaze slowly roamed over the auction attendees, then settled on the piece of jade as he introduced, "The next item is this piece of Phoenix Blood Fire Jade, which was formed by the blood essence of a late-True Immortal Stage fire phoenix true spirit following its demise. It contains the power of fire laws, and it's an exceptional primary material for refining Acquired Immortal Treasures.

“The base price is 200 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least 10 top-grade spirit stones."

This piece of Phoenix Blood Fire Jade contained a remarkable amount of power of laws, and even Han Li was tempted to make a bid for it. However, he didn't have a particularly large stash of spirit stones at his disposal, so after some contemplation, he decided against making any bids.

"210!"

"240!"

"280!"

"300!"

There were many people interested in the piece of Phoenix Blood Fire Jade, but most of the bidders were True Immortal cultivators on the second floor. Even if those on the first floor wanted to get their hands on this precious material, the price was simply too steep for them.

The price for the Phoenix Blood Fire Jade was quickly bid up to 450 top-grade spirit stones, a bid that had been made by a bald red-robed man on the second floor.

With the submission of this bid, the second floor fell silent as well, and no further bids were made, much to the red-robed man's elation.

"500!"

Right at this moment, a bid was made by someone in one of the booths on the third floor. Judging from the voice of the bidder, it seemed to have been a woman, and she had raised the price by 50 top-grade spirit stones in one go.

The red-robed man faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a hint of anger flashed through his eyes, but after some contemplation, he slowly lowered his hand and didn't make any further bids.

"Sold for 500 top-grade spirit stones!" Wen Hua declared with an elated expression.

The piece of Phoenix Blood Fire Jade was quickly taken to that booth on the third floor.

Han Li took a glance in that direction before withdrawing his gaze. In his opinion, the price paid was more than the item was worth.

Chapter 151: Heavy Water Lightning Beads

The auction continued, and as the auction items increased further and further in value, the atmosphere in the venue was also becoming more fervent and electric.

At this point, the attendees on the second and third floors were the only ones still making bids, while those on the first floor could only watch the proceedings.

At this moment, there was a square jade box sitting on the auction platform, inside of which was a purple jade tome.

"The next item is a high-grade True Immortal cultivation art by the name of the Purple Heavens Lightning Arts. It's an extremely rare lightning-attribute cultivation art, and upon reaching full mastery, one would be able to open up all 36 immortal acupoints in their body, thereby progressing to the Golden Immortal Stage!

“Regarding its origins, I'm sure the story that I'm about to tell next is one that's already quite familiar to everyone. This was the exact same cultivation art that Daoist Master Purple Heavens used several million years ago to slay three late-True Immortal cultivators!" Wen Hua introduced.

This declaration immediately created a huge stir throughout the entire venue, and a few surprised voices could even be heard coming from the booths on the third floor.

Han Li's expression also changed slightly upon hearing mention of the term "immortal acupoints".

Even though he had already converted all of his spiritual power to immortal spiritual power following the recovery of his cultivation base, due to the loss of his memories and a lack of a suitable cultivation art, it could be said that in some sense, he hadn't truly begun to cultivate.

However, through some Earthly Immortal cultivation arts, he had learned that opening up these immortal acupoints was integral to the advancement of one's cultivation base, and just as Wen Hua claimed, opening up 36 immortal acupoints would allow one to progress to the Golden Immortal Stage.

However, Earthly Immortal cultivation arts placed more importance on the accumulation of the power of faith and the manifestation of law powers, so very little mention of immortal acupoints was made. It seemed that after cultivating for a sufficiently long period of time, the immortal acupoints would naturally open up, and that seemed to be the case for the Black Sea Heavy Water Tome as well.

Wen Hua was quite pleased with the crowd reaction, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he declared, "Daoist Master Purple Heavens has already been missing for over 1,000,000 years, but this cultivation art has been passed down. However, I'm obligated to inform all of you that the prerequisites required to use this cultivation art are very rigorous.

“One has to possess a top-tier lightning-attribute spiritual root, or innate lightning-attribute constitutions such as the Five Lightning Physique or the True Lightning Essence Physique. Only then will the cultivator be able to attain full mastery of this cultivation art. Without further ado, the base price for this cultivation art is 500 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least 10 top-grade spirit stones."

Many people were very tempted to participate in the bidding race for the cultivation art, given that it was of the lightning attribute, which was renowned for its power.

There were many Earthly Immortals in the Black Wind Sea, but they were outnumbered by itinerant cultivators, who needed suitable high-grade cultivation arts more than anything else.

However, many people were left disappointed after hearing the rigorous prerequisites that had to be satisfied in order to use this cultivation art, but there were still quite a few people that were interested.

Han Li was also missing a cultivation art, so he was initially tempted, but he was also left feeling disappointed after hearing about the required prerequisites.

"510!"

"530!"

"580!"

Even though Han Li wasn't bidding for the cultivation art, there were plenty of people keen to get their hands on it, and following a flurry of bids, the price was quickly raised to 700 top-grade spirit stones.

"800!"

A rather lazy voice rang out from one of the booths on the third floor, raising the price by 100 top-grade spirit stones in one go.

A middle-aged scholarly man on the second floor who had made a bid of 600 top-grade spirit stones earlier hesitated momentarily, then gritted his teeth as he declared, "850!"

"900!"

The bidder on the third floor seemed to have been rather displeased by the competition they were facing, and it was clear that their pockets were extremely deep.

Han Li couldn't help but grimace upon hearing this.

Everything that he currently owned, including the reward from Lu Jun and the spoils that he had plundered from the two Azure Feather Island cultivators and the Three Scourges of Splendid Mountain, only added up to around 1,000 top-grade spirit stones.

Prior to this, he had already instructed Mu Xue to gather information on the auction, so he knew some of the auction items that were still to come, and he had already decided on his target.

He had thought that he would have more than enough funds to secure his target auction item, but it seemed that he was mistaken. These True Immortals who had cultivated for countless millennia were truly astonishingly wealthy.

After the price was raised to 900 top-grade spirit stones, the other bidders on the second floor could only surrender, despite their clear reluctance to do so.

The sale of the Purple Heavens Lightning Arts was like the precursor to the climax of the auction, and some of the subsequent treasures weren't quite of the same caliber as the Purple Heavens Lightning Arts, but frequent bids were still made thanks to the electric atmosphere.

The auction item that was currently being presented was a dark golden hammer.

It was an octagonal hammer roughly the size of a human head, and the handle was over four feet in length. Its appearance wasn't all that remarkable, but it was giving off a vast aura, as if there were a huge mountain sitting on the stage, rather than just a hammer.

"The next item is an Acquired Immortal Treasure called the Mountain Shattering Hammer. It's forged from a combination of 10,000-year-old copper essence and Profound Golden Glacial Iron. It contains the power of metal laws, and just a single blow with this weapon can shatter mountains and split rivers!

“However, the hammer is also extremely heavy and can be quite unwieldy for some, so I'd advise careful consideration before bidding. Without further ado, the starting price is 600 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least 10 top-grade spirit stones," Wen Hua declared.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as his grip unconsciously tightened around the armrests of his chair.

This was the exact item that he was targeting.

He didn't know what perils he was going to encounter during his journey to search for his lost treasures, and he was desperately in need of some powerful treasures to use along the way.

Even though he was unable to draw upon the power of metal laws in the Mountain Shattering Hammer, it was undoubtedly a very suitable weapon for him as a Profound Immortal.

"610!"

"630!"

"660!"

Despite Wen Hua's warning, there were still many people willing to cast bids for the Mountain Shattering Hammer, and before Han Li even had a chance to place a single bid, the price had already soared to 700 top-grade spirit stones.

"900!" Han Li declared, raising the price by 200 in one go.

If he allowed the price to continue to rise over small increments, things could quickly get out of hand, so he had to nip the bidding in the bud.

Everyone around him immediately turned to him with stunned expressions.

"1,000!"

A voice rang out from the third floor. The voice seemed to have belonged to an elderly man, and he hadn't cast any bids on any other auction items prior to this.

A dark look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Aside from spirit stones, he had prepared some other treasures as well, with the most important one being that Soulbirth Flower, which he had already matured to 30,000 years old, so it could definitely fetch a handsome price.

"1,200!"

Before Han Li had a chance to make another bid, yet another 200 top-grade spirits stones were added to the bidding price, and the bid had been made by the owner of the lazy voice from earlier.

"1,500!"

The same elderly voice rang out once again, raising the price by another 300.

"1,800!"

The owner of the lazy voice wasn't backing down in the slightest.

Not only were the tens of thousands of cultivators on the first floor stunned by how quickly the price was rising, even those on the second floor couldn't help but be astonished by the wealth of the pair of competing bidders on the third floor.

Han Li could only shake his head with a wry smile.

The bidding war continued, and the price was quickly raised to over 2,000 top-grade spirit stones. Ultimately, the owner of the elderly voice secured the item for a price of 2,300 spirit stones.

Close to half a day passed by in the blink of an eye, and at this point, the auction was nearing its conclusion.

All of the most precious auction items were being brought onto the stage one after another, including materials that contained law powers, high-grade Earthly Immortal cultivation arts, immortal herbs, some exotic beasts, and even the egg of a Nine-headed Frost Dragon.

The Nine-headed Frost Dragon was a true spirit with the innate ability to wield the power of water laws, and upon reaching full maturity, its powers would rival those of a mid-True Immortal cultivator, so it was far more formidable than any beast that Han Li had ever encountered.

To one's surprise, a fierce bidding war immediately ensued, and in the end, the egg was purchased by someone on the third floor for over 2,000 top-grade spirit stones.

These were the true treasures of the auction.

At this point, even though the ordinary cultivators on the first floor could only sit and watch, they were still thoroughly enthused by the bidding wars they were witnessing, and many of the people on the second floor were also beginning to come to terms with the fact that they were also out of the running.

Han Li was starting to grow a little disinterested, despite the lively and bustling scenes transpiring before him.

None of these items were things that he needed. There were powerful spirit treasures presented, including even a Profound Heavenly Treasure, but none of them suited him, so he didn't make any bids.

"The next items are three Heavy Water Lightning Beads. This treasure was refined using level three heavy water by a cultivator with exceptional mastery over the laws of water. Even though it's a disposable treasure, it's extremely powerful, and even a mid-True Immortal cultivator could be prone to sustaining severe injuries if they were struck by one of these lightning beads head-on."

Three blue jade boxes were brought onto the stage as Wen Hua was speaking, and each one contained a longan-sized black bead, which appeared to be completely unremarkable aside from some black mist drifting around them.

"The starting price for these three Heavy Water Lightning Beads is 500 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least 10 top-grade spirit stones," Wen Hua declared.

Many of the cultivators in the venue were very excited after hearing Wen Hua's description of the beads.

They were astonishingly expensive considering they were disposable treasures, but they were definitely worth buying if they really were capable of severely injuring even mid-True Immortal cultivators.

Han Li was also rather tempted by the item as he stroked the True Water Pouch strapped to his waist.

While was he contemplating how to proceed, the bidding had already begun, and it didn't take long before the price was raised to 700 top-grade spirit stones.

"750!" Han Li finally made a bid.

This was already quite a steep price, and some of the bidders immediately backed out of the bidding war.

"760!" Another bid was cast by a red-haired young man not far away from Han Li.

Han Li took a glance at the young man, then made another bid without any hesitation. "800!"

The young man hesitated momentarily, then decided against making any further bids.

"850!" This time, the bidder was a bald man on the second floor.

"900!" Han Li immediately countered.

"1,000!"

The bald man took a glance in Han Li's direction as a cold smile appeared on his face.

During the bidding for the Mountain Shattering Hammer earlier, he had been observing the bidders to try and gauge the depths of their pockets, and Han Li was naturally one of the people that he had been observing.

Chapter 152: First Glimpse of a Dao Pill

At this point in the bidding, everyone had already fallen silent. It wasn't that no one could afford this price, it was just that the three Heavy Water Lightning Beads simply didn't seem worth such a steep price to them.

After all, they were disposable treasures, and a sum of 1,000 top-grade spirit stones was potentially enough to purchase a low-quality Acquired Immortal Treasure.

Hence, everyone was merely watching Han Li and the bald man in silence, interested in seeing how far they were willing to go.

Of course, this was an extremely welcome sight for the auctioneer, Wen Hua.

The higher the final selling prices of the auction items, the higher his commission would be, and his reputation as an auctioneer would also be enhanced.

"1,000 top-grade spirit stones going once! Are there any more bidders?" Even though this was a question that appeared to have been directed at everyone, Wen Hua was looking straight at Han Li.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he sat in silence, and a triumphant look appeared in the bald man's eyes upon seeing this before he looked away in a casual manner.

No further bids were made, and as Wen Hua declared that the price of 1,000 top-grade spirit stones was going twice, the triumph in the bald man's eyes became even more pronounced.

Right as Wen Hua was about to finalize the sale, Han Li suddenly interjected, "I don't have enough spirit stones on me, but I have something I would like to have appraised."

This declaration created quite a stir, and the bald man also faltered slightly before a derisive sneer appeared on his face.

Meanwhile, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a rectangular jade box, which he handed to the female attendant beside him.

The attendant hurriedly took the jade box from Han Li, then rushed over to the table beside the auction platform under the scrutiny of tens of thousands of people before setting the box down onto the table.

The blue-robed man and the middle-aged woman weren't even looking at the box, clearly displaying no interest in what Han Li was offering.

At this point in the auction, they had already appraised countless treasures, and the vast majority of them were quite mediocre, with the most valuable one being a Sea Soul Rock that contained a wisp of water law powers, but even that item was only appraised to be worth 480 top-grade spirit stones.

With the other two appraisers showing a complete lack of interest, it was left to the grey-robed elderly man to appraise the item, and he gently opened the box, upon which a surprised look immediately appeared on his face.

He took a glance in Han Li's direction, then passed the jade box to the blue-robed man beside him.

The blue-robed man had witnessed the change in the elderly man's expression, and a hint of intrigue appeared in his eyes as he took a glance at the item in the box as well. A similar look of surprise immediately appeared on his face, and he passed the box to the middle-aged woman, who displayed the same reaction as the other two appraisers.

The three of them then held a discussion through voice transmission, and the gray-robed elderly man turned to Han Li as he said, "We have appraised this item to be worth 1,000 top-grade spirit stones. Is that a satisfactory price for you, Fellow Daoist?"

The smile on the bald man's face instantly stiffened in the wake of this declaration, and a flurry of chatter immediately rang out.

"What?"

"Did I mishear him? What could possibly be worth 1,000 top-grade spirit stones?"

"Could it be an Acquired Immortal Treasure? It doesn't look like something like that would fit in such a small box!"

"Could it be some type of pill?"

……

According to the rules of the auction, the appraisers had no obligation to reveal to everyone what the items that they appraised were. Hence, everyone was left to speculate about what could possibly have been in the box.

Han Li contemplated this price for a moment, then gave the gray-robed elderly man a nod to indicate that he accepted the offer, following which he immediately placed a bid of 1,100 top-grade spirit stones.

The box contained the Soulbirth Flower that he had matured to 30,000 years of age, and it would've definitely been an extremely sought-after item in the Black Wind Sea. Hence, he was actually not very pleased with this price, but he was in need of spirit stones, and with the Heaven Controlling Vial, it hadn't been all that difficult for him to nurture the flower, so he decided to accept the price after some thought.

After some hesitation, the bald man placed another bid as well. "1,150!"

"1,200!"

"1,300!"

"1,500!"

The bald man hesitated momentarily, then gave a cold harrumph as he leaned back against his chair with his arms crossed, bowing out of the bidding war.

"Sold for 1,500 spirit stones!" Wen Hua immediately declared with an elated expression.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li was approached by a young woman in black, who asked, "Would you like to finalize the transaction now or wait until the end of the auction, Senior? If you want to finalize the transaction now, I'll have to ask you to come to the rear hall with me."

"I'll do it now," Han Li replied, then rose to his feet and followed the woman toward the rear hall.

Seated inside one of the booths on the third floor were Lu Jun and Lu Yuqing, and the latter's gaze fell upon Han Li through the booth, upon which her brows furrowed slightly.

"What is it, Yuqing?" Lu Jun asked.

"For some reason, that man seems a bit familiar to me," Lu Yuqing replied as she cocked her head to the side in a contemplative manner.

"Have you met him before?" Lu Jun followed her gaze and took a glance at Han Li, who just so happened to making his way toward the rear hall.

"Maybe it's just my imagination," Lu Yuqing replied with a shake of her head, ridding herself of that train of thought.

The auction continued, and her gaze was immediately drawn to the next auction item.

Meanwhile, inside the rear hall, a black-robed elderly man was seated with his legs crossed, and there was a rectangular jade box placed beside him.

"Please take a seat, Fellow Daoist," the elderly man said with a warm smile as he rose to his feet and cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li sat down across from the elderly man, then immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release a small pile of precisely 500 top-grade spirit stones onto the table.

"I see you like to do things quickly, Fellow Daoist," the black-robed elderly man chuckled, and with a sweep of his sleeve, three jade boxes appeared on the table.

Han Li removed the lids of the jade boxes with a sweep of his own sleeve to examine the three Heavy Water Lightning Beads for verification, following which he gave a pleased nod.

With the transaction complete, he gave the elderly man a nod, then rose to his feet to depart.

"Please wait a moment, Fellow Daoist," the black-robed elderly man hurriedly called out as he also rose to his feet.

"Can I help you?" Han Li asked.

"I have been requested by someone to ask if you have any more Soulbirth Flowers that you'd like to sell. It only has to be above 20,000 years of age, and of course, we'll be sure to offer you a satisfactory price," the black-robed elderly man said.

"If I had more Soulbirth Flowers, I would've already brought them out earlier in the auction instead of watching all those treasures slip away from right under my nose," Han Li replied in a rather self-deprecating manner. "I only managed to obtain this one by chance."

A hint of disappointment appeared on the elderly man's face upon hearing this.

With that, Han Li turned to leave once again, only to suddenly turn back around as he said, "Come to think of it, I also have something I'd like to ask you, Fellow Daoist. Do you know these Heavy Water Lightning Beads were refined by?"

The elderly man faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "These beads were also purchased by our auction house by chance, and we don't know who they were refined by. However, I've heard that they were refined by a powerful being outside of the Black Wind Sea."

Han Li nodded in response, then made his way out of the rear hall and returned to his seat in the auction venue.

His return naturally attracted a great deal of attention and scrutiny, but he paid those prying eyes no heed.

"The next item is a pair of horns from the late-True Immortal Stage spirit beast, the Sky Splitting Roar. The horns have been perfectly preserved with no loss of spiritual nature whatsoever. The base price is 600 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least 10 top-grade spirit stones."

With a wave of Wen Hua's hand, a pair of glowing purple horns appeared on the stage, emanating dazzling purple radiance.

All of the cultivators in the hall were extremely excited to see this, and a fierce bidding war immediately commenced.

Han Li naturally had no intention of taking part, but he continued to remain in the venue and watch the auction.

Close to three hours later.

"And now, for the moment everyone has been waiting for! The next item will be the final item of our grand auction!" Wen Hua declared in an excited voice as he placed an item onto the auction platform.

It was a red wooden box that was extremely tightly sealed with a bunch of spirit talismans plastered onto its surface.

Even so, the world's origin qi around the box was still fluctuating slightly as rippling light that resembled surging flames appeared around it.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

There were other cultivators who couldn't wait to see what was in the box, and they released their spiritual sense to try and inspect the box's contents, only to be thwarted by the spirit talismans on the box.

Wen Hu wasn't bothered at all by this, and his smile remained unchanged as he chanted an incantation while casting a series of incantation seals through the air.

The spirit talismans on the box flew off one after another, and upon the removal of the final talisman, the wooden box sprang open on its own to reveal a crimson pill.

The pill was only around the size of a thumbnail, and it was giving off fiery red light that was proliferating outward in rings around it.

There was an extremely eye-catching crimson line on the surface of the pill, and upon closer inspection, one would find that it was formed by countless runes, giving it an extremely profound and mystical appearance.

Countless stunned voices rang out one after another, and the entire hall quickly erupted into a frenzy.

"Your eyes do not deceive you, fellow daoists. What you're looking at is a dao pill, renowned as the kings of all pills!" Wen Hua declared, and there was a hint of genuine excitement in his voice.

As an Earthly Pill Master, his pursuit and longing for improvement in the art of pill refinement was something that the average person simply couldn't comprehend.

"I'm sure all of you are aware of just how valuable dao pills are, so I won't say too much about it here. This is a first-tier fire-attribute dao pill. If any of you are using fire-attribute cultivation arts, there's a chance that you'll be able to master the laws of fire using this dao pill! The base price is 2,000 top-grade spirit stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least 100 top-grade spirit stones!" Wen Hua declared, promptly commencing the bidding.

Chapter 153: Perceiving the Lightning Beads

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing the base price of 2,000 top-grade spirit stones.

With such an astronomically high starting price, there was no way he would be able to secure it with his wealth, or lack thereof.

After Wen Hua announced the commencement of the bidding, most of the people in the hall fell silent and began to look around with anticipation in their eyes. Everyone wanted to see who would ultimately lay claim to this dao pill.

"2,000!"

Finally, the brief silence was broken by someone from a booth in the southeastern corner of the third floor, and the voice sounded as if it belonged to an elderly man.

Cultivators from all of the most powerful forces on in the Black Wind Sea were gathered here for the auction, so there was no shortage of people with immense wealth at their disposal and a keen interest in this dao pill.

"2,200!"

"2,500!"

……

All of the bidders were from the third-floor booths with no exceptions.

Within no more than half a minute, seven or eight rounds of bidding had already concluded, and the price of the dao pill had been bid up to over 3,000 top-grade spirit stones.

"4,000!"

A female voice suddenly rang out, and once again, it was from one of the booths on the third floor. Everyone looked on in astonishment as the flurry of bids drew to a temporary halt.

The entire auction venue had fallen silent once again.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this voice, and he seemed to recall that this was the same person who had secured that piece of Phoenix Blood Fire Jade from earlier.

"4,200!" Another bid rang out from the third floor.

The female voice immediately retaliated with an astonishingly high bid. "5,000!"

Everyone else was silenced for a moment by this extraordinary bid, only to erupt into a raucous frenzy, and everyone focused their gaze on that booth, trying to see what the person inside looked like.

"5,000 top-grade spirit stones going once! 5,000 spirit stones going twice! If anyone's still interested, you better place your bids now! If you miss this opportunity, another one may not arise even in the next 1,000 years! And... Sold for 5,000 top-grade spirit stones! Congratulations to this fellow daoist!"

With that declaration, the dao pill was sold to the mysterious cultivator on the third floor, and that also spelled the conclusion of the Black Wind Sea's centenary auction.

Wen Hua thanked everyone for coming, then declared the conclusion of the auction.

Han Li was mixed in the crowd as he slowly made his way out of the palace.

Everyone around him was still spiritedly discussing everything they had seen during the auction, particularly that dao pill at the end, which was undoubtedly going to be talked about for a long time to come.

Looking at the excitement on the faces of the people around him, Han Li developed a better idea of just how rare and precious dao pills were.

Upon returning to his temporary cave abode, Han Li immediately activated all of the restrictions inside before making his way into the secret chamber.

After taking a seat in the secret chamber, he flipped a hand over to summon the three Heavy Water Lightning Bead, then picked up one of them between his thumb and index finger for a close examination.

The bead was completely unremarkable in appearance and only around the size of a longan. There were wisps of black mist that lingered perpetually over its surface, and it wasn't giving off any special aura at all, making it appear quite innocuous.

However, given how much people had been willing to bid for the beads during the auction, he was confident that the power contained within them had to be far more potent than he could imagine.

Of course, he hadn't paid such a steep price for the beads just for their destructive power. Instead, he wanted to see if he could study them to find new ways to utilize heavy water.

After all, even though he was able to use heavy water, if he didn't know how to wield it, then it wouldn't even be as powerful as an ordinary spirit treasure in his hands.

He placed the bead onto palm, then closed his fingers over it, carefully massaging it to feel the patterns on its surface.

Only after a long while did he open his hand again, and a peculiar look had appeared on his face.

The material of the Heavy Water Lightning Bead was identical to the heavy water refined by his Earthly Deity Avatar, and he was able to feel some tiny marks on its surface that were as thin as human hairs, connecting together to form a series of strange patterns.

Even with his wealth of knowledge and experience, he wasn't able to make heads or tails of the patterns.

After a moment of contemplation, he closed his eyes, and a translucent thread shot out of his glabella, entering the black mist before venturing into the bead.

It was as if there were an entire world contained within the bead, and initially, all he could see was inky darkness. However, upon closer inspection, he spotted specks of black light, as well as wisps of azure and purple lightning that were flashing incessantly.

At the same time, he could feel the traces of law powers within the bead.

These three types of power were combined together to create a very harmonious equilibrium, and they were all connected while also keeping one another in check, like a ferocious tiger that was biding its time, waiting to be let loose from its cage so that it could unleash its wrath.

Close to two hours passed by, and Han Li finally reopened his eyes.

He shook his head as he heaved a faint sigh, then stowed the three Heavy Water Lightning Beads away before exiting the cave abode. After that, he flew in a certain direction as a streak of azure light, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

……

In a completely uninhabited area of the sea tens of thousands of kilometers away from Black Wind Island.

A streak of azure light arrived in a flash, then faded to reveal Han Li.

He released his spiritual sense to encompass the entire surrounding region in a radius of thousands of kilometers in the blink of an eye, carefully inspecting his surroundings.

Only after ensuring that there were no other cultivators in the area did he flip a hand over to produce one of the Heavy Water Lightning Beads.

Azure light flashed over his palm, and a wisp of immortal spiritual power was injected into the bead.

The surface of the bead immediately lit up with crimson light, and all of the spirit patterns engraved upon it also flashed momentarily before dimming again.

Han Li casually tossed the bead forward, and it shot forth rapidly through the air, giving off no aura fluctuations as it traveled tens of thousands of feet in the blink of an eye.

A thunderous boom rang out as the Heavy Water Lightning Bead exploded, and a mountainous ball of black light appeared with hundreds of bolts of azure and purple lightning that were over 1,000 feet in length surging through the air in all directions. They resembled whips of a lightning god, flashing through the surrounding space while giving off formidable law fluctuations.

The space that was struck by the bolts of lightning immediately began to warp and shudder violently, looking as if it were about to be torn apart.

Meanwhile, a giant crater had appeared on the surface of the sea beneath the vast ball of black light, and all of the fish and sea beasts within the crater were instantly destroyed.

In the next instant, the ball of black light also exploded into vast expanses of black radiance that swept forth in all directions.

Han Li had already conjured up his True Extreme Membrane, and blue light was flashing in his eyes as he carefully observed every single detail that arose following the explosion of the lightning bead.

The waves of black light reached him in the blink of an eye, and his pupils contracted drastically as he shot back in retreat, but it was already too late, and he wasn't able to fly very far at all before the black light caught up to him.

A sound akin to that of pitter-pattering rain falling on a banana leaf rang out, and there were countless hair-thin black needles within the black light, striking against his True Extreme Membrane .

The True Extreme Membrane flashed erratically as countless white spots appeared on its surface, and only after a long while did it return to a stable state.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this. Thankfully, the True Extreme Membrane was able to withstand the assault. Otherwise, he would've most likely already had countless tiny holes punched into his body at this point.

All of those black needles had been formed by heavy water, granting them extraordinary penetrative power, and even his body most likely wouldn't have been able to keep them at bay without any additional defenses.

The sea down below churned violently, and an enormous crater with a radius of close to 10,000 feet appeared on its surface.

Han Li spread his spiritual sense through the area, and a stunned look appeared on his face as he discovered that everything with a radius of close to 10 kilometers from the epicenter of the explosion had been pierced by the heavy water needles, killing all of the sea beasts in the area.

Given how fearsome these black needles were, Han Li imagined that even he would've sustained severe injuries had he been situated at the epicenter of the explosion.

After witnessing all of this, Han Li finally understood why the beads had triggered such a fierce bidding war during the auction.

Only after several more seconds had passed did the residual effects of the explosion begin to subside.

Han Li made sure that the aura of law powers in the air had completely faded before flying back to the epicenter of the explosion, where there was still a charred smell lingering in the air.

At this point, the crater on the surface of the sea down below had already been refilled by seawater, but there were still some unnatural wave formations in the aftermath of the explosion.

Given the price that Han Li had paid for these Heavy Water Lightning Beads, he had essentially just detonated 500 top-grade spirit stones, and if any other auction-goers had been present, they would've been stunned by such an astonishing waste.

However, Han Li was completely unfazed, and his head was slightly bowed as he contemplated what he had just seen in silence.

Only after a long while of contemplation did he murmur to himself, "It seems like the power of laws were used to forcibly seal the power of lightning into heavy water, and an injection of immortal spiritual power would be required to unleash this power. However..."

It seemed that there was something that he was unable to wrap his head around, and his voice trailed off into silence as he fell into deep thought.

Judging from the process through which the Heavy Water Lightning Bead had released its power and the final outcome, there was no way that it would've been capable of unleashing such devastating power if it had only released the power of laws and lightning stored within.

Han Li closed his eyes as he carefully replayed what he had just seen in his mind over and over again, and all of a sudden, he was struck by a flash of enlightenment.

In the instant that the Heavy Water Lightning Bead released its power, all of the spirit pattern restrictions engraved upon its surface had been activated, causing the lightning to disperse the heavy water, transforming it into countless tiny blasts of heavy water that contained the power of laws.

Anything within the area would be like a foreign object that disrupted the fragile equilibrium, causing it to be simultaneously attacked by the heavy water, the lightning, and the power of laws, which was a formidable combination that even the average True Immortal wouldn't have been able to withstand.

Even though Han Li had managed to develop a rough idea of how these beads worked, he was still left feeling rather dismayed.

In order to prevent his magic power from being contaminated by the power of faith, he had refrained from accepting the power of laws derived by his Earthly Deity Avatar, so it was impossible for him to replicate the refinement of these Heavy Water Lightning Beads.

However, this hadn't been a completely fruitless experiment. At the very least, through his observations, he had received a great deal of inspiration on how he could utilize his heavy water.

After lingering in the area for a moment longer, Han Li rose up into the air before flying into the distance.

After flying for a few hundred kilometers, he began to descend toward a nearby small coral island that was only several kilometers in radius.

Upon landing on the island, he flipped ah and over to produce the True Water Pouch was filled with heavy water.

Over the course of the past three years, he had been maturing the Soulbirth Flower with the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial while also intermittently refining crystals that contained the laws of time, helping his Earthly Deity Avatar derive more heavy water.

At this point, he had already accumulated enough heavy water to fill most of a small stream.

Chapter 154: Blaze Dragon Dao

After a brief pause, Han Li flipped a hand over, and a ball of heavy water around the size of a watermelon flowed out of the True Water Pouch, where it hovered in mid-air, enveloped by his immortal spiritual power.

The heavy water was flowing and circulating incessantly, and it didn't appear remarkable at all, but its weight was already comparable to that of a mountain that was several thousand feet tall.

He closed his eyes, and after running all of the ideas that he had developed earlier through his mind, he reopened his eyes.

He then made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a burst of silver lightning shot out of his palm, forming a silver lightning net around his hand.

After that, he thrust both palms forward, and the silver lightning net began to extend toward the ball of heavy water as if it were a living creature.

The lightning net wound itself around the ball of heavy water, and the latter immediately began to sway and quiver violently, as if it were receiving some type of powerful stimulus.

Han Li hurriedly released more of his immortal spiritual power, and with the injection of immortal spiritual power, the ball of heavy water was gradually stabilized again, but its surface was still rippling incessantly.

Han Li began to lower his other hand upon seeing this, injecting lightning into the ball of heavy water.

The tiny arcs of lightning resembled countless peerlessly sharp blades that sliced countless minuscule gashes onto the surface of the ball of heavy water, then burrowed their way deeper inside.

As more and more lightning was injected into the ball of heavy water, it began to slowly shrink, and Han Li was ecstatic to see this.

However, just that slight lapse of concentration resulted in the simultaneous explosion of the lightning and the ball of heavy water.

A burst of powerful shockwaves instantly struck him head-on, blasting him back through the air before sending him plunging into the sea.

By the time he returned to the coral island, close to half of the island had already been destroyed by the explosion, and a wry smile appeared on his face upon seeing this.

After taking a moment to adjust his robes, Han Li pulled out his True Water Pouch again and released another ball of heavy water from within.

Moments later, tiny arcs of silver lightning reappeared as well.

……

A short while later, another violent explosion rang out, and silver lightning erupted in all directions.

This time, Han Li was already prepared, so he wasn't sent flying, but his brows were tightly furrowed.

He made a sweeping motion with his hand, and wisps of immortal spiritual power were released, gathering the tiny particles of heavy water that had been scattered through the air.

This heavy water had been extremely difficult to come by, and he didn't want to waste any of it.

Three days and three nights passed by in the blink of an eye.

This morning, Han Li suddenly rose up from the island, hovering high up in the sky.

His robes were flapping around him amid the sea breeze, and there was a hint of weariness in his eyes, but his eyes were glowing brightly, much like the rising sun on the horizon.

In his hand was a black ball that was roughly the size of a human fist, and there were matte silver patterns that bore a strong resemblance to arcs of lightning running all over its surface.

During the past few days, Han Li had failed on countless occasions to replicate the Heavy Water Lightning Bead, but he had finally succeeded here.

In terms of physical appearance, there were clear differences between this lightning ball and the Heavy Water Lightning Beads. The lightning ball was significantly larger, and there was no black mist lingering around it. Due to the presence of the eye-catching silver lightning veins on its surface, Han Li had decided to name it Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

Due to the lack of incorporation of law powers, the heavy water hadn't been refined to a sufficient degree of purity, so the lightning ball was quite large, and the lightning within also wasn't sealed as securely as was the case in the Heavy Water Lightning Beads.

However, this was the extent of his capabilities up to this point.

Just figuring out the right ratio of heavy water to lightning alone had already proven to be an extremely difficult task. Due to how difficult heavy water was to control, injecting too little power of lightning into the heavy water would result in a product that was lacking in power, but injecting too much would result in an unstable product that could explode at any moment.

Finally, he had managed to refine one that he was quite pleased with, so the next step was naturally to test out its power.

With that in mind, Han Li injected a wisp of immortal spiritual power into the ball, then tossed it forward with a flick of his wrist.

The Heavy Water Veined Lightning flew through the air in an arc, then fell toward the surface of the sea.

After flying to about 4,000 to 5,000 feet away from Han Li, the silver patterns on its surface abruptly lit up, following which a thunderous explosion rang out.

Immediately thereafter, countless arcs of silver lightning spread through the air in all directions, encompassing the entire area in a radius of over 1,000 feet.

Han Li had already retreated to over 10,000 feet away, but his gaze had remained firmly fixed on the explosion this entire time.

The explosion was extremely similar to the one that displayed by the Heavy Water Lightning Bead earlier. Just like in that explosion, a vast ball of black light that was close to 1,000 feet in size had appeared, accompanied by flashes of silver lightning.

However, what was different this time was that the explosion was lacking in the formidable law power fluctuations.

As was the case with the explosion of the Heavy Water Lightning Bead, a massive crater had appeared on the surface of the sea beneath the ball of black light, sending enormous waves hundreds of feet tall surging in all directions.

Moments later, the surface of the sea was still riddled with enormous waves, but it was no longer as violent and terrifying as it appeared earlier.

Han Li flew back to the spot where the lightning ball had exploded, and after carefully sensing the changes in the surrounding air, he spread both hands open to release hair-thin strands of immortal spiritual power.

The air around him rippled slightly, and countless barely visible black spots were drawn toward the palms of his hands by his immortal spiritual power.

Only after a long while did the tiny black specks converge to form a pair of fist-sized balls of black liquid, which was none other than the heavy water contained in the lightning ball from earlier.

"Looks like the lack of law powers is really impacting its power. That wasn't even a tenth as powerful as the explosion from the Heavy Water Lightning Bead," Han Li murmured to himself as he heaved a faint sigh.

Despite this, he was still quite pleased with the power of the Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

Even with the lack of law powers, he had managed to replicate the Heavy Water Lightning Bead quite well, and just like the Heavy Water Lightning Bead, his Heavy Water Veined Lightning also appeared to be completely innocuous right up to the moment before it was detonated.

Furthermore, he was able to recover the tiny specks of heavy water dispersed by the explosion, so not much of a loss was incurred.

Most importantly, he only had two Heavy Water Lightning Beads left, but given sufficient time, he would be able to refine an unlimited supply of Heavy Water Veined Lightning. If he were to unleash dozens or even hundreds of this lightning at once, then their collective power would still be extremely formidable.

Right at this moment, his brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he flipped a hand over to produce an azure mask that he quickly put on his face.

In the next instant, a vast expanse of azure light surged forth, transforming into a massive azure array plate projection.

A series of ripples surged out of the azure light, and a humanoid projection of a figure wearing a loose-fitting robe and an azure vulture mask appeared before Han Li.

"Have you contacted me about the mission that I released?" Han Li asked.

"That's right, I have some information for you," the projection replied, and their voice was a little sharp, but it was impossible to tell whether they were male or female.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. "You only have some information for me?"

"I'm afraid so. Both of the things that you're searching for, namely dao pill recipes and cultivation arts related to the laws of time, are extremely difficult to come by. There are many guild members enquiring about such items every single day, but how many of them actually end up obtaining those things?" the projection chuckled.

"I clearly stated in the mission debriefing that I want concrete and useful information. If you only have some inconsequential information or unreliable rumors to impart, then I'm afraid that won't suffice," Han Li said.

"Why don't you take a listen to what I have to say before you decide whether the information I have for you is worth the reward?" the projection chuckled.

Han Li merely nodded in response, encouraging the figure to continue.

"Have you heard of the Heaven Flow Palace, the Blaze Dragon Dao, and the Dawn Fall Sect?" the projection asked.

"The Heaven Flow Palace is a vastly renowned immortal sect in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, but I don't know about the other two sects," Han Li replied.

"All three of these sects are in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and I'm telling you about them because all three of them possess cultivation arts related to the laws of time," the projection said.

Han Li was rather intrigued to hear this, but his expression remained completely unchanged as he asked, "Would you be able to elaborate on that?"

"Out of those three sects, the Heaven Flow Palace is the most powerful, the Dawn Fall Sect is the most enigmatic, while the Blaze Dragon Dao has been around the longest. However, all of them have been studying the laws of time for millions of years. According to my knowledge, the Dawn Fall Sect's premier cultivation art, the Illusory Dawn Treasured Scripture, can allow one to glean the laws of time upon reaching a sufficiently advanced level.

“The Heaven Flow Palace has a cultivation art called the Water Divination Time Arts, which is also related to the laws of time. The Blaze Dragon Dao also possesses a cultivation art of this distinction, but I'm not sure what its name is," the projection explained.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, then asked, "Do you know if any of those cultivation arts are superior to the others?"

"That concerns the secrets of the three sects, so I don't know the answer to that," the projection replied.

"I see. Do you know the locations of the three sects? Surely this is information that you're privy to."

"Of course. The Heaven Flow Palace is situated in the Point Heaven Mountain Range of the Upper Arr Continent, which is located in the south of the immortal region. The Dawn Fall Sect is situated in the Peaceful Small Heaven Realm in the north of the immortal region, and the Blaze Dragon Dao is situated in the Bell Toll Mountain Range of the Ancient Cloud Continent, which is located in the east of the immortal region," the projection replied.

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then asked, "Do you know what are the requirements to join the Blaze Dragon Dao?"

According to what he had learned during these past few years on Black Wind Island, the Black Wind Sea was situated in the southeast of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, which meant that it was closest to the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Heaven Flow Palace.

His top priority at the moment was to recover his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and Daoist Xie, which had been revealed to be in the east by the Bonded Eight Spirits Vat, thereby making the Blaze Dragon Dao a logical destination.

Instead of answering Han Li's question, the figure asked, "Is the information that I'm providing worthy of the reward for your mission?"

"If that's all the information that you have, then I could've uncovered all of this myself in due time. If you don't have any information that's more useful than what you've provided so far, then I suggest you don't waste any more of our time," Han Li replied in a cold voice.

The figure wasn't fazed by Han Li's cold demeanor, and they countered, "Don't underestimate the information that I've provided, Fellow Daoist. Without my help, even if you manage to get to the Blaze Dragon Dao, you'll only be made a guest elder at the very most, and the secret scriptures of the inner sect will be completely out of your reach."

Chapter 155: Departure

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked.

"According to my knowledge, the Blaze Dragon Dao keeps a very close eye on its cultivation arts, and they're only made available to inner sect disciples and elders. In order to enter the inner sect, you'll require a recommendation from an inner sect elder.

“Otherwise, even as a True Immortal, you'll only be accepted as an outer sect guest elder, and only after an extremely extensive probation period will you have a sliver of an opportunity to enter the inner sect," the projection explained.

"It sounds like you know someone that can put in a recommendation for me," Han Li said as he raised an eyebrow.

"To tell you the truth, that's not something I can do for you. However, I know of a way that'll allow you to obtain an inner sect token of one of the elders at the Blaze Dragon Dao. With that token, you'll be able to directly enter the Blaze Dragon Dao's inner sect," the projection said.

A smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he prompted, "In that case, I'm all ears. This piece of information is definitely worthy of the reward I'm offering."

"I once took on a mission from our Transient Guild, requiring me to help the clan of one of the Blaze Dragon Dao's inner sect elders resolve a major problem, and the reward for completing the mission is an inner sect token left behind by that elder. I can pass this mission onto you," the projection said.

"Given how valuable the reward is, I'm assuming the mission won't be very easy to complete, right?" Han Li asked.

"The mission debriefing didn't actually reveal exactly what needs to be done. It only states that this mission can only be completed by someone with a True Immortal Stage cultivation base at the very minimum. As for the exact details of the mission, you'll have to go to the clan in question to find out," the projection replied.

"Is there a time limit on when the mission must be completed?" Han Li asked.

"No. Anyone that takes on the mission will receive a jade slip, and as long as the jade slip hasn't broken on its own, that means that the mission is still in effect," the projection .

Han Li paused for a moment to contemplate the situation, then decided, "Alright, I'll take on the mission. Please give me the jade slip, Fellow Daoist."

Han Li then raised a hand to release a blue storage pouch, which flew through the air and into the azure array plate.

At the same time, a white jade slip also slowly flew out of the array plate.

Han Li caught the jade slip, then inspected it briefly before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The jade slip contained the mission debriefing, as well as a map of the Ancient Cloud Continent.

However, upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that the map was severely lacking in detail, with only the area near the Bell Toll Mountain Range displayed, while almost everything else was left blank.

After examining the storage pouch sent over by Han Li, the figure said, "This is a tracking map. Once you reach the general vicinity of the Bell Toll Mountain Range on the Ancient Cloud Continent, the shortest path to the destination will be revealed to the holder of the jade slip."

"I see. You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist," Han Li replied with a nod.

The figure cupped their fist in a salute toward Han Li, then quickly vanished on the spot, and the array plate that was hovering above the sea also disappeared.

Han Li stowed his mask away, then flew back toward Black Wind Island as a streak of azure light.

Several days later.

The residual hype of the centenary auction still hadn't died down yet, so the entire Black Wind Island was still as lively and bustling as ever. Many of the shops in Black Wind City were seizing this opportunity to do everything they could to attract more customers through their doors.

The streets in the city were packed with people and carriages, and there were also many figures flying through the air to access the hovering buildings up above.

A unremarkable-looking azure-robed young man was making his way along a wide street toward the center of the city, and beside him was another young man with a dark complexion. They were none other than Han Li and Mu Xue.

"Senior Liu, I've always felt like you're not an ordinary cultivator, but I didn't think you would actually be able to secure a teleportation spot from the Heavenly Star Pagoda," Mu Xue said as he turned to Han Li with a wide smile, and Han Li also smiled in response, but offered no explanation.

Mu Xue didn't speak any further about this subject upon seeing this. Despite the fact that Han Li had always displayed a mild and amiable personality, he still harbored a great deal of awe and veneration toward this unfathomable senior, and of course, he longed to reach this level himself someday.

Looking at the throngs of people making their way through the streets, Han Li suddenly asked, "Have you ever thought about leaving Black Wind Island to see the outside world?"

Mu Xue faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied in a slightly dejected manner, "Black Wind Island is already the most prosperous place in the entire Black Wind Sea. If an itinerant cultivator like myself were to go anywhere else, I would struggle just to survive."

"The world is a vast place that encompasses far more than just the Black Wind Sea. You have decent cultivation aptitude, you're just missing some resources," Han Li said with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Senior Liu. I can only hope to encounter more clients like yourself and save up some more spirit stones. Perhaps I'll be able to advance a little further on the path of cultivation then," Mu Xue replied with a self-deprecating smile.

Mu Xue reminded Han Li very much of his younger self, and thinking back to when he first embarked on the path of cultivation, his aptitude had been far inferior to Mu Xue's. If it weren't for the Heaven Controlling Vial, perhaps he wouldn't have even made it to the Spirit Realm.

A reminiscent look appeared in his eyes as he was guided by Mu Xue to the Heavenly Star Pagoda.

Around an hour later, the two of them arrived at the end of the main street leading to the center of the city, and a white stone plaza that was over 10,000 feet in size had appeared up ahead.

There were only a few people on the plaza, and all of them were hurriedly making their way toward a cylindrical stone pagoda at the very center of the plaza.

Han Li looked up to find that the stone pagoda was over 1,000 feet tall, and the entire structure was of a pristine white color. There were countless lines of different depths and shapes on its surface, forming some type of special array patterns.

"That's the Heavenly Star Pagoda up ahead, Senior Liu. This is where we'll have to part ways," Mu Xue said in a respectful voice as he extended a deep bow toward Han Li.

By the time he stood up straight again, Han Li was already nowhere to be seen, and a forlorn look flashed through his eyes.

Right at this moment, a familiar voice suddenly rang out in his heart.

"Do not excessively belittle yourself, Mu Xue. The spirit stones and that cultivation art in the storage pouch are my parting gifts to you. Work hard in your cultivation, and there's definitely a chance that you could make a name for yourself someday."

Mu Xue faltered slightly upon hearing this, then laid a hand onto his own waist to find that a storage pouch had appeared there without his detection.

He immediately began looking around, and he spotted Han Li near the Heavenly Star Pagoda.

Looking at Han Li from afar, a surge of warmth instantly welled up in his heart, and he extended another deep bow, remaining in a bowed position for a long time.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued to make his way directly toward the pagoda without looking back at Mu Xue.

The pagoda didn't have any visible entrances, and just as a befuddled look appeared on Han Li's face, a burst of spiritual power fluctuations suddenly surged forth, following which an object flew out of his sleeve amid a flash of light.

It was the black badge that had been given to him by Lu Jun, and it flew into the pagoda before vanishing without a trace.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of spatial fluctuations swept over Han Li, and he also vanished on the spot, reappearing inside the pagoda a second later.

He looked around to find that the interior of the pagoda was completely hollow, much like a giant upside-down cup.

There were countless array runes inscribed onto the walls around him, as well as spirit stones of an exceptional quality embedded onto the wall at the points where the runes intersected.

There were also circles of ring-shaped array patterns engraved onto the ground underfoot, giving off faint spatial fluctuations.

At this moment, there were around 30 to 40 other people in the pagoda, and there were both humans and beings of other races among them. However, the one common trait that they all shared was a formidable aura.

Han Li's gaze roamed over the people around him, and as his gaze fell upon a woman in a long red dress, he couldn't help but look at her for a moment longer.

The woman possessed breathtaking beauty, and her fiery red dress perfectly accentuated the gorgeous curves of her exceptional figure.

Her facial features were extremely intricate, but her brows and eyes were a little long and narrow, giving off a cold aura that presented a stark contrast with her alluring body, but it was somehow still a perfectly harmonious combination.

Many of the people in the pagoda were also casting furtive glances her way, some with hints of lust in their eyes, but one dared to step out of line.

Even though Han Li's gaze had also lingered momentarily on her, that wasn't due to any physical attraction that he felt. Instead, it was because he couldn't sense the woman's cultivation base at all, thereby evoking a sense of wariness within him.

The woman paid no heed to all of the glances cast her way, crossing her arms in front of her chest as she pondered something in silence.

All of a sudden, she seemed to have detected something, and she turned to take a glance at Han Li, but at this point, his gaze was already elsewhere.

Right at this moment, an elderly voice suddenly rang out. "Sorry to keep you all waiting, fellow daoists. It's time for the teleportation to commence. Simply carry your badge in your hand and you'll be able to enter the array."

Han Li turned to find that the gray-robed elderly man that had been seated on one side of the array had risen to his feet, and a circular array plate had appeared in his hand.

With a sweep of his sleeve, dozens of streaks of blue light shot forth, and each of them flew toward one of the people in the pagoda with unerring accuracy.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand to draw the approaching streak of blue light into his grasp, upon which he discovered that it was a profound talisman with around a dozen silver runes inscribed in beveled silver text flashing on its surface.

Everyone else caught their talismans as well, then proceeded to make their way toward the circular array engraved onto the ground.

Han Li stepped into the array along with everyone else, and after everyone had piled into the array, the elderly man made a hand seal with one hand, then firmly pressed his palm down onto the array plate while chanting a fast incantation.

A loud buzzing sound rang out as all of the runes on the walls of the pagoda began to glow brightly, as did all of the spirit stones embedded onto the walls, and all of the spiritual power contained within the spirit stones surged forth in a frenzy.

The array patterns underfoot began to radiate dazzling white light, which swallowed up everyone in an instant.

Chapter 156: The Perilous Path of Cultivation

The entire surrounding space was filled with dazzling white light, immediately followed by a rush of dizziness, while the sound of howling wind rang out.

At the same time, there seemed to be gusts of astral wind sweeping toward everyone, only to be kept out by some type of invisible force right before it came into contact with their bodies.

Only after what seemed like a long time did this peculiar sensation abruptly fade away, and everything became clearly visible again.

Han Li quickly inspected his surroundings to find that everyone had been teleported into a massive underground cavern, and the ground and the walls of the cavern were quite similar to what was inside the Heavenly Star Pagoda, with the same engraved runes and embedded spirit stones.

The talisman that Han Li had been holding had vanished at some point during the teleportation, and a wry smile appeared on his face upon seeing this.

He had wanted to study the talisman, but the teleportation had concluded before he had a chance to react, and the talisman had disappeared from his possession.

Seated not far away outside the array was an elderly itinerant immortal with a head of white hair coupled with a set of youthful facial features, and there were around 20 to 30 people standing behind him. These people were all dressed in different attire, and many of them didn't appear to have been from the Black Wind Sea.

After Han Li and the others emerged from the array at the center of the cavern, all of those people stepped onto the array to replace them.

Right as he was passing by these people, a sense of peril suddenly welled up in Han Li's heart, and he reflexively took a glance at a few of the people in the ground.

The group of cultivators in questions were quite unremarkable in appearance, and their auras were very stable. Even their expressions were quite calm and collected, but for some reason, Han Li could instinctively sense a dangerous aura from them, and that was making him quite apprehensive.

Right at this moment, a physically imposing green-skinned man emerged from the group that had been teleported into the underground cavern alongside Han Li, and he arrived in front of the elderly itinerant cultivator as he cupped his fist in a salute and said, "Thank you for your hard work, Elder Yi. I'll be taking over from you for the next 100 years."

The elderly man rose to his feet with a smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a round array plate that he offered to the green-skinned man as he said, "I was wondering who the island master would send to relieve me of my post, but I didn't think it would be you, Brother Lu! I'll leave everything here to you then."

The green-skinned man accepted the array plate, and the two of them bade farewell to each other before the elderly itinerant immortal also made his way into the array.

Moments later, everyone in the array was teleported to Black Wind Island amid a flash of bright white light.

Only after everyone in the array had disappeared did the hint of apprehension in Han Li's heart begin to fade.

Meanwhile, the green-skinned man stowed away the array plate as he turned to everyone and declared, "From this day forth, the Black Wind Cave teleportation array will be closed for 100 years. If you wish to return to the Black Wind Sea, come back 100 years later when the array reopens. Of course, you have to prepare enough immortal origin stones to cover the teleportation cost.

“If you leave this cave and travel northward along the coastline for a few thousand kilometers, you'll reach Seaside City. Those of you who are visiting the Primordial Wave Continent for the first time can stop by Seaside City for some supplies before continuing on your way. I wish all of you a smooth journey."

Everyone cupped their fists in a salute toward the green-skinned man before exiting the underground cavern.

Han Li followed everyone out of the cavern, and he was immediately greeted by a slight fishy odor in the air, which was carried into his nostrils by the sea breeze.

He rose up into the air, and from that vantage point, he could see that he was situated above a vast and boundless sea.

Directly up ahead was the choppy and turbulent ocean, while behind him was a winding coastline, and the cavern that he had just emerged from was situated within a well-concealed cliff on the coast.

The people that had arrived here alongside Han Li didn't linger here for very long before scattering in all directions, and the woman in the red dress had also departed.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li began to fly northward along the coastline as a streak of azure light.

Initially, the landscape down below was rather barren and desolate, but after flying for a while, vast forests began to appear.

The trees in this place were remarkably tall, and it was a very common sight here to see trees standing close to 1,000 feet in height, resembling a series of tall mountains. The ground was covered in a thick layer of fallen leaves, as well as countless shrubs and weeds, giving it a primordial appearance, as if no one had ever set foot in this place.

The forest stretched into the distance as far as the eyes could see, and Han Li could hear the roar of a certain type of demon beast ringing out up ahead.

The primordial aura of this place evoked a long-absent sense of excitement in Han Li's heart, and after flying for close to an hour, the outlines of a coastal city began to appear in his field of view.

The city wasn't very large, only several hundred kilometers in radius, and it was completely enshrouded under a light barrier that resembled a dense film of yellow sand. At first glance, it appeared as if there were a giant yellow turtle shell encompassing the entire city, and the words "Seaside City" were inscribed above the city gates in ancient text.

There was only a single opening in the yellow light barrier that granted access to the city gates, and it was quite a lively and bustling area with cultivators occasionally emerging from the city on their own or in groups to fly into the forest up ahead.

At the same time, there were also cultivators flying out of the forest toward the city. Many of them looked rather worse for wear, and some of them even had bloodstains on their clothes, but most of them appeared to be quite excited.

Han Li quickly descended onto the ground, and at this point, he had already withdrawn his aura, posing as a Body Integration cultivator as he joined the crowd that was entering the city.

There were two teams of azure-robed guards situated at the city gate, and all of them were at the Spatial Tempering Stage, while their leader was a Body Integration cultivator.

However, these guards didn't raise any questions to the people entering the city. Even for a completely unfamiliar face like Han Li, he was allowed into the city after issuing some spirit stones as payment.

Beyond the city gate was a wide street that extended into the city, and the street was lined with all types of shops.

The city didn't have a particularly large population, but most of them were cultivators with lofty cultivation bases, and mortals were an extremely rare sight here.

The shops that lined the streets weren't particularly elegant. In fact, they were rather crude in appearance, selling wares such as spirit herbs, ore, demon beast materials, and other types of materials.

After a brief inspection, Han Li discovered that despite the crude appearance of the shops, the wares being sold all seemed to be of quite a high standard that wasn't inferior in the slightest compared with the most prestigious shops in Black Wind City.

As opposed to calling it a city, it was more accurate to call Seaside City a supply point for cultivators.

After observing his surroundings for a while, Han Li made his way toward a variety shop.

There was no one else in the shop aside from a hideous man with pockmarks all over his face sitting behind the counter, and he hurriedly rose to his feet at the sight of Han Li.

The pockmarked man was only a Deity Transformation cultivator, and he was displaying a very respectful demeanor after sensing Han Li's Body Integration Stage aura. "What can I help you with, Senior? My shop isn't very big, but I have a very comprehensive range of wares that'll be sure to satisfy all your needs."

"Do you sell maps here?" Han Li asked.

The pockmarked man flipped a hand over to produce an azure jade slip as he smiled and replied, "Yes, I have the most detailed map of the Lost Grave Forest here. If you want to hunt for any demon beasts or gather any spirit herbs, the map will lay out all of the locations where you'll find the things you're looking for."

It seemed that the Lost Grave Forest was the name of the primordial forest outside Seaside City.

Han Li shook his head as he replied, "I don't need a map of the Lost Grave Forest. Do you sell maps of the Primordial Wave Continent? Also, if you have any maps of the other nearby continents, I'd be happy to purchase them as well."

The pockmarked man faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a slightly peculiar look appeared in his eyes.

"Is there a problem?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"No, not at all," the pockmarked man hurriedly replied, then flipped a hand over to produce a pair of jade slips, one yellow and one blue.

Han Li picked up the yellow jade slip, then injected his spiritual sense into it.

"That one contains a map of our Primordial Wave Continent, while this blue jade slip contains a map of the nearby area. You've definitely come to the right place for maps, Senior. My family has been selling map jade slips for generations.

“It's easy to find maps of the Primordial Wave Continent, but maps of the nearby continents are quite rare, and I daresay my shop is the only one in the entire city that sells such maps," the pockmarked man said with a hint of pride in his voice.

As it turned out, the pockmarked man had a right to be proud. The map in the yellow jade slip was far more detailed than the average map, not only clearly depicting the terrain on all parts of the Primordial Wave Continent, there were even some detailed annotations attached to certain special areas.

One of those special areas was the Lost Grave Forest outside Seaside City. The forest had a radius of tens of thousand of kilometers, and it was inhabited by all types of demon beast. In fact, it was said that there were even some True Immortal Stage demon beasts residing in the heart of the forest, making it an extremely perilous place.

In addition to that, there was also an abundance of natural treasures in the forest, so there were many cultivators who would come here from far and wide to hunt for demon beasts and search for spirit ingredients. Of course, once they entered the forest, they would be solely responsible for their own safety.

There were many perilous places on the Primordial Wave Continent, and the Lost Grave Forest was only one of them.

Compared with this place, the Black Wind Sea could be considered to be an extremely safe area.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense from the yellow jade slip, and an uncertain look had appeared on his face.

Even though he had already made preparations for this trip, it seemed like the Immortal Realm outside of the Black Wind Sea was far more perilous than he had imagined. Even with his current powers, he wouldn't dare to proclaim that he could safely cross the Primordial Wave Continent, and this was a perfect representation of how perilous the path of cultivation could be.

After a brief pause, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the blue jade slip, and moments later, he withdrew his spiritual sense again.

This was indeed a map of the nearby continents, but it was nowhere near as detailed as the map of the Primordial Wave Continent, with only some important areas being marked out.

Just as he had anticipated, the Primordial Wave Continent and the nearby continents were separated by the sea, and the Ancient Cloud Continent was situated to the east of the Primordial Wave Continent, with the continents separated by what was known as the Thunderstorm Sea.

Seaside City was situated on the westernmost border of the Primordial Wave Continent, so if he wanted to get to the Ancient Cloud Continent, then he would have to cross the entire Primordial Wave Continent and the Thunderstorm Sea.

According to the annotations on the map, the Thunderstorm Sea was, as its name suggested, rift with violent thunderstorms all year round, making it an extremely perilous place to traverse through.

Chapter 157: Immortal Outlet

"Are you alright, Senior?"

Han Li had been standing on the spot, holding the two jade slips with a dazed expression for quite some time, and the pockmarked man was growing a little concerned.

Han Li snapped out of his train of thought, then asked, "How much for these two jade slips?"

The pockmarked man stated a price that wasn't very expensive, and Han Li issued the requested sum of spirit stones.

"You just said that your family has been selling map jade slips for generations, so you must know the Primordial Wave Continent very well. I have some questions to ask you. If you can provide me with satisfactory answers, then you can keep these spirit stones." Han Li flipped a hand over as he spoke, producing a small pile of spirit stones that he set down onto the counter.

A hint of greed appeared in the pockmarked man's eyes as he glanced at the high-grade spirit stones on the counter, and he said, "Go right ahead, Senior. I'll be sure to tell you everything I know."

"Is there any safe way to cross the Primordial Wave Continent from Seaside City? For example, are there any teleportation arrays I can use?" Han Li asked.

"You seem to have very little knowledge on our Primordial Wave Continent, Senior. Among all of the continents in this area, our Primordial Wave Continent is situated in quite a secluded region, and most of the land is primordial and uninhabited.

“Even if there are some cities, they're only small cities with very low populations, so most of them won't have any teleportation arrays. This is particularly true for a rural city like Seaside City. Hence, if you want to get to somewhere from here, the only way is to fly there," the pockmarked man replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Having said that, this doesn't apply to the entire journey. While there are no teleportation arrays in Seaside City, the central region of the continent is far more prosperous, and there are some cities there that have teleportation arrays, but I've heard the required cost to use those teleportation arrays is extremely steep," the pockmarked man hurriedly added.

"Do you know which cities on the continent have teleportation arrays?" Han Li asked.

"All of the cities with teleportation arrays have already been marked out on the map of the Primordial Wave Continent. Perhaps you didn't notice them, but they're the ones with white vortex symbols on them," the pockmarked man replied with a smile.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then injected his spiritual sense into the yellow jade slip again, and sure enough, there were indeed some cities in the central and eastern regions of the Primordial Wave Continent that had some tiny white vortex symbols on them.

"I see." Han Li nodded as he withdrew his spiritual sense from the jade slip.

There were quite a few of those cities on the map, so as long as he could make it to the central region of the Primordial Wave Continent, the rest of his journey across the continent would be far safer.

The pockmarked man hesitated momentarily, then asked, "Are you really planning to cross the entire Primordial Wave Continent, Senior?"

Han Li nodded in response.

"In that case, I must inform you that there are many perils along the way. If you're traveling alone, there are many natural obstacles that you'll most likely struggle to cross. My advice is for you to go and take a look in the Immortal Outlet in the city," the pockmarked man advised.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression upon hearing this. "Alright, thank you for providing me with this information, you can have those spirit stones."

He knew that he would come into contact with the Immortal Palace very quickly after leaving the Black Wind Sea, but he didn't expect this day to come quite so soon.

During his time in Black Wind City, he had learned that these so-called Immortal Outlets were places set up by the Immortal Palace, where cultivators could take on the missions released by the Immortal Palace and also release missions of their own.

It was clear that the pockmarked man regarded the journey across the entire continent to be an extremely perilous one for a Body Integration cultivator, so he was advising Han Li to make the journey as part of a team that was carrying out a mission.

It wasn't impossible for him to make the journey on his own given his current cultivation base, but this was a completely foreign continent to him, and he was missing all of his treasures, so it was best to take some safety precautions.

With that in mind, he gave the pockmarked man a parting nod before leaving the shop.

There were no flight restrictions in the city, and after flying along the main street in the city for a while, a golden building appeared in front of Han Li.

The building was situated on a hill, and it looked as if it had been constructed from pure gold. What was most remarkable about it was that there was a massive golden dragon engraved onto the roof of the building, and it was roaring to the heavens, presenting a formidable and majestic sight to behold.

The golden building appeared to be rather similar to the imperial palaces of the mortal world, and all of the mortals passing through the area regarded the building with awe and veneration in their eyes.

The words "Immortal Outlet" were visible above the gate of the golden palace, inscribed in ancient text.

Han Li stood at the entrance of the building for a moment before making his way inside.

Upon entry, he was greeted by the sight of a vast and spacious hall that was at least 10,000 feet in size. There were many cultivators dressed in different attire in the hall, but the majority of them were at or below the Deity Transformation Stage, and there were barely even any Spatial Tempering cultivators around.

To the left of the hall was a large shop that was selling all types of treasures, pills, and spirit materials. The wares being sold here seemed to be of a slightly superior standard to the wares sold in the shops in the city, and as a result, it was attracting quite a few customers.

To the right of the hall was another shop with a series of long stone tables placed outside. It seemed to be a shop that exclusively dealt in acquisitions, and there were many cultivators lined up outside, waiting to sell things to the shop.

The hall and these shops were managed by some golden-robed cultivators with the same golden dragon design embroidered onto their robes, and the most powerful one among them was a Spatial Tempering cultivator, who was seated deep in the hall with his eyes closed.

The hall resembled a small city, and it was far more lively and bustling than the actual city outside.

At the very center of the hall was a huge azure jade wall, upon which was inscribed many lines of small text that contained mission descriptions and corresponding rewards.

There were many cultivators gathered near the stone wall, all of whom were inspecting the missions on the wall, and some of them were speaking to their companions, seemingly gauging whether a mission was worth taking on.

Han Li took a glance at the shops on either side of the hall, then paid no them no further heed as he made his way directly to the stone wall at the center of the hall.

There was a huge number of missions on the wall, and they were constantly changing intermittently.

However, the missions at the very top of the stone wall were displayed in golden text, and they were the only permanent missions on the wall, while the other missions that were constantly changing were inscribed in white text.

After taking a moment to listen to the conversations taking place around, Han Li learned that the missions displayed in golden text were ones that had been released by the Immortal Palace, while the rest had been released by ordinary cultivators.

Upon learning this distinction, he directed his attention back to the missions before him, and sure enough, there were indeed missions recruiting companions for long journeys.

In fact, there were quite a few of these missions, and some of them were purely recruiting travel companions, while others required one to protect someone on the way to other cities.

These missions all had different cultivation base requirements, but the longer journeys generally requested cultivators ranging from the Deity Transformation Stage all the way to above the Spatial Tempering Stage. However, this was no surprise.

Aside from a small number of areas on the Primordial Wave Continent, the rest of the continent was rife with peril, and there were many stretches between cities that were so perilous that they were completely uninhabited for hundreds of thousands of kilometers. For the vast majority of cultivators, attempting to cross those areas was no different from committing suicide.

Upon emerging from the pockmarked man's shop, he had already decided on his next destination. It was a city near the central region of the Primordial Wave Continent by the name of Bright Hill City.

That was the closest city of Seaside City that had a teleportation array.

As his gaze roamed over the wall, Han Li quickly narrowed down his selection to three missions, one of which was purely recruiting travel companions, the second one required one to escort a merchant party to their destination, while the last one required one to escort a certain person.

He approached the stone wall, then said to one of the golden-robed cultivators sitting there, "I want to take on mission number 252."

This was the merchant party escort mission. The commencement dates of the other two missions were still quite far away, while the merchant party was going to set off in three days.

The golden-robed man flipped a hand over to produce a jade tablet, and he didn't even bother to raise his head as he said, "Hand over your immortal token."

"Immortal token?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately realized that this so-called immortal badge was most likely something that was required for one to take on missions from the Immortal Outlet.

The golden-robed man's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he pointed at a room with an azure door in the deepest part of the hall as he said, "Have you not collected an immortal token yet? See that room over there? That's where you can get an immortal token."

Han Li thanked the golden-robed cultivator before making his way toward the room.

He was currently in disguise, and he was praying that no one would be able to see through it.

At the moment, he was wanted by the Ubiquitous Pavilion, and he definitely didn't want to have his true appearance cataloged in an organization like the Immortal Palace, which had a presence throughout the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Han Li strode over to the azure door, then gently exhaled before knocking on the door.

The door swung open on its own to reveal a small room, within which was seated a golden-robed elderly man with a Body Integration Stage cultivation base.

Han Li was quite relieved to see this. Given the cultivation base and spiritual sense of the elderly man, the chances that he could see through Han Li's disguise were extremely slim.

"You're here for an immortal token, right? Come," the golden-robed elderly man said as he beckoned to Han Li.

Han Li cupped his fist in a salute toward the man, then stepped into the room.

"Tell me your name and where you came from," the elderly man instructed as he pulled out a book and a silver brush.

"My name is Liu Shi, and I come from the Black Wind Sea."

The elderly man nodded in response, then wrote something down onto the book before flipping a hand over to produce a golden badge that he waved in Han Li's direction.

A burst of golden light surged out of the badge before enveloping Han Li's entire body.

Han Li was slightly alarmed by this, but he maintained a calm façade.

The golden light receded in a flash, and Han Li's visage had been emblazoned onto the badge.

The elderly man waved his silver brush over the badge a couple of times, and golden light flashed from the badge before immediately fading.

"Alright, it's done. This immortal token will serve as your proof of identification when you go to Immortal Outlets to accept missions and rewards, so make sure to keep it safe," the elderly man said as he tossed the golden badge at Han Li.

Han Li caught the badge with a surprised expression.

That burst of golden light just now had only served to record his visage without conducting any type of examination on him, and he couldn't help but be surprised by how lax this process was.

Alternatively, could it be that the masks of the Transient Guild were able to bypass the identity verification of the Immortal Palace?

The golden-robed elderly man seemed to have noticed Han Li's expression, and he said in a meaningful voice, "Our Immortal Palace has no intention of knowing too much about our fellow daoists, nor do we care if you've presented your true appearance to us."

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, then gave the elderly man a nod before exiting the room.

Looking at the throngs of people in the hall, he realized that it was most likely precisely because of how lax the administration process was that there were so many people gathered here.

With the immortal token, Han Li was quickly able to claim the mission that he wanted.

One of the golden-robed cultivators seated beside the stone wall cast an incantation at him, and a passage of text immediately appeared on his immortal token, instructing him to travel to an inn in the city to meet the person who had released the mission.

Han Li didn't linger in the Immortal Outlet any longer as he exited the palace, and after taking a moment to determine what direction he was supposed to go in, he flew away as a streak of azure light.

Chapter 158: Setting Off

Seaside City, White Cloud Inn.

This wasn't a particularly large inn, and just like the majority of the inn in the city, it catered to both mortals and cultivators.

Of course, the vast majority of cultivators who stayed in inns like this didn't possess particularly lofty cultivation bases, and as a safety precaution, they would often disguise themselves as mortals. In reality, this was kind of an unspoken rule. After all, if a mortal were to learn that they were living next door to an almighty cultivator, then they most likely wouldn't even be able to fall asleep at night.

On this day, the White Cloud Inn was much busier than usual. Starting from several days ago, someone had reserved the entire inn, and all of the original employees had been temporarily kicked out. At the moment, everyone in the inn was extremely busy.

The entire inn, from the front hall to the backyard, was laden with large crates that were filled with all types of goods.

There were also a series of horse-beast-drawn carriages that were also laden with all types of goods outside the inn, and these were the most common form of transportation on the Primordial Wave Continent.

A slightly rotund middle-aged man was pacing back and forth, instructing his subordinates to load the crates of goods from the beast-drawn carriages onto a white flying ark in the yard.

Despite how busy he was, a faint smile would occasionally appear on his face.

As the regional manager of the Chengquan Trading House, one of the three biggest trading houses of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, he had purchased a batch of several types of rare spirit materials unique to this area during the past 100 years.

Due to how dangerous this continent was, as long as he could transport these goods safely to Bright Hill City in the central region of the continent, he would immediately be able to sell everything for several times the price he had purchased it for.

The only downside to all of this was that among these goods, there was a large batch of spirit materials with very stringent freshness requirements, so they had to be kept alive. Hence, they couldn't be stored in storage treasures and could only be transported using this flying ark.

The only concern that he had now was the safety of the return journey.

This wasn't his first time traversing across this continent, so he knew that it was a very perilous trip. Recently, there had been a rather frequent occurrence of the trading house running into unforeseen perils all over the continent, resulting in the demise of even some Spatial Tempering Stage elders, so he didn't dare to get complacent.

He was only a Deity Transformation cultivator, and even though there were many elders and guest elders in the trading house, only two of them were at the Body Integration Stage. Hence, after some extensive thought, he decided to hire Body Integration cultivators at a steep cost to accompany them on this journey from the Immortal Outlet.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light descended in front of the inn before fading to reveal a dark-skinned man with a coarse beard, and it was none other than Han Li in his disguised form.

The rotund middle-aged man turned to Han Li upon sensing his arrival, and his immediately widened as he detected Han Li's cultivation base.

A bright smile appeared on his face as he hurriedly emerged from the inn, then cupped his fist in salute as he asked, "I presume you must've taken on my escort mission, Senior. May I know your name?"

"My name is Liu Shi. You must be Fellow Daoist Kou, right?" Han Li asked.

"That would be me."

The rotund man turned and invited Han Li into the inn, then instructed one of his subordinates to bring Han Li a cup of spirit tea.

After taking a seat across from Han Li, the man hesitated momentarily, then said, "This might be a little rude of me to ask, but may I please see your immortal token, Senior Liu?"

Han Li did as he was requested, flipping a hand over to produce his immortal token before handing it to the man.

The man inspected the token for a moment, and after verifying that it did indeed belong to Han Li, the smile on his face widened even further as he said, "We'll be counting on you, Senior. We're not setting off until two days from now, so in the meantime, you can rest in one of the rooms in the inn."

Han Li nodded in response, and the rotund man immediately instructed one of his subordinates to take Han Li to one of the rooms on the second floor.

Han Li set up an array in the room, then sat down with his legs crossed on the bed and flipped a hand over to produce a stack of thick books.

These were introductory books to the Primordial Wave Continent that he had purchased in the city earlier, and this was the perfect time to be reading them.

Two days passed by in the blink of an eye.

Late that night, a white flying ark was hovering in the air above the inn, and all of the goods had already been loaded onto the ark.

On the deck of the ark, there were around a dozen cultivators standing at the bow and the stern, and Han Li was one of them.

All of these cultivators belonged to the same trading house that the rotund man worked for, and aside from a pair of Body Integration cultivators, the rest of them all possessed rather lowly cultivation bases.

At this moment, Han Li was standing on one side of the deck, and he was taking a furtive glance at the other side with a peculiar look in his eyes.

Standing near the bow of the ark was a gorgeous woman in a long red dress.

Through his observation, he had determined that this was the very same woman who had recently been teleported out of the Black Wind Sea with him, but at this moment, she was wearing a red veil over her face that concealed her features.

Han Li had previously been unable to detect her cultivation base, but at the moment, her aura indicated that she was an early-Body Integration cultivator.

However, due to the fact that he was in disguise, the woman didn't seem to have identified him.

The commencement of the journey was imminent, and the man with the Kou surname was feeling rather uneasy as he cupped his fist in a salute to everyone. "I'll be counting on all of you for this trip."

Han Li and the others all nodded in response.

The rotund man took a glance at Han Li and the woman in the red dress, and he was feeling slightly more reassured. With a sweep his sleeve, countless white spirit patterns instantly appeared on the flying ark, and a vast expanse of white mist was also released to encompass the entire ark.

From the outside, the flying ark appeared to be no different from a cloud drifting through the sky, so it was very well-concealed.

The flying ark set off, flying over the night sky at a decent pace.

"Regarding our journey, this is the arrangement that I propose: the two of you and the two elders of our trading house will be split up into two groups, with one group protecting the ark while the other group rests, and we'll swap over once every half a month. What do you all think?" the rotund man asked.

"I'm happy to follow your lead," Han Li replied with a nod, while the woman in the red dress also nodded in silence.

The other two were both elders of the trading house, so they naturally had no objections, either.

"Alright, in that case, the elders of our trading house will look after the ark for this first half-month. I'll be counting on you," the rotund man said to the two other Body Integration cultivators.

The two of them offered no response as they sat down onto the ark, one at the bow, and one at the stern.

Meanwhile, Han Li and the woman in the red dress were arranged rooms to stay in on the ark.

The room was quite spacious, completely with a guest hall and a bedroom, and there was also a small secret chamber.

With a wave of his hand, several dozen streaks of azure light flew out of Han Li's sleeve, landing around the room to form an azure light barrier.

After that, he arrived in the secret chamber before taking a seat with his legs crossed.

There was still half a month until he had to relieve the other two Body Integration cultivators from their posts, and he had to make full use of this time.

After a moment of contemplation, he raised a hand, and a ball of heavy water flew out of the True Water Pouch strapped to his waist before hovering in mid-air in front of him.

A serious look appeared on his face as he made a series of hand seals, and arcs of silver lightning sprang out of his palms before entering the ball of heavy water.

The ball of heavy water immediately began to swell and warp in an unstable manner, looking as if it were about to explode, but it was forcibly trapped within the azure light that Han Li was releasing out of his hands.

He flicked his fingers rapidly through the air to cast a series of incantation seals, and the silver lightning within the heavy water instantly became very tame, transforming into thin strands of silver lightning.

At the same time, the heavy water also began to settle down, and the two gradually integrated themselves with one another.

A long while later, the ball of heavy water was nowhere to be seen, having been replaced by a fist-sized black ball with silver lightning veins flashing on its surface. This was another ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

At this point, Han Li had already become quite proficient in refining Heavy Water Veined Lightning, and he inspected the black ball for a moment before stowing it away.

Immediately thereafter, he drew another ball of heavy water out of his True Water Pouch, and silver lightning flashed from his hands once again to fuse with the heavy water...

The destructive power of the Heavy Water Veined Lightning was still rather lackluster, but given sufficient quantity, they could still pose a serious threat.

He didn't know what perils he was going to encounter in the journey ahead, so he had to prepare for the worst.

A month passed by in the blink of an eye, and Han Li was relieved of his post by the two trading house elders. Nothing of note had taken place during this time.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li was seated with a rather weary look on his face, but his eyes were filled with elation.

He had already refined part of the heavy water he was carrying into Heavy Water Veined Lightning, and there were seven or eight balls of the lightning in total.

A single ball of veined lightning wasn't very useful, but given sufficient numbers, it could definitely prove to be quite a formidable force that even a late-True Immortal cultivator would have to be wary of.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed the black ball in his hand into his storage bracelet, then flipped a hand over to produce a pill. After swallowing the pill and meditating for a short while, all of the weariness in his eyes had completely faded.

He flipped a hand over to produce a black array plate, and it was none other than one of the Twin Starshift Plates.

He had just sent a crystal to the Black Wind Sea a month ago, and this was the day on which his Earthly Deity Avatar was supposed to send him the heavy water that it had refined.

He cast an incantation seal onto the array plate, which immediately began to buzz audibly while releasing a large expanse of black light.

Han Li cast another incantation seal onto the array plate, causing it to revolve on the spot and glow even more brightly.

However, the usual ball of heavy water didn't appear, and a befuddled look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Could it be that something had happened to his Earthly Deity Avatar?

Right as he rose to his feet to take a closer look, a small ball of heavy water slowly appeared over the center of the array plate.

He heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, then sat down once again before stowing the ball of heavy water away with a wave of his hand.

The black array plate continued to revolve on the spot, and only after several more minutes had passed by did another small ball of heavy water appear.

This was not an encouraging sight for Han Li, and a contemplative look appeared on his face as he continued to scrutinize the array plate.

Judging from this situation, it seemed that nothing was wrong with his Earthly Deity Avatar, but there was a problem with this Twin Starshift Plate. For some reason, it was having much more difficulty transmitting heavy water than before.

With that in mind, he carefully inspected the array plate, but didn't discover anything amiss.

There were eight dark azure spirit stones embedded into the center of the array plate. These stones were called Starshift Stones, and they contained the power of space, and they acted as the energy source for treasures like the Twin Starshift Plates to function.

The eight Starshift Stones were giving off a faint glow, indicating that there was still sufficient spatial power within them, so theoretically speaking, the Twin Starshift Plate on the Earthly Deity Avatar's side should've been fine as well.

Why is this happening?

Han Li fell into deep thought with his brows tightly furrowed, and a short while later, he abruptly raised his head as a possibility occurred to him.

He had left the Black Wind Sea and was currently traveling eastward over the Primordial Wave Continent, so at the moment, he had to have been a vast distance away from his Earthly Deity Avatar. Could it be that there was an effective distance limit on the Twin Starshift Plates?

Chapter 159: Eastbound Journey

The more Han Li thought about it, the more convinced he became that this problem had to have something to do with distance.

It stood to reason that this array plate would function similarly to a teleportation array, so the longer the distance, the more difficult the transmission.

A concerned look appeared on his face as he arrived at this conclusion.

He had only just arrived on the Primordial Wave Continent, so he was still quite far away from the Blaze Dragon Dao, yet it was already becoming extremely difficult to have heavy water transmitted to him. By the time he reached the Blaze Dragon Dao, the Twin Starshift Plates would most likely be rendered completely useless.i

However, he couldn't just abandon his journey to the Blaze Dragon Dao for this reason, so this was just a problem that he would have to find a solution to after reaching the Blaze Dragon Dao.

With that in mind, he refocused his attention on the Twin Starshift Plate. Seeing as it was still able to transmit heavy water to him for the moment, he had to capitalize on this window of opportunity before it passed him by.

Back when he was in the Black Wind Sea, it would've only taken mere moments for his Earthly Deity Avatar to transmit all of the heavy water that it had refined in a month to him, but on this occasion, the same process took a full three days.

Han Li turned his gaze to the Twin Starshift Plate in his hand to find that the eight Starshift Stones had become semi-transparent, clearly having had most of their spiritual power exhausted.

The spiritual power used up in all of the past transmissions combined was less than what had been used for this single transmission.

A wry smile appeared on his face as he stowed the array plate away, then drew another ball of heavy water out of his True Water Pouch to continue refining more Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

Half a month passed by in the blink of an eye, and Han Li was on lookout duty once again.

He made his way out of his room, and he discovered the flying ark was traveling over a lush forest.

The woman in the red dress also emerged from her room not far away, and the two of them exchanged a glance before making their way to the opposite ends of the ark.

Both of the Body Integration Stage elders of the trading house were looking rather weary, and they cautioned, "We're beginning to get quite deep into the Lost Grave Forest, and more and more high-grade flying demon beasts are appearing, so make sure to be on your guard."

The man with the Kou surname had also arrived on the deck, and he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li and the woman in the red dress. "I'll be counting on you."

It seemed that he had been quite on-edge during this trip, and he would regularly come out to the deck to oversee proceedings. At this moment, he was looking quite weary, and his eyes were slightly bloodshot.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Kou. I accept the mission, and I'll do my best to complete it," Han Li replied with a nod, then flew over to the left hand side of the ark's bow.

The woman in the red dress offered no response, merely giving a slight nod before flying toward the stern.

The flying ark continued onward, but a short while later, a burst of rustling suddenly rang out from the forest down below. As it turned out, there was a red cloud flying rapidly toward the ark, and it hadn't been fooled by the white cloud around the ark at all.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes, and he was able to identify the red cloud as a flock of giant red birds.

These birds resembled eagles, and each of them was several dozen feet in size. They didn't have many feathers, and large sections of wrinkly red skin was bared, while each of them had a fleshy crest on its head. Their talons were disproportionately thick and large compared with the rest of their bodies, and they were extremely hideous in appearance.

The man with the Kou surname hadn't gone back to rest yet, and upon spotting the flock of birds, he exclaimed, "Those are Chicken Crest Eagles!"

The birds were closing in on the ark extremely quickly, and there were close to 1,000 of them, with each of them giving off an aura that wasn't inferior to that of a Nascent Soul cultivator.

The birds began to squawk with excitement as they opened their beaks to blast a series of crimson fireballs toward the flying ark.

At the same time, bright red light began to glow from their talons, and a flurry of sickle-shaped crimson claw projections were unleashed, howling through the air as they hurtled toward the ark.

"Activate the protective barrier!" the man with the Kou surname yelled.

The spirit patterns around the ark instantly lit up, and streaks of white light emerged to form a thick white protective barrier.

The crimson flames and claws projections struck the protective barrier with tremendous force, but the barrier remained resolute, displaying no signs of breaking.

At this point, Han Li had already risen up into the air, and with a sweep of his sleeve, nine streaks of white light flew out, revealing themselves to be a set of nine identical white flying swords.

Each flying sword was glowing with white radiance, and they were all spirit treasures.

Han Li had found this set of flying swords in the First Scourge's storage pouch, and they were a little similar to his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, so he decided to keep them, seeing as he had no suitable treasures to use at the moment.

Han Li made a hand seal with one hand, and the nine flying swords began to glow brightly ,transforming into hundreds of white sword threads in a flash.

The sword threads intertwined to form a massive white sword net, which encompassed the entire area of several thousand feet up ahead.

All of the crimson birds that came into contact with the white sword net were instantly sliced into pieces, falling into the forest down below as chunks of flesh and blood.

In the blink of an eye, dozens of the birds had been slain.

Meanwhile, the woman in the red dress had also sprung into action. A dragon formed by crimson flames had appeared before her, and it was extremely life-like. The dragon was close to 1,000 feet in length, and it blasted an enormous pillar of flames out of its mouth, incinerating all of the crimson birds in its path into ashes.

There was a huge number of these birds, but they were lacking in individual power, and it didn't take long before most of them had been slain by Han Li and the woman, following which the rest fled for their lives.

The nine flying swords flew back to Han Li at his behest, and the flying ark continued onward, but it didn't take long before more disturbance appeared up ahead, and the ark was attacked by a swarm of black hornets.

Han Li immediately released his set of nine flying swords once again...

At this point in the Lost Grave Forest, there was a huge number of flying demon beasts in the area, and even though the ark was concealed, many of the demon beasts were able to see through the concealment.

There were certain days when the ark was attacked more than 10 times in a day, but thankfully, the man with the Kou surname was quite familiar with the layout of the forest, intentionally steering the ark so that it avoided all of the dwelling places of powerful demon beasts.

As a result, they were only attacked by demon beasts that weren't all that formidable, and given how Han Li and the woman in red were both actually True Immortal cultivators disguised as Body Integration cultivators, they naturally had no trouble dealing with these attacks.

The man with the Kou surname was feeling much more reassured upon seeing this.

However, as a result of all these attacks, the flying ark was frequently forced to slow down, so progress wasn't ideal.

Around a dozen more days passed by in the blink of an eye.

A giant white vortex formed by countless rapidly revolving white sword threads had completely enveloped a mountainous azure beast, trapping it inside.

The azure beast roared as a layer of metallic azure light surfaced over its entire body, keeping the countless surrounding sword threads at bay.

At the same time, it was blasting gusts of fierce azure wind out of its mouth in an attempt to shatter the vortex around it.

However, the white sword threads were extremely formidable, and they were able to quickly slice the dark azure light around the giant beast into shreds before piercing into its body.

The azure beast didn't even get a chance to cry out before it was sliced into a pile of meat by the countless sword threads.

With a wave of his hand, the countless sword threads converged to reform the nine flying swords at his behest, then flew back up his sleeve.

There were still several other azure beasts near the flying ark, and they were all quickly slain as well, following which the ark continued onward.

At this point, the vegetation of the forest down below was gradually becoming more sparse, exposing large sections of earth, and it seemed that they were finally about to fly out of the Lost Grave Forest.

After close to another half-day passed by, the forest down below had completely vanished.

The landscape up ahead was beginning to turn black, and there were some black rocks on the ground as a bleak desert appeared up ahead.

The ark suddenly began to slow down here, and the man with the Kou surname arrived along with the two Body Integration Stage elders.

"Up ahead is the Black Rock desert. It's already quite late now, so it won't be wise to keep going. We'll rest here for the night, then continue our journey tomorrow. Thank you for your hard work, seniors!"

Han Li immediately recalled that he had previously read about the Black Rock Desert in one of the books that he had purchased in Seaside City.

It was a perilous place where gravity was several times heavier than it was elsewhere, apparently because there were underground ore veins that were affecting the origin magnetic force in the region.

Furthermore, there were some extremely formidable dark beasts residing deep in the Black Wind Desert that lurked underground during the day, then came out at night.

Thankfully, the desert wasn't very large, so all of the people crossing this area would choose to do so as quickly as possible during the day.

The ark slowly descended toward the ground, and everyone on the ark was feeling rather weary. Aside from the two Body Integration Stage elders, who were on lookout duty, everyone retired to their rooms to rest.

Dusk slowly transitioned into night, and a bright full moon appeared in the sky.

There was not a single cloud to be seen in the sky above the entire desert, only countless dazzling stars that were flashing radiantly.

The ark was resting beside a giant rock, and it was completely enshrouded in darkness, with the only light on the ark coming from some lit lamps in the rooms.

Right at this moment, the door of one of the rooms on the ark swung open, and a figure emerged from within, silently treading over the ark quickly arriving on the desert outside.

It was none other than Han Li, and he was traveling along the desert in leaps and bounds. Once he was sufficiently far away from the ark, azure light emerged over his body, and he flew away into the distance.

Only after flying for close to 100,000 kilometers did he draw to a halt, then descended toward an oasis down below.

This desert oasis was only several hundred kilometers in area, and most of the plants here were sand poplar trees and hardy willow trees, which were capable of growing in dry, desert conditions. The trunks of these trees were generally only several dozen feet tall, and due to their constant exposure to the scorching sun and the fierce desert winds, their branches and leaves were all growing in a rather lopsided manner.

On the edge of this oasis was a miniature crescent-shaped lake, which was shimmering under the moonlight, presenting an alluring sight in the desert landscape.

Han Li made his way to the edge of the lake, then scooped up some water before drinking it out of his cupped hands, instantly filling his mouth with a cool and refreshing sensation.

He sat down onto the ground, then released his spiritual sense to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of tens of thousands of feet.

Shortly thereafter, he reached into the front for his robe and pulled out the Heaven Controlling Vial, which he carefully set down before himself.

As a ray of moonlight shone down upon the vial, it immediately began to glow, and all of the leaf patterns on its surface lit up, giving the entire vial a glittering and translucent appearance. A series of specks of white light took shape around the vial, transforming into giant halos of white light that were glowing radiantly.

The small lake was also instantly illuminated by the white light, and looking at it from afar, it was as if the lake had suddenly been frozen solid.